Pam?
Yeah?
Did you see Oprah yesterday?
No, I didn't.
I... I'm going to be a father.
What was Oprah about?
Angelina Jolie was on.
And she adopted a baby from Asia,
and she said that it changed her life,
and that really inspired me.
So I want you to look into see how
much a little Chinese baby would cost.
That's a really big decision.
I know.
Maybe you should wait
before you adopt.
Well...
Or not adopt.
Just do it, okay?
Roy's sister looked into it and
the application alone costs $1,000.
Well, find out
if there's a cheaper, less
expensive baby out there, okay?
You know, she also said the
waiting list is, like, eight months.
Eight months?
Yeah.
I don't even know if I want
a baby in eight months.
Probably won't.
You know what, Pam?
If in 10 years,
I haven't had a baby
and you haven't had a baby...
No, Michael.
Twenty years.
Thirty.
Sure.
It's a deal.
All right,
three pairs of pants.
Three pairs of socks.
Mmm-hmm.
Three packs of condoms.
Yes.
Fun jeans.
Right there.
Sign.
Per diem.
Guess where I
am going? I will give you a hint.
It is a booze-fuelled sex romp
where anything goes.
You are correct, sir!
I am headed to Philadelphia
for the annual Northeastern
Mid-Market Office Supply Convention.
And Jim Halpert is going
to be coming, which'll be fun.
Poor little guy has been stuck
working under Josh,
the poor man's Michael Scott,
as he is known around my condo.
Don't be mad,
it is a business trip.
But I don't understand.
It's for managers.
Monkey, I am an ARM,
Assistant Regional Manager.
I know! It's...
I was just really hoping we
could spend some time together.
Are you still there?
Yes, monkey.
Don't "monkey" me! You can't
wait to get out of here, ARM!
In the Martin family,
we like to say,
"Looks like someone took
the slow train from Philly."
That's code for
"Check out the slut."
What is...
Why are there flies in here?
Oh, my God! Are you
so excited for tonight?
I'm so excited. You guys
are gonna click, I can feel it.
So what are you wearing?
This.
You look so pretty.
Thank you.
Yes, I have a date.
He's a cartoonist
for the local paper,
which is really neat,
because I like to draw, too.
I'm kind of nervous.
I haven't been on a
first date in nine years.
Probably shouldn't
broadcast that.
Well, remember, no matter
how much you may want to,
do not sleep with him on the
first date, it gives him all the power.
Sleep with who?
Whom? Whom? Whom?
My neighbor, Alan. They're
going on a date tonight.
Oh, wow! Oh, my God,
I have a great idea.
You know what you should do? Be
hilarious. Wear your wedding dress.
It'd be a great icebreaker!
And your veil.
Yeah. Do it!
I'll probably just wear this.
Really?
Okay, well, word of advice,
unbutton that top button,
let those things breathe.
Any message you want me
to relate to Jim?
"Um," okay. Um...
You got that?
I got it.
Write it down.
I'll write it down.
Um, um, um, um...
There's my girl.
Noticed you handing out
some shekels.
How would one get
on that train?
That was per diem
for Philadelphia.
That town smells
like cheese steaks.
That town is full of history!
Andrea's the office bitch.
You'll get used to her.
Creed.
Can I have
my neck pillow back?
Michael!
Can I have
my neck pillow back?
Hey, Michael. MICHAEL:
Hey, Josh, how you doing?
Pretty good, how you doing?
Good to see you.
There he is! There's
the traitor. Traitor! Traitor!
Come here, you. Come here!
The... The progidal...
My son returns!
I was shocked when he told me
he was transferring to Stamford.
It's like with firemen, you
don't leave your brothers behind.
Even if you find out
that there is a better fire
in Connecticut.
It's really good to
see you, man. Yeah.
Wow. I didn't expect that.
It's good to see you, too.
Oh, hey, how's it going up there?
Have you made any sales yet?
Yeah, sold about 40,000.
Hey!
Shut up, that's impossible.
No, it's not, and I did, yeah.
Well, I did it, too.
You know, when I saw Dwight,
I realized
how stupid and petty
all those pranks
I pulled on him were.
And then he spoke.
I wonder how hard it would be
to get a copy of his room key.
So did you hear?
What?
Pam's back
on the market again.
Really? She's dating?
If I weren't engaged,
I would so hit that.
So what kind of commissions
you get up there?
Oh, Dwight,
I missed you so much.
You're so immature.
Listen, Michael, I heard
you were a great salesman,
and I just wanted
to let you know
that if our branch
absorbs your branch,
I'm gonna look for a
place for you in Stamford.
Oh, hey!
- Hey.
- Hey, Jan.
We all checked in?
Yes.
Great. Let's dump our stuff and
meet back down here in half an hour.
- Okay.
Jan?
Look, I think we need to set
some ground rules.
What are you talking about? The
800-pound gorilla in the room. Carole?
I'm still dating her,
so nothing can happen
between us at the convention.
Step away from me, Michael.
Thank you for being so brave
with all of this.
Thank you.
Alan's cartoon's
so funny, right?
And they're, like, so smart.
I don't even know what
they mean half the time.
This party is gonna
be awesome! I know!
That is specifically why I chose
a room close to the elevator.
More foot traffic.
Check it out.
That is crooked. On that side.
Wow.
Hey, hey!
- That is a lot of liquor.
- Yeah.
And a dartboard.
Well, that's how we do it in
Scranton, or did you forget?
Ain't no party like
a Scranton party
'cause a Scranton party
don't stop!
We should probably head on
down, you know, hook up with Jan.
Hey, well, we have time!
One for the road, gentlemen?
"A shot of Midori, perhaps?"
Oh, no, sorry,
it's an inside joke.
There's this bartender
in Stamford who...
You know what?
You just had to be there.
I wish I was!
I love inside jokes.
Love to be
a part of one someday.
We should...
Yeah!
All right, see you guys down
there. See you guys. All right.
Change your mind,
come back up.
I'll do a shot
with you, Michael.
Don't be gross.
It's not even lunch yet.
Swag!
Stuff we all get.
I basically decorated my condo
for free with all of my swag!
Check it out!
Oh, my God.
Hi! I'm Michael Scott,
Dunder Mifflin.
Dwight Schrute, Assistant
Regional Manager, Dunder Mifflin.
All right.
I'm a huge fan.
Thanks, appreciate it, guys.
You know what?
I'm having a big blowout tonight,
Room 308, hope you can come.
All right, maybe. If I can.
Well, cool!
Okay, so can I tell people
you're gonna be there?
No, you cannot.
So maybe. See you.
Why do they call him "The
Bus"? Because he's afraid to fly.
Smile!
Do you remember me
from last year?
There's a party
in my room, 308.
Can't miss it,
right off the elevator.
Tonight! Be there!
All right,
Jan just e-mailed me.
She wants us to
meet her up front.
Yup! Yeah, she's up front. You
don't have e-mail on your phone.
I don't have to, I just know.
Yes? Hello?
No one just called you.
All right. Nice meeting you.
Take care.
Nice to meet you.
I'll see you soon.
Yeah, stop by.
Take care.
See you in a bit. Bye-bye.
May I have
a moment of your time, please?
I need you to do something
for me. Yes, anything.
I want you to
dig up some dirt on Josh,
find out if there are
any skeletons in his attic.
I'll talk to my buddy down
at the station, stat.
Hey, Pam.
Hey, what's up?
It's... How are...
I might ask if you wanted...
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
He's not in the office.
Can I take a message?
I will.
You, too.
Sorry, what's up?
If...
I just completely forgot
what I was gonna say.
It's so weird.
Okay.
Well, if you think of it,
I'll be here.
Okay.
So I called my buddy down
at the station today
to have him run a background
check on Josh Porter,
see if there's any known
aliases, etcetera.
And?
He wasn't volunteering today.
Yeah. Things have been
pretty crazy around the office.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
We moved Ryan
over to your desk...
Tell him I say hi. I will call
him later with that message.
Hey, how's Toby?
Toby Flenderson is everything
that is wrong with the paper industry.
Is he why you left?
Oh, no, it was just, you know, a
good opportunity for me, a promotion.
I got a chance to... Opportunity,
promotion, blah, blah...
You know, Jim,
those are just words.
Have you taken into account
other factors, vis-a-vis bosses?
Is Josh funnier than I am?
Does he even have a girlfriend?
Because I have two, basically.
Michael, it's really
not a competition.
Jim got us a great lead with the
new rep from National Envelope.
Really? Great. We can
grab lunch with him tomorrow.
Hey, Jan? Jan? Don't
worry, I have got the tip.
Whoa, Michael!
Wow!
Oh, my God, thank you!
Hey, no problem.
Was that your per diem? No,
that was a different $100 bill.
What have you generated,
Michael?
I have generated a lot of
interest in my party this evening.
What party?
The party I'm having tonight in
308, obviously, you are invited.
Michael, Jim and Josh
are in meetings all day,
and I am in and out
of meetings.
I... I can't
stay on top of you 24/7.
You should order the most
expensive thing on the menu.
So he knows you're worth it.
If you do that,
you're gonna have to put out.
Oh, yeah,
you'll have to put out.
Is there a key for a Jane Doe?
Thank you.
Any messages for 3087
All right.
Hey, hey, fellers.
Michael!
Hey, Michael!
What's up?
Well, Jim and I have a meeting
with uni-ball in about 45 minutes,
so we should probably go now.
Hey, check this out!
How about that?
A little friendly competition.
Stamford versus Scranton. I
don't think so... I don't really...
Jim, looks like you picked a
bad time to defect, my friend.
Fine, all right.
Okay! Excellent.
Do the wing flaps.
Oh, just shut it.
Hey, Pam, what's up?
Yeah. No, tell him I will give him
general specifics tomorrow, okay?
Yes. Say hi to Pam!
Hi, Pam!
Hi, Pam.
Yes. That is Josh
and Dwight and Jim.
Pam says hi.
Have fun on your date.
Very good,
talk to you later. Bye.
You first!
Come on.
Nice try, Josh!
Not. Hit the... Hit the rim.
Okay, and...
Okay, double or nothing.
On what? We didn't bet
anything, Michael, we...
Well, we... Let's... You know,
we should go. We gotta go.
Come on. Come on!
We'll do it later.
Let's go...
Say, while I have you here,
could I talk to you about some
new and exciting advances
to our product line?
Fine.
Jim and I have different
definitions of friendship.
I think it's talking
and being friends,
and Jim thinks
it's moving to Connecticut
and being best friends
with Josh. Well...
Phooey on that.
I'm done. I am not going to
be speaking with him anymore.
Whatevs. Long-distance
relationships never work.
That is so true.
Ready?
Okay, let me tell you what
we're looking for. Great.
Sorry,
my meeting ran late.
Really?
Yes, Jan, really,
with the rep from Hammermill.
They're exclusive
with Staples.
Used to be.
Evan'll call you in the
morning to work out the details.
We can now
sell Hammermill products.
Yes!
Well, Michael, I just...
I underestimated you.
Yeah, well, maybe next time
you will estimate me.
Dwight's room key.
And Dwight's room.
What can I say?
Old habits die hard.
D?
Oh, my God!
Dwight got a hooker!
Oh, my God, I gotta call...
Well, I gotta call somebody,
I don't even know who to call.
Dwight got a hooker!
So, Alan, Pam is
obsessed with your cartoons.
She reads them every day.
Oh, great.
I don't like ketchup.
You love ketchup!
He loves ketchup.
So how do you come up
with your cartoons?
Oh, I just... I kind of
think about stuff that I see.
Or dream them.
You dream in cartoons?
How fun.
Hey! First guest!
You are going to have
some tequila, my friend.
I thought there was a party
in here. This is the party.
This is Room 308?
Party central!
So what can I do you for?
All right.
See, this one is great
because it could work
on a couple different levels.
"More freedom fries
for the table?"
"Freedom fries". Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, people always
say, like, "Don't be edgy,"
but I don't know...
I don't know any other way.
Yeah, you got it.
Well, it was... It was really
nice meeting you, Alan.
Yeah, next time bring
some of your illustrations.
I'll let you pick my brain.
"More freedom fries"!
Yeah!
That's great.
Okay.
I went on a date.
It wasn't a love connection.
I think when I like someone
again, I'll just kind of know.
Michael.
Am I the first to arrive?
People have been
filtering in and out.
Can I get a drink?
What?
Sure.
Do you like Cosmos?
Yeah, sure, sounds good.
So why are you here?
Is Josh busy?
Michael...
I get it!
Did I do something or...
No. No, I totally get it!
He made
a better paper airplane,
Stamford does better
in sales. You...
I get it, we had some fun.
We had some laughs...
Wait, wait, wait. I didn't
transfer because of you.
You're a good boss.
You're a great boss.
I'm not better than Josh.
Michael, it's not about...
I transferred because of Pam.
Oh, my God.
You don't even know.
She's single now.
No, I... I heard something
about that.
It's just... I kind of
put it all on the line.
Twice, actually.
And she said no.
Twice.
I'm sorry, man,
I'm sorry, it's...
Hey, you know what?
I will talk to her.
Nope, that's okay.
Yeah.
No, that's all right.
I will. I'll talk to her.
You should at least
talk to Roy,
I mean, he knows exactly
how you're feeling, just...
Yeah.
Okay, maybe.
Are we early?
Hey! No, you know, people
have been filtering in and out.
Hey. Evan, this is Jim.
How are you?
Hey, Arnie Rissman,
Michael, Jim.
Hey, Arnie, how you doing?
You guys work together?
No, we used to.
Yeah.
Now we're friends.
Best friends.
Some people need dozens of friends
to say, "Hey, look at me, I'm popular!”
But not me. I'm very picky.
I need three, maybe two.
When you meet that someone
special, you'll just know,
because a real relationship,
it can't be forced.
It should just
come about effortlessly.
Now would you do me the
pleasure of hitting the lights, sir?
What are
all those stains?
Blood, urine,
or semen.
Oh, God,
I hope it's urine.