Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas... No!
Why did you
bring that here?
Don't worry, she's dead.
Oh, wait.
He's dead.
Dwight? What...
I accidentally
ran over it.
It's a Christmas miracle.
Well, get it out of here.
Relax, okay? And
because this is Christmas,
I am going to
roast this goose
and prepare it with
a wild rice dressing.
Do we have any cayenne pepper
in the kitchen?
Merry Christmas, Dwight.
Jim.
Wow. What do we
got here?
What does it look like?
Dead goose.
And circle gets the square.
All right.
So, can you watch this?
I'm gonna get
my carving knife
out of the trunk.
Oh, Dwight,
we talked about this.
No, Toby,
this is different.
He's already dead.
Once I brought in a duck to prepare
for lunch, and people got upset.
Apparently they got
attached to the duck
and didn't want
to see it killed.
He was already dead,
and we Schrutes use
every part of the goose.
The meat has a delicious,
smoky, rich flavor.
Plus, you can use
the molten goose grease,
and save it in
the refrigerator,
thus saving you
a trip to the store
for a can of
expensive goose grease.
Wow. Win-win.
Exactly. Thank you, Jim.
I like goose.
And it's already dead.
Is it so crazy
if we eat it?
That's crazy.
It's crazy.
Dwight, you cannot
keep that here.
Okay, that is ridiculous, and
totally against the spirit of Christmas.
Come on, Dwight, we went
over this, like, for half an hour.
It's Christmas, Toby.
It's a dead animal in
our office. You can't...
Toby...
I'm sorry.
Please. Please.
Clean it in your car.
I would like it
off my desk.
Oh, Pam, take a chill pill.
Deck the halls
with boughs of holly
Fa, Ia,
la, la, Ia, Ia, Ia, la, la
'Tis...
Hey! I would like a nice
slice of Christmas Pam.
Side of candied Pams.
And perhaps,
some Pam chops...
Can I help you, Michael?
...with mint.
I'm looking for
the Toy Drive box.
It's behind you.
Okay.
Well, I need to put
this bike in there.
I hope it will fit, with all
these little knick-knacks.
Wow. What kind
of bike is that?
I don't know.
Average kind.
The tires look pretty worn.
Well, that is
probably from the test drive.
But the paint's chipping.
Is that your
old bike, Michael?
No.
Yo, Michael.
Sweet ride, Mike.
Oh, thanks.
Michael?
Yes?
Oh, Pam, that is so sweet.
You didn't have to do that.
I didn't.
It's from corporate.
Okay. Did everybody
get one of these?
Yep.
Terrific. Good.
This is going to be
the best Christmas ever.
My girlfriend, Carole, is
coming to our party tonight
and I have
a little surprise for her.
I've got two
tickets to paradise
Pack your bags We're
leaving day after tomorrow
I'm taking her to Sandals,
Jamaica, all-inclusive.
All-inclusive.
You know what
that means, right?
Yeah!
I think you're supposed to
put a toy in the box, Creed.
And a happy holiday to you.
Carole.
Hi. Is Michael
around here?
There she is!
A Christmas Carole. Hello.
You're about five
hours early to the party.
Oh, you're such a blonde.
Michael...
Hey, everybody? I don't
know who you haven't met yet,
but I think this
is one of them.
This is my girlfriend,
Carole.
This is just
the front of her.
Show them the other side.
What?
Turn around.
Turn around. Come on.
Get out of here!
No, you get out of here.
Michael?
Yes.
If I may say, she's even
prettier than you described her.
Oh, ouch! Michael, I don't
think there's anything wrong
with the way
you described her.
Thank you.
I really need
a moment alone with you.
Not as much as I need
What is this?
That is my Christmas card.
It's a picture of you
and me and your kids
on a ski trip,
having a blast.
"Ski-eason's Greetings."
No. See,
we never went on a ski trip.
I know. I know.
I went on a ski trip...
Right.
...two years ago with my kids
and my ex-husband.
Yes, but what you
didn't realize at the time
was that I was
with you, in a sense.
I was in your heart...
Michael... ...and next
to your kids. What?
This is so weird.
I don't understand.
It's a bold move to
Photoshop yourself
into a picture with your
girlfriend and her kids
on a ski trip
with their real father.
But then again,
Michael's a bold guy.
Is "bold" the right word?
I think you're
a really sweet guy.
Okay.
But I don't know
how to deal with
this thing, and the proposal,
and I don't think things
are gonna work out with us.
No. No,
no, no, no, no. Okay. Okay.
You know what?
You're not thinking straight.
You know what you need?
You need to think
this through in...
"Jamaica's largest
freshwater pool!"
What are you
talking about?
I got us tickets
to Sandals, Jamaica.
We leave day after tomorrow.
You had better find the
skimpiest bikini there is.
Michael...
And it's all-inclusive.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
No... Carole?
You walk out that
door and it is over.
I know.
Jim?
Hey.
I need to give you your
Christmas gift now, because...
Well, I'll just tell you.
What?
For the past few months,
I've been sending Dwight
letters from the CIA.
Are you serious?
They're considering him
for a top-secret mission.
There's his application.
Oh, and this is where
I made him list every secret
he promised
he'd never, ever tell.
"Last year, my boss,
Michael Scott, took a day off
"because he said
he had pneumonia,
"but, really, he was leaving
early to go to magic camp." Wow.
So, here's the gift.
You get to decide what
his top-secret mission is.
Sorry I didn't wrap it.
You know what?
I really don't
think I should be
doing this stuff
anymore, though.
No, just because
of the promotion.
Oh, yeah.
Just feels
a little bit like...
No, I get it.
Of course. Okay.
I feel like there's a chance
for me to start over.
And if I fall back into the
same kind of things I used to do,
then what am I doing?
I'd like
everybody's attention.
Christmas is canceled.
You can't cancel a holiday.
Keep it up, Stanley,
and you'll lose New Year's.
What does that mean?
Jim, take New Year's
away from Stanley.
Michael, what's going on?
Carole and I split up.
Amicably.
And I just don't think
it would be appropriate
to celebrate under
the circumstances.
Will they still air Rudolph?
That's not fair!
Are we going to
cancel Hanukkah as well?
Fine! Have your party.
Just no guests.
But we invited guests.
Well, you know what, Phyllis?
All of your guests
would have probably canceled
at the last minute anyway,
leaving your life a stupid,
rotten mess.
So. Okay.
It hurts.
I know.
It hurts my heart.
It hurts my stomach.
It hurts my arms.
Okay, well,
why are you laying like that?
Thanks.
How did you push
away the bad thoughts?
Like what?
Like maybe,
the real reason they left
was because
there were things
they wanted you to
do in bed that were...
What...
...foreign and scary?
I...
I don't really...
And not that you
didn't want to try them.
Some wine
might have helped.
Do you know what
I'm referring to?
I don't
need to know.
Michael?
Yeah?
Sorry to interrupt.
It appears we're
one bathrobe short.
Take it from Toby.
Copy.
Pam, would you like to go
to Sandals, Jamaica with me?
It's all... Okay.
No, thank you.
Hey, Dwight.
Pretty nice robes. I...
Why?
Phyllis, I need you to pick
up green streamers at lunch.
I thought you said
green was whorish.
No. Orange is whorish.
So, I had
a couple of ideas
to make the Stamford
people feel more at home.
Each year we have
a Christmas raffle...
Okay.
It would never work here.
Another idea was karaoke.
No.
A Christmas drinking game.
Yes!
God help you.
What?
These are all
terrible ideas.
And none of them are on the
theme of a Nutcracker Christmas.
I think you should leave.
You're kidding.
You tried this out,
and it's clearly not for you.
It's time to go.
Come on. Please? Thank you.
Okay. Thank you very much.
You
touched my heart you touched my soul
You changed my
life and all my goals
I know you well
I know your smell
What are you doing?
We're getting rid of everything
that reminds you of Carole.
Hey, what's the haps?
Carole?
Oh, look at this.
Your old condo
closing papers.
It's riddled
with Carole's name.
I wish I could
throw this in the box.
You have been
the one for me
Why don't you just
buy the whole song?
I don't have to buy it.
I just want to taste it.
I just want... I just
want a little taste of it.
Look at this,
she saved you $2,000
because they failed to
report a mold problem.
But wouldn't that
affect the final...
How did she...
Oh, I see what she did.
That is good.
Wow. That Carole
is one smart cookie.
Goodbye my lover,
goodbye my friend
You have been the one
You have been the one for me
You touched my heart,
you touched my soul...
This is an old adage.
But they say that
when you find true love,
you know within
the first 24 hours.
With Carole,
I knew within the first 24 minutes
of the second day I met her.
I feel like I've been
kind of cold to Karen.
And there's no
real reason for it.
I mean, it's not like she's
ever done anything to me.
So, I think I probably
shouldn't be cold to her.
Hey, Karen, sorry
about that meeting today.
That was really crazy.
Yeah, right?
I'm so glad you said that.
Because I don't know how
those meetings usually go.
Usually like that.
Does anyone ever
stand up to Angela? Or...
I think one of
her cats did once.
She came in with
scratches all over her face.
Right.
I really liked
your karaoke idea.
Oh, cool, yeah.
That could really be fun.
You guys do a raffle?
Thank you.
Yeah, we do a raffle.
Hey, Kev.
Hey.
This should have
been up yesterday.
It'll be all right.
What is that?
"The Committee to
Plan Parties invites you
"to a Margarita
-Karaoke-Christmas"?
There's no such thing as
the Committee to Plan Parties!
There is now.
We just started it.
Well, you can't
just start a committee.
You have to have funding.
What's your funding?
Two hundred dollars.
What's ours again?
Two hundred and one dollars.
Right.
Hey, a margarita-karaoke-
Christmas party.
That sounds like fun.
No. That is not a party.
There is only one party,
and it's hosted
by the Party
Planning Committee,
and it starts at 3:00.
Then why are
there two flyers?
I understand that this is confusing
for everyone. Let me explain.
There's a party
that starts at 3:00...
Right.
...and then there's a way more
fun party that starts at 2:45.
Right, and if you're interested
in the way-more-fun party,
all the info
can be found here,
on our more
brightly colored flyer.
I didn't see where it was.
Yep, looks like the Scranton
people and the Stamford people
are finally coming together.
And that's what
you want, right?
I think that's really...
Pam and Karen,
I am ordering you
to cease and desist
all party
planning immediately.
You can't do that.
As ranking number three
in this office, I am order...
I'm number three.
You're number four.
Yeah, but I'm number three.
No.
You must turn over to me
all Christmas decorations
and party
paraphernalia immediately.
They will be returned
to you on January 4.
Okay,
I think I can help here.
Okay, good.
As ranking number two,
I am starting
a committee to determine
the validity of
the two committees,
and I am the sole member.
The committee
will act on this now.
Okay, this is stupid.
Could you
please keep it down?
I'm in session.
I have determined
that this committee is valid.
Yeah! What? No! No!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait.
Permission to join
the Validity Committee.
Permission denied.
Damn it.
Hey. I can't concentrate when
I know you're in pain, man.
Let me take you to lunch.
Come on! My treat.
All right.
Nothing here to
distract myself with anyway.
That's my boy.
I know
the perfect place, too.
Hooters?
No. Benihana.
Much classier.
But don't worry, the
babes are totally hot, too.
I need my entourage.
Jim! Dwight! Ryan. Come on.
We're going to Asian Hooters.
Oh, man, I can't.
Why not?
I'm not feeling so well.
I got a ton of
work to do here.
MSG allergy, peanut allergy.
I just ate there last night.
All right. Feel better.
Thanks.
Come on, Jim, let's go.
Okay.
Wow! Thanks for taking
all the excuses, dude.
Doctor appointment.
Car trouble. Planter warts.
Grandad fought
in World War ll.
Use your head, man.
I keep mine in here.
Look alive, Halpert.
Welcome back.
Bros before hos. Why?
Because your bros are
always there for you.
They have got your back
after your ho rips your
heart out for no good reason.
And you were nothing
but great to your ho,
and you told her that she
was the only ho for you,
and that she was better than
all the other hos in the world.
And then...
Then suddenly she's
not your ho no mo'!
So she looks
really hot, so I said,
"You look hotter than
usual today." Thank you.
Michael?
Head of the table.
May 1?
Actually, sir,
I'm going to need to
take this chair, so...
Dwight, just leave him.
Leave them alone, please.
They are on a date.
They look very happy.
So she looks at me,
right, and she goes,
“I'm sorry.
Do I even know you?"
After a year!
A year of buying
lattes from her.
Do you believe that?
Yes.
I can't hear
what you're saying.
Carole used to drink lattes.
Who're you talking about?
She would get this
little foam mustache...
Carole had a mustache?
...and I used to say,
"Hey, got latte?"
And she'd say,
"That's not funny."
What are you
guys talking about?
She totally got me.
She understood
that we didn't have
to laugh... Michael?
...to enjoy each other.
Michael.
What?
Repeat what you said louder!
It is my job to be
there for Michael.
How can I be
there for Michael
if I'm here for Michael?
I'm already starting to forget
what color eyes she had.
I can't...
Okay, I'm gonna call her.
I am going to call
and find out... No!
Who are you calling?
Put it away.
Put that away.
I'm going to call her.
SOS! We...
Hi. Mayday!
Man down over here.
We need your help.
What can I get for you?
I think we'll start
with a round of Nagasakis.
One part eggnog,
three parts sake.
Some places won't make it for you,
though, because eggnog is seasonal.
You should put out
salt for the rims.
That's a great idea.
Phyllis?
I was just getting a snack.
You can have
your snack in here.
Pam, don't tell her
what to do. Phyllis?
Okay.
I think I'll go
to Angela's party,
because that's
the party I know.
I miss the days when there was
only one party I didn't want to go to.
So, I only use three?
If you're using more than three
pieces of tape to wrap a present,
you're doing it wrong.
Okay. And where'd you get
all those cool bows?
Oh, I just get those
at any party supply place.
Okay.
Are you sure I
can't use, like,
the cartoons
from the newspaper?
Oh, yeah,
your mom will love that.
Hey.
All right,
I'll see you guys later.
Bye.
He's cute.
You should date him.
Yeah, maybe.
Looks like you got a little
Nakiri knife action going there.
No, is Usuba.
Yeah, I bet you wish you had
a Nakiri, though.
Actually,
the Usuba is the better knife
when you working
with this quantity.
I don't know.
Still think Nakiri's better.
I think he'd know.
Nothing he's doing
is cheering me up.
Wait for the onion.
Trust me.
Hey, Cindy,
he just had his heart broken.
You wouldn't do
that to him, would you?
I don't know.
Sure you would!
Look at you.
I bet you break up
with a guy every hour.
You made her laugh! Yes!
She totally digs us.
Watch. Watch. Watch.
What did I tell you?
You're right. That's good.
Hello, everyone.
We would just
like to announce that
our party is starting
now in the break room.
So...
I have a very important announcement
to make about your paychecks.
Your paychecks will be
arriving, as scheduled, on Friday.
And they will be in the correct
amount that they normally are in.
Please stand by for a very
important announcement
further
regarding your paycheck!
I need to know if I
can start the party.
Michael.
Hey!
Over here! Michael!
It's...
I don't know.
No one can hear me.
You know what?
Start the party.
Did Michael give you
permission to do this?
Start the party.
Also, I would like
to inform you
that, as a special treat, my
party will be starting early.
In fact, it will be
starting right now.
Our party is also
starting now. Yeah.
All right, Stanley!
Good choice!
Welcome, Hannah!
You will not be disappointed!
Why would I be disappointed?
I said you
wouldn't be disappointed.
Meredith, if you don't come to my
party, you will be very, very sorry.
That a threat?
No, it's an invitation.
We have vodka!
Lots of it.
I hear Angela's party will
have double-fudge brownies.
It will also have Angela.
So double-fudge, Angela.
Double-fudge,
Angela.
Brownies. Cupcakes.
Don't push it.
Are we taking this
too far?
You know what, I don't think
we're taking this far enough.
What?
I got goosebumps.
I don't back down.
My sister and I used
to be best friends,
and we haven't
talked in 16 years
over some disagreement
I don't even remember.
So...
Yeah, I'm pretty good.
Mmm.
Damn, this chicken is good!
My compliments to the chef,
which is you!
Right?
Awesome! I need some meat.
I want some steak.
That guy's got steak.
I see steak!
Excuse me.
En garde!
It's family style.
No. It's not.
Cindy! Cindy.
I love steak. I love it!
I want you to close your eyes
and imagine your dream house.
Come on!
Do it for Michael.
He's had a really
long day.
What're you doing?
This is great.
Jim! Jim!
Okay...
Cindy, you are so...
What...
What's happening?
She's asleep.
Narcolepsy.
Probably.
Okay. Now, open your eyes
and describe it to me.
I don't know.
It has four
bedrooms and a loft.
Oh, my God! Now she's up.
Yeah.
And she's trying to describe
how to correctly butcher a goose.
But she's having
trouble coming up with it.
Okay. Cindy! Yo!
Cindy! Cindy!
Hold its neck back, insert
the knife beneath the jaw,
bring it all the way around.
There's gonna be
a good amount of blood.
But don't let
that bother you.
Have a bucket
there for the blood,
and the innards,
and the feathers.
Oh, no, this is different.
The CIA thing,
that was a prank on Dwight.
This is more like a...
Okay. It's pretty
much the same thing.
What do you think?
Fruity, and delicious.
See, I told you.
You want one, Meredith?
No, thanks.
They're too sweet.
Hey, so, what's the status?
It looks like they
forgot the power cord.
What?
Oh, you're kidding me!
No.
Oh, God.
You guys... Guys?
I'm sorry, but there's a problem
with the karaoke machine.
What?
Well, that blows!
Hang on, little ladies.
You don't need this thing.
I'll go grab my synthesizer.
All right!
Yeah, Darryl!
Darryl! Darryl! Darryl!
Hey.
Hey, look, when you get
done with your meeting,
you should come
to the break room.
We having a party.
Oh, okay.
All right. See y'all.
These nuts are
really hard to crack.
Try harder, then.
No one has seconds
until everyone's had some.
You've got to be kidding!
You've got
to be kidding!
Cold, huh?
That'll help.
Is it cold in there?
They have been
checking us out all night!
I'm not kidding!
You know what we should do?
What?
We should invite them
to the Christmas party.
Now you are
thinking! Yes!
And you know what?
Because you've had such
a rough day, you get Cindy.
You are such a mensch,
my friend.
Okay! Where is everybody?
I would like them to
meet my new girlfriend.
I'm sure they'll
want to meet her, too.
The least I could do was
give some poor sick kid a bike.
That rocks.
No, you rock.
Tell you what,
if you want it, it's yours.
Thanks!
I wanna give you something.
Oh!
That's what she said.
Hello! I would like everybody
to meet my new girlfriend.
And my new girlfriend.
Where's Dwight?
Is he the hot one
or the giant baby?
The giant baby.
Wow. I am so sorry.
I had no idea this
party'd be so lame.
There's another
party in the break room.
Oh, party in the break room!
Let's go!
Let's go. Thank God.
- Let's go to the break room!
- Excuse me!
Waitress lady! Hey!
Where do you think
you're going with that?
I thought I could have it.
No, you can't have it!
I don't walk into your house and
steal your Hello Kitty backpack!
Shut it!
Come on. Party.
Hey! It's Angela!
Hey...
We're going to the...
I want you to know
That I'm happy for you
I wish nothing but...
I just think that there are two
specific kinds of people in the world.
People who own houses,
and people who own condos.
And my question to
you is, do you agree?
Do I agree about what?
"Do you agree about what?"
Wow! You're lucky
you're so darn cute.
What're you
talking about?
What are you talking about?
And I'm here to remind you
Of the mess you
left when you went away
It's not fair to deny me
Of the cross I bear
that you gave to me
You, you, you, you, you,
you, you Oughta know!
Nice. Way to go, Kev!
Good work!
Yeah!
Did you have
fun at Benihana's?
No!
It was awful.
I couldn't hear anything.
I've had
the worst day here.
Dwight, you won the raffle.
No way! Yeah!
Open it. Open it.
Do you like it?
Walkie-talkies.
Can I talk to you for a
second? - Yes!
Well, the Committee to Plan
Parties has served its purpose.
We're gonna disband
in the name of Christmas.
In the name of
Nutcracker Christmas.
Angela?
We've been hearing really
great things about your brownies,
and we were hoping you'd
consider merging the two parties.
I'm not sure.
Does your karaoke machine
have Christmas songs?
Yeah, but we don't
have a power cord.
I may have seen it somewhere.
Is it this one?
Yeah, thanks.
We'll go tell everyone.
Okay.
And if you want love
We'll make it
Swim in a big sea
of blankets
Take all your big plans
And break 'em
This is bound to take a while
your body is a wonderland
Your body is a wonderland
Your hands
I'll use my hands on it
Something 'bout the way
your hair falls in your face
Whatever we deny or embrace
For worse or for better
We belong, we belong
We belong together, Ryan
When you know, you just know.
Right?
Right.
Check her out.
Which one?
My little gal over there?
Babelectable.
Which one is she?
It's the...
It's one of those two.
You don't know?
Dude, you should know.
Yeah, well, it's been hard. They're
wearing the exact same uniform,
and I've been drinking,
and, you know how all
waitresses look alike.
I honestly don't see
what the big deal is.
Stevie Wonder is married.
Are you going to tell me
that Stevie Wonder
doesn't love his wife
just because he's not sure
what she looks like?
Hey!
Where's my girl?
Is she in the fridge?
Where is she hiding?
I don't know where she is!
'Cause I'm drunk.
I can't even find her.
You know where I am.
I do!
Hi! I just haven't
hugged you in a while.
Good. That felt good.
Let's go. Party!
Spinning and
reeling with love
Given the time
I might come back down
But it feels so good
My feet don't
touch the ground
Well, everybody knows
I'm crazy about you
Monkey, this is possum.
Do you copy?
Copy, possum.
What's your 20?
No way.
What a horrible,
horrible movie that was.
And now we get to
remember it forever.
Thank you.
Hey!
Hey, you!
How are you?
This party blows,
SO we're gonna leave.
No, no, no.
Hey, you should stay,
because we are
having fun, and...
Cool.
Where do you wanna go?
We're just gonna take off.
You know what?
I... Okay, listen.
I like you.
I really like you.
So much, in fact, that I would
like you to accompany me
on a trip to Sandals,
Jamaica.
Nah, I have school.
Can I help? Okay.
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas.
Lady,
from the moment I saw you
Standing all alone
You gave all
the love that I needed
That waitress was the one.
No, she wasn't.
How can you be sure?
Well, for starters,
I've known you as a couple
since the beginning
of the relationship,
which was approximately
three hours ago...
Don't make fun of me.
You're making fun of me.
Sorry.
I guess I didn't
know her very well.
I marked her arm.
You what?
I put a mark on her arm
so I could tell them apart.
I don't... I know. I know.
I can't believe I
gave her my bike.
Yeah.
Why do I feel like crap?
You just had a rebound.
I had a rebound.
Yeah.
Which, don't get me wrong,
can be a really fun distraction.
But, when it's over,
you're left thinking about
the girl you really like,
the one that
broke your heart.
I totally rebounded.
Someone else shoots, and
I take the ball and I score.
Well, I guess I
didn't really score,
and I'm not sure who is
actually shooting, but...
Whatever!
Doesn't matter.
It's all good.
Or, as my ex might say,
"Domo arigato, Mr. Scotto!"
Little baby
Pa rum pum pum pum
I am a poor boy, too
I have no gift to bring
Pa rum pum pum pum
That's fit to give a king
Pa rum pum pum pum...
Yeah. Yes,
I just wanted to see
if you would like to
come to Jamaica with me.
There's this
resort called Sandals.
Really?
Okay. All right.
I promise you
won't be disappointed.
It's all-inclusive.
Shall I play for you?
Pa rum pum pum pum
Too soon.
I played my drum for Him
Pa rum pum pum pum
I played my best for Him
Rum pum pum pum
Night, Pam.
Night.
Oh, you know what?
Sorry, I forgot to tell you. I
intercepted a transmission earlier,
and it seems that the CIA
is gonna need Dwight
down in their headquarters
at Langley for training
and an ice cream social
with the other agents.
We should get him a bus
ticket to make his trip easier.
Oh, no, that
would be great. We should try.
It costs $75.
Well, maybe the CIA
could send a helicopter.
"You have been compromised.
Abort mission. Destroy phone."
"Destroy phone."