There you go.
Nice dress, Ryan.
It's not a dress,
it's a kurta.
Okay.
Tonight, one of our most
ethnic co-workers, Kelly,
has invited us all to a Diwali
celebration put on by her community.
What is Diwali, you may ask?
Well, to have Kelly
explain it,
"It's... I have...
It's so super fun and it's gonna be great."
A lot of gods with
unpronounceable names.
Twenty minutes later you find out
that it's essentially a Hindu Halloween.
You look so handsome.
You really do.
I love the material.
I know.
How come
you didn't get me one?
Okay. So, between
Meredith's minivan
and if I borrow Bob's Yukon
that should fit about 12 people.
I actually might not go.
I'm feeling kind of tired.
Do you want to make Appletinis and
watch Sex and the City at my place?
Oh, I don't know.
I haven't decided yet.
I don't get why you won't go.
Did I do something wrong?
I mean, I thought
we were really close friends.
I just feel
kind of tired, you know?
Maybe you've got mono.
Maybe.
I just... I don't really
have anyone to go with.
Well, go with Dwight.
He's single too, right?
Yeah, totally single.
Hundred percent available.
Are you guys going to this
Indian thing tonight?
I don't know.
Who's... Who's going?
Oh, you mean like,
"Is Pam going?"
Don't go.
They eat monkey brains.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop that.
That is offensive. Indians
do not eat monkey brains.
And if they do, sign me up
because I am sure that they
are very tasty and nutritional.
It's important that this
company celebrates its diversity.
And you know what, Stanley,
come Kwanza time,
I have got you covered, baby.
I don't
celebrate Kwanza.
Really?
You should. It's fun.
I love the people here.
And if there was one thing
I don't really care for,
is that they can be
terribly, terribly ignorant
about other cultures.
And I don't want them embarrassing
me in front of my girlfriend, Carole.
Diwali is a very important
holiday for the Hindus.
But frankly,
I'm a little appalled
that none of you know very
much about Indian culture.
So, without further ado,
Kelly, you are on!
Diwali is awesome and there's
food and there's gonna be dancing,
and I got the raddest outfit.
Kelly?
It has sparkles...
Why don't you tell us a little bit
about the origins of the holiday?
Oh, I don't know.
It's really old, I think.
How many gods do you have?
Like hundreds, I think,
maybe more. I don't know.
And that blue, busty gal,
what's her story?
She looks like Pam
from the neck down.
Pam wishes.
Kelly, I'll take this one.
Diwali is a celebration of the
coronation of the God-king Rama
after his epic battle with
Ravana, the demon-king of Lanka.
It symbolizes the battle...
All right...
...between good and evil...
...all right.
This isn't Lord of the Rings.
Here we are.
I'm sorry.
I started biking to work.
Josh does it and he lives
a lot farther away than I do.
And also it saves gas money, keeps
me in shape, helps the environment
and now I know it makes me
really sweaty for work.
Nice basket.
Thank you.
Now a lot of people say that
Kelly is one in a million
and that's true, but it's also
not true, because frankly,
there are literally billions of
people just like Kelly in the world.
Here are some famous Indians.
Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar.
He is a Nobel Prize-winning
physicist. Impressive.
Apu from The Simpsons.
Hilarious Indian.
M. Night Shyamalan, The
Village, Unbreakable, Sixth Sense...
"I see dead people."
Okay.
Spoiler alert.
He was dead the whole time.
Just stop it.
What's... Oh, what?
Where did that come from?
Karen, my chips got stuck
in the vending machine again.
I need
your skinny little arms.
Oh.
Did you shake it?
Yeah, I shook it, I shook it.
We have such a
roller-coaster thing, Karen and I.
Excuse me?
Roller-coastery friendship.
Hot and cold, on again, off again,
sexual tension-filled type of deal.
It's very Sam and Diane.
Wow. Yeah?
From Cheers. Yeah.
And another thing about the Indian
people, they love sex positions.
I present to you
the Kama Sutra.
I mean, look at that.
Who has seen that before?
I have,
that's Union of the Monkey.
Oh, that's what they call it.
This is the best meeting
we have ever had.
Thank you, Kevin.
You know, I find this
incredibly offensive.
Well, I find it beautiful.
Well, whatever Kelly wants
to do in her own house is fine,
but we shouldn't all
be subjected to it.
Actually, she's right.
This is inappropriate.
Why don't I take these?
No, you're not
going to collect them.
Yeah. No, this is a
delightful, charming culture.
My Indian cultural seminar
was going great until
Toby decided he was too immature
to deal with culturally explicit images.
It's just sex, people,
everybody does it.
I'm doing it with Carole
probably tonight.
All right, I think you guys
should be all set.
Oh, here's the corporate
card for dinner Thanks.
Now, Karen, let's keep it
to $20 a person this time.
Got it.
Okay.
Once a quarter, the sales staff
of this branch has to stay late
to do order form
consolidation which,
amazingly, is even less
interesting than it sounds.
You guys ready to party?
What's that?
I said,
"Are you ready to party!"
Isn't this fun?
Not wearing shoes?
I wish some of us
still had our shoes on.
Stop it. It's a disease.
I told you.
I thought you said
this was a costume party.
What does that
look like to you?
An Indian woman in a sari.
No one's even gonna notice.
Nice outfit.
Hey, Kevin. It's a costume.
So you can just cool it, okay?
Carole? Carole...
I'll have one
of those as well.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Now these are limes,
lemons, onions...
I'm a vegetarian.
What can I eat?
It's all vegetarian.
I'll just have some bread.
You used your hands.
Oh, yuck, oh...
What, is it too spicy?
No.
These s'mores are disgusting.
They're not s'mores,
they're samosas.
Do you think
they have any s'mores?
All they are is chocolate,
graham cracker and marshmallow.
How difficult
would that have been?
So, you're
Kelly's sisters, huh?
What?
Rupa, Neepa, Tiffany,
stop acting like such little
losers and just be cool!
Come on, Ryan. Come on.
Leave him alone! I hate you guys.
They said something
about Zach Braff...
Don't even listen to them...
No, you know...
Very official.
I decided to come.
I feel a little underdressed,
but at least I'm not dressed
like a slutty cheerleader, right?
Is that mean?
Temp! Temp!
I don't even want
to hear it, okay?
Stop it.
Stop it right now.
I didn't come to Diwali
to get yelled at.
Ryan is a temporary worker.
Makes no money.
Vali is a whole doctor, so
handsome. Makes good money...
Do you think
I want to date a doctor?
...and he's a perfect match.
Hey, Big Tuna, you ready?
Yep.
One, two, three, shot!
Oh, holy mother of God...
Oh, that burns!
Golly...
That's good...
Wow! Thirty years.
And you two only met once
before the wedding night?
Yes.
Wow.
How long have you been married
to the cheerleader?
She's not a cheerleader! She
thought this was a costume party.
No, we're not married
yet.
She is very fair.
Very fair and very kind.
So, tell me, is your marriage
the kind of thing
where when you die, she
has to throw herself on a fire?
No, okay.
It's still very cool.
Okay, thanks.
One, two, three, shot!
Are you okay?
I'm gonna be.
Hi. I'm just gonna...
Just for a sec. Just a sec.
Everyone? I'm sorry. Could I
have your attention, please?
Thank you. Hi. Sorry, I just
have an announcement to make.
Okay. I have learned a lot
about Indian culture tonight,
but I have learned
even more about love.
And I know
you're all thinking,
"Who is this crazy gringo
and what is he talking about?”
Well, I'm not crazy.
Maybe I'm crazy in love.
So, without further ado,
Carole...
Carol Stills,
I would like you to do me the
honor of making me your husband.
Oh, Michael...
What do you say?
Can we talk about this
in private?
I didn't hear you?
Can we talk about this
in private?
Oh, you gotta be kidding.
Okay.
No, I get it. I get it.
You're not ready. We'll wait.
This is our ninth date,
Michael.
Well, yeah. But I...
I feel like I've known you
many lifetimes.
Maybe I'm Hindu after all.
Okay, I'm not Hindu, but...
Carole, Carole, I just... I feel
like... I just like you so much.
I'd better go. Okay? You
can find a way home, all right?
Yes.
Okay.
Okay. Good night.
Good night.
Hey, you know what?
Why don't I come with you?
"Cause I've got this book
called the Kama Sutra...
Okay, good night, Michael.
All right.
Good night.
Well, I was a temp,
but I got promoted.
So the compensation
is a lot more competitive.
So you're saving money now...
Yes...
...to start a family and home?
Oh, or travel?
And buy an Xbox.
Is there anything you wanted
to ask us tonight?
Can you believe that my boss
proposed to his girlfriend in public?
That is so Michael.
Is it?
He's really outgoing, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, would you excuse me
for a second?
It's hot in there.
How's the naan?
Dry.
You look like
you were having fun.
I am. You should come
dance with us.
I have to watch our shoes
so they don't get stolen.
Who were you texting?
No one.
I went to
the doctor I went to the mountains
I looked to the children...
Andy, no a cappella.
I looked to the
children I drank from the fountain
There's more than one answer
to these questions
Pointing me in
a crooked line...
Wait.
The less I seek my source
Oh, come on, guys, please.
The closer I am to fine
That's not good.
Tuna! Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God.
Wow. That's so spicy.
Here.
Yeah.
You're waiting for a call?
No.
Wow.
Pam, when Carole said,
"No," tonight,
I think I finally realized
how you must be feeling.
We're both the victims
of broken engagements.
Well, you were
never really engaged.
I was in that
marriage arena, though.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
I kind of thought something
would happen tonight, too.
So alike.
What are you doing?
I'm rejecting your kiss.
I... What? I didn't...
Can I have a ride home?
If you sit in the back.
Night, guys.
Hey, can I have a ride, man?
I have my bike.
No way, dude.
I am not driving home.
I brought an inflatable bed
for just such occasions.
You're welcome to share it,
though. It's a roomy twin.
I'm good.
Hey, dummy, get in the car.
I'm a drunk driver.
Yes, you are.
Here, let me take that thing.
Just get in the car.
Okay.
You can really hold
your liquor, though, really.
Yeah. You can't.
Okay.
And I am just going to lie down
in the back, if that's all right?
Sure.
Here's your bag.
Just don't puke on anything.
You okay?
So good.
Good.
These are not my shoes.
This is just like that show
Taxicab Confessions...
If you say one more word,
I'm stopping the car.
Sorry.
This is going out to
Indians everywhere.
It's a tribute to one of the
greats, Mr. Adam Sandler.
Diwali is a festival of lights
Let me tell you something
Tonight has been
one crazy night
So put on your saris
It's time to celebrate Diwali
Everybody looks so jolly
but it's not Christmas,
it's Diwali
The goddess of destruction,
Kali
stopped by to celebrate Diwali
Don't invite any zombies
lo a celebration of Diwali
Along Came Polly
to have some fun at Diwali
If you're Indian
and you love to party
have a happy, happy, happy
happy Diwali!
Happy Diwali!