Hey.
Oh, what's this?
That is a demerit.
"Jim Halpert. Tardiness."
Oh. I love it, already.
You've got to learn, Jim.
You are a second in command,
but that does not
put you above the law.
Oh, I understand.
And I also have
lots of questions.
Like,
what does a demerit mean?
Let's put it this way. You do
not want to receive three of those.
Lay it on me.
Three demerits, and
you'll receive a citation.
Now, that sounds serious.
Oh, it is serious.
Five citations, and you're
looking at a violation.
Four of those, and you'll
receive a verbal warning.
Keep it up, and you're
looking at a written warning.
Two of those, that will
land you in a world of hurt,
in the form of
a disciplinary review,
written up by me, and placed on
the desk of my immediate superior.
Which would be me.
That is correct.
Okay. I want a copy on my
desk by the end of the day
or you will receive
a full desaggelation.
What's a... What's that?
Oh, you don't want to know.
Hey, Phyllis.
Are you all right?
I think I just got flashed.
What? Really?
In the parking lot.
Oh, my God.
Move!
Okay,
I'll call the real police.
What happened?
What can I do to help?
Okay.
I'll check the web.
Thank you.
The police are on it.
They say they've
already had three calls.
Can you tell us
what happened?
I was walking to the building and
this man asked me for directions.
And he was holding a map.
And when I walked over,
he had it out on the map.
Phyllis.
You're a married woman.
The guy was just hanging
brain. I mean, what's all the fuss?
If that's flashing,
then lock me up.
It's just, like, so creepy.
Yeah.
What's happening?
Oh, some guy exposed himself
to Phyllis in the parking lot.
Really? Is she okay?
Yeah. Bob Vance took
her for a walk to calm down.
Okay.
Phyllis, you say?
What is so funny?
I mean,
did he even see Pam?
Or, Karen from behind?
I'm guessing not.
I'm sorry.
It's pretty funny
when you think about it.
Not really. No.
It's disgusting and demeaning.
Oh, okay.
Masters of comedy,
a guy dropped his pants.
Have you ever
been to the circus?
Okay.
He's back!
Hey, what's going on?
There's a police car in the...
What?
What's going on?
Oh, Phyllis got flashed.
It's...
I don't think laughing about
it is an appropriate response.
Oh, come on.
We're laughing at Phyllis
but she's not even here.
So, no harm, no foul.
I don't think
the women in this office...
Incidentally, where were
you during all of this?
Maybe you're the flasher.
I was at a parent-teacher
conference.
Prove it.
Let's see your penis.
I... You know...
As that was coming out of my
mouth, I knew that it was wrong.
In all the excitement,
I forgot that my primary
goal is to keep people safe.
Women can't have fun
if they don't feel safe.
For example, Jan and I have a
safe word in case things go too far.
Foliage.
And if one of us says that
word, the other one has to stop.
Although last time, she
pretended she didn't hear me.
Michael, come over
after work tonight, okay?
I miss your body.
I don't know.
I feel... I drive a lot.
I'm spending a fortune
on gas and tools.
Okay. I'll give you $200. And if I get up
before you, I'll leave it on the dresser.
That... I don't know.
That makes me
kind of uncomfortable.
$3007?
Well... I don't know.
Look, whatever.
Just let my assistant know
if you're coming over
So he can get more vodka.
Okay?
- Hunter, are you on?
- You got it, Jan.
The employees of this
office are very small and delicate.
Deserve protection
from local pervs.
Better a thousand
innocent men are locked up
than one guilty man
roam free.
I am sick over this thing. Those
people out there are clearly afraid.
And that can't happen.
Not in my house.
Agreed. Let me show you
what I've been working on.
There are
several penises there
I'd love Phyllis
to run her eyes over.
You know, see if we
can catch this pervert.
This is the last thing that Phyllis
needs to see right now, Dwight.
Look at that one.
Dwight,
are those your pants?
That's a Polaroid.
Attention, everybody. Dwight
has something he would like to say.
Due to a recent
incident involving
Phyllis, a man,
a map, and his penis,
I think you know
what I'm referring to,
Michael has authorized me to form
an emergency anti-flashing task force.
Question. Won't that interfere
with your other task forces?
Answer. No, because this
is being given priority one.
This is a petition
for the business park
to upgrade their
security cameras
as well as install two
floodlights in the parking lot.
And I know what
you're thinking.
Won't that just shed
more light on the penises?
But that is
a risk we have to take.
Pam. You can draw, kind of.
Why don't you work
with Phallus
on drawing
a picture of the exposer
that I can post
around the community?
Phallus?
Phyllis. Sorry.
I've got penises on the
brain. Back to work, everybody.
I don't often miss Roy,
but I can tell you one thing.
I wish someone had flashed me
when I was with Roy.
Because that would have been
the ass-kicking of the year.
Especially if it had been Jim.
He would not have wanted me
to have seen Jim's...
I'm...
I am saying a lot of things.
I didn't really
get a good look.
That's okay.
I don't feel like
answering phones.
Hey, did you guys see this
memo that Dwight sent out?
"Women will be sent home
if they wear makeup
"or heels exceeding
one-quarter inch.
"Females are not allowed
to speak to strangers
"unless given written
authorization by Dwight Schrute."
This is ridiculous.
Attention. I am removing
all bananas from the kitchen.
Dwight, this memo that
you distributed is insulting.
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
"Sleeves down to the wrists"?
"Button-up collars
and muted colors."
Nobody dresses like that.
Okay.
You know something, Dwight?
We are not the terrorists.
Why don't you just take these
women, put them in a burlap sack,
and hit them with a stick?
Because that's
what you're doing.
I celebrate these women.
They deserve the right
to dress as they please.
If Pam wants to show more
cleavage, she should be able to.
I encourage that.
Look, it's really simple.
We just want you guys
to treat us with respect.
See? That's what we're talking
about. Did you hear that, Dwight?
Yes.
Did you hear that, Michael?
No, Dwight. Respect.
R-E-S-P-C-T.
Find out what it means to me.
All right.
You know what? That's it.
Conference room. Five minutes.
Women's appreciation.
Wait a second. How are
you qualified for that?
Oh, I don't know, James.
Did I come from a woman?
Have I slept with a woman?
More than one?
Less than three.
That is not current.
You know what? Why
doesn't Oscar run the meeting?
He's a homosexual.
Why don't you run the
meeting? You play with dolls.
Those are
collectible action figures.
And they're worth
more than your car.
You know what? I am
the expert. I will conduct it.
I know the crap out of women.
I would like to apologize
for all the men who thought
this was a laughing matter.
Are we still
discussing this?
I say again,
what is the big deal?
Nobody likes to be flashed.
When Meredith flashed me
at that Christmas party,
I nearly vomited.
I don't remember doing that.
What a surprise.
Okay. No catfights.
Please? Let's...
My point is...
A penis, when seen
in the right context,
is the most
wonderful sight for a woman.
But in the wrong context,
it is like a monster movie.
Alien.
What? Shut it. Shut up.
Okay. So, what I want to engage
us in today is a hardcore discussion
about women's problems
and issues and situations.
Magazines and TV
shows and movies
portray women
as skinny, tall goddesses.
Well, look around.
Are women like that?
No. No, they are not.
Even the hot ones
aren't really that skinny.
So, what does that say?
That says that you
women are up against it.
And it is criminal.
Society doesn't care.
Society sucks.
I don't even consider myself
a part of society.
F.Y.I. because I am so
angry over all of this.
If it were up to me, you ladies
would be the fashion models.
Yes, Andy.
Then, the fashion models could
come here and work with me.
What you're saying
is extremely misogynistic.
Yes.
Thank you.
That was not necessary, but I
appreciated it. And it proves my point.
Women can do anything.
I'm saying that
you're being sexist.
No. I'm being misogynistic.
That is insane.
I am not being sexist.
That's the same thing.
Michael.
Yes.
When I got
my hair cut short,
you asked me
if I was a lesbian.
Because...
That was one
possible explanation
as to why
you got that haircut.
And when we get mad, you
always ask us if we're on our periods.
I have to know whether
you're serious or not.
I wish I could menstruate.
If I could menstruate,
I wouldn't have to deal
with idiotic calendars
anymore.
I'd just be able to count
down from my previous cycle.
Plus, I'd be more in tune
with the moon and the tides.
Can we just get back to work?
Yes. Okay. Yes.
This is not work talk.
You're right. You're right.
And you know why?
It's because of where we are.
This is
a masculine environment.
We need to find a place
where you feel comfortable.
You know where
we're gonna go?
Steamtown Mall.
Frankly,
it's kind of insulting.
But I have a bunch of stuff
I need to return in my car,
so I can do that.
Malls are just
awful and humiliating.
They're just
store after store
of these
horrible sales people
making a big fuss out of an
adult shopping in a junior section.
There are petite adults
who are sort of smaller
who need to wear,
maybe, a kids' size 10.
Okay! Let's go,
ladies of Dunder Mifflin.
Hey, we should have
a calendar printed up.
Pam, put that in
my good idea folder.
Let's go!
Are you finished
with the sketch?
Yeah.
Doesn't seem like the type.
Phyllis got a good look.
I plan on plastering this
pervert's face everywhere.
You can run,
but you cannot hide.
Meredith, slow down!
We're not gonna get there
any faster if we're dead.
Thanks. I know how to drive.
Oh. Yeah.
You really shouldn't litter.
My car. My rules.
Hey, Jim.
You want to go in
the women's bathroom??
No. Thank you, though.
You aren't curious?
Not really.
I've seen a bathroom before.
Yeah, but,
it's every guy's fantasy.
I think you mean
a girl's locker room.
And in the fantasy,
there's usually girls in it.
Yeah.
I'm going in.
Go crazy.
Oh, my God.
I really appreciate
your letting me work
alongside you
so closely today.
Of course you do, moonface.
That's because you're a preppy
freak, you're the office pariah,
and nobody likes you.
So, start hanging these
all around the building.
This guy looks
like a real deviant.
No duh.
That's why we've got to
catch him. Start hanging those.
Aye, aye, Captain.
More like, aye, aye, General.
I don't think
she's gonna make it.
Don't think
she's gonna make it!
It's a little too tight.
I'm gonna find another spot.
Many women are
competent drivers.
Okay. Come on.
This is what we know.
Well, I stand corrected.
This is pretty cool.
Yes.
Hey, where did you decide
to take Karen tonight?
Anna Maria's.
What's the occasion?
Six-month anniversary.
What?
Nothing. I think,
we all kind of thought
you guys were just,
like, hooking up.
No. We've been
dating for six months.
She might mention an e-mail
that I wrote a while back.
Oh, right.
I remember that one.
She read it to me.
She said
she's not really ready
to date somebody
in the office,
but she really
likes you as a friend.
I figured. That's cool.
I wouldn't want to be in an
office relationship, anyway.
All right.
I hope nobody's on a diet.
Thanks, Michael.
Thank you, Michael.
You're welcome.
Okay.
So. Let's dish.
What do you
want to dish about?
Anything you guys want.
This is your time.
What is a Pap smear?
Or is it shmear
like cream cheese?
Okay. New topic.
Kelly, how are
things with Ryan?
Awesome.
Awful, I mean.
But, sometimes awesome.
What... What do you
think of role-play?
It can be fun.
Yeah?
Well, Jan has this
schoolgirl fantasy.
That's a pretty common one.
I just...
I feel uncomfortable
wearing the dress.
Okay. I'm gonna be
at the doll store.
Sometimes the clothes at
GapKids are just too flashy.
So, I am forced to go to
the American Girl store
and order clothes for
large colonial dolls.
Michael,
you shouldn't do anything
that you're
uncomfortable with.
Jan says anything that doesn't
scare us is not worth doing.
I don't know. Maybe we're different
people. I like cuddling and spooning
and she likes
videotaping us during sex.
Oh, my God.
And then, watching it back right
afterward to improve my form.
That is not healthy behavior.
No. It's not that bad.
The worst part is
that she shows it
to her therapist
and they discuss it.
Michael, you need
to get out of this.
No.
She's just fooling around.
It's a woman thing.
No. Normal women
don't do stuff like that.
This is bad.
No.
No, that's all right.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
You guys,
what am I gonna do about Jan?
Done.
Read the pros first.
Okay.
"Jan is smart, successful.
"Good clothes. Hot.
"Perfect skin. Nice butt."
She does have
very nice clothes.
Okay, okay. Cons?
Cons.
"Wears too much makeup.
"Breasts not anything
to write home about.
"Insecure about body.
“I'm unhappy
when I'm with her.
"Flat-chested."
What was the last one?
She's totally flat.
Shrunken chesticles.
No. The one before that.
“I'm unhappy
when I'm with her."
Michael.
You shouldn't be with someone
who doesn't make you happy.
I'm happy sometimes.
When we scrapbook.
Or right towards
the end of having sex.
Look, most relationships
have their rough patches.
You just have to push
through it sometimes.
Yeah. That's smart.
Maybe.
But it sounds like you're
just wrong for each other.
That sounds good, too.
I don't know who's right.
I just don't.
I don't know. I don't know.
I bet you know.
Don't think. Just answer.
What do you want
to do about Jan?
I want to break up
with Jan.
Wow!
I want to break up with Jan.
My mom taught me that.
Wow!
I cannot believe this
yogurt has no calories.
No one said
it has no calories.
Oh, hey, guys.
I want to do
something nice for you,
because you did something
so nice for me earlier.
I want you to go in there.
I want you to buy one item,
on me.
As a thank you.
Come on. Get in here.
Let's face it. Most guys are from
the Dark Ages. They're cavemen.
And they like a woman
to be showing her cleavage
and to be wearing
eight-inch heels.
And to be wearing
see-through underpants.
But for me,
a woman looks best when
she is just absolutely naked.
This is so great, huh?
We should do this
much more often.
I think we hang out
an appropriate amount of time.
What are you doing in here?
This is the woman's room.
You're in here.
I pay for that privilege.
Okay.
I'm a pretty normal guy.
I do one weird thing.
I like to goin the women's
room for number two.
I've been caught several
times, and I have paid dearly.
You don't want anything?
My treat.
Some panties, or...
Like, a thong or
G-string, T-back?
Get a nice bra.
Padded bra.
See-through? Push-up?
Lace? Thigh-high?
Bustier?
Anything. It's just...
You know what? I would love to
buy you a fresh set of underwear.
Phyllis?
What do you think? Too much?
Jim's gonna love it.
I'm kind of in between
boyfriends right now,
so I don't need
anything sexy.
But I do need
some new hand towels.
I figure I can
cut up this robe.
Slower.
Meredith. Slow it up.
Oh, no.
It's Jan. What do I do?
Answer it.
Don't answer it.
Okay. It stopped.
Oh, crap.
That is pretty cool.
Michael? You know how
to change a wheel, right?
Yeah. Yep.
Can somebody
grab me the lever?
And [ will...
Here. Meredith?
Why don't you put
your hazards on?
Yeah. Get your
hazards on for safety.
Let's see.
There we go!
Good. Yes. We have the...
All right.
I think I've got it.
Do you have a Crescent?
A Crescent-Allen?
I don't think we really
need that, Michael.
You know what?
I'm going to...
You take care of that.
I'm gonna do traffic detail.
You know?
I changed a tire today.
All by myself.
This bathrobe's
already coming in handy.
Coming!
Think we'll find him?
Yeah, I do.
Because justice never rests.
Halvsies?
No. Wholesies.
Listen, man.
I really appreciate
you letting me shadow you
today. I feel like I learned a lot.
Natch.
Yep. If you don't mind, I think
I'll hang up some of these posters
around my neighborhood,
schools, post office, et cetera.
You know?
I may have
underestimated you.
You're not a total ass.
Okay. I am really
going to do this.
Good luck, Michael.
You know what?
I need my girls with me.
Pam, Karen, even Phyllis.
Come on.
Let's do this.
Let's do it.
Okay. Remember. Be strong.
I love you guys.
No,
I'm getting her voicemail.
Don't leave a...
Hey, Jan. It's me. Michael.
I'm just calling to say that I
think we need a little break.
Permanently.
And, I know everybody says
this, but I want to remain friends.
Or, at least, business
associates who get along.
Oh. Just so you know,
it's not me. It's you.
Okay, buddy.
Somebody just walked in.
I have to go.
So, I'll talk to you later.
Michael. I was...
I was really unhappy with
our conversation earlier. And ...
I just... I couldn't
stop thinking about it,
so I decided that I
would drive down here
and apologize
to you in person.
So...
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
So, we're good?
Abso-fruitly.
Oh. Hold on. Sorry.
No.
Wait a second.
Oh. It's from you.
Want to grab some dinner?
Hey, Jan. It's me. Michael.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm just calling to say that I
think we need a little break.
Permanently.
And, I know
everybody says this,
but I want to remain friends.
Maybe some Italian.
Or, at least,
business associates...
Chinese?
...get along.
Oh. Just so you know,
it's not me. It's you.
Okay, buddy...
Any man who says he totally
understands women is a fool.
Because they are
un-understandable.
There's a wishing
fountain at the mall,
and I threw a coin in
for every woman in the world
and made a wish.
I wished for Jan
to get over me.
I wished for
Phyllis a plasma TV.
I wished for Pam
to gain courage.
I wished for Angela a heart
and for Kelly a brain.
Michael. How can you
appreciate women so much
but also dump one of them?
You mean,
how can I be so illogical
and flighty and unpredictable
and emotional?
Well, maybe I learned
something from women after all.
Dunder Mifflin Paper /
Sex Predator Hotline.
This is Dwight Schrute.
Hey, Dwight. It's Jim.
Jim, what are you doing?
I'm busy.
No. You're not.
I'm looking right at you.
I'm hanging up.
Don't.
I have information
about the sex predator.
You have information
about the sex predator?
I saw him two minutes ago.
Where?
In the women's bathroom,
above the sink.
Anti-flashing task force!
Above the sink.
Pam!