Oh, she's absolutely adorable.
He.
Oh, sorry. He's...
He's dressed all in pink.
That's his favorite color.
Oh, that's fun for him.
Fantastic.
Oh, wow, look at that.
How cute.
Thank you.
Oh, may I?
Oh, sure.
Hey, look at me! I'm a baby.
I'm one of those babies
from Look Who's Talking.
What am I thinking?
Look at all those staplers. What's a
stapler? I don't even know. I'm a baby.
Hey, Mom! I'm thirsty! I'm
thirsty, Mama! I want some milk!
And you know where
milk comes from? Breasts.
Hey.
Almost done?
Just about. Yeah.
Now.
Yes, I have started
lo see Karen.
It's very new and... Not really
ready to talk about it openly yet
just because I think,
once the word gets out there,
it might affect the way
people behave around us or...
I don't know. Just not yet.
Yeah, Jan,
it looks like a check,
a piece of paper of some
sort. Receipt. I don't know.
Jan, this is Angela Martin
from Accounting.
We have a rebate from the
Federal Work Opportunity Program
and no one knows
what that means.
We get that money
for hiring an ex-convict.
I didn't hire an ex-convict, unless
they mean Toby. Convicted rapist.
I'm just kidding.
When did the check come?
Last week.
Okay, that's when
the branches merged.
So Josh must have been taking
advantage of this program. Smart move.
One of the Stamford people
is a criminal?
Hey, Jan, speaking of Stamford,
Hannah brought in her baby.
Jan, which one of the new
employees is a criminal?
A reformed convict,
and I'm not sure
so hang on, let me e-mail
our H.R. Stay on the line.
Who is it?
Hannah?
Andy?
Martin?
Oh, you are such a racist.
Wait, why am I a racist?
Because you think he's black.
He is black, right, and...
He was the last one...
Stop it, stop it right...
Just stop it right now!
Okay, it's someone
named Martin Nash. Yeah!
Michael?
Why did the convict have to be a
black guy? It is such a stereotype.
I just wish that Josh had made
a more progressive choice,
like a white guy
who went to prison for
polluting a black guy's lake.
I wonder what he did.
In our society a black man can
be arrested for almost anything.
He was probably at a sporting event
and saw some people pushing each other
and he intervened.
Why would anyone
go to jail for that?
So what we need to do
is to forget
about this whole
Martin-in-prison thing.
People will draw unfair conclusions
about Martin and/or black people.
Cool.
Okay.
Angela?
Sure.
Let's protect the convicts
at the expense of the general
feeling of safety in the workplace.
As a 90-pound female
that sits in an ill-lit,
rarely-visited corner of the
office, naturally, I agree with that.
Good.
All right.
Jim Halpert.
I am so horny.
Okay, I can't help you
with that.
Oh, I think you can, Big Tuna.
Tell me about
that Indian chick, Kelly.
She seems pretty slutty,
good for a romp in the sack.
She is dating Ryan, I think.
Oh, and I care, why?
She's high-maintenance.
Next. How about...
Angela?
Blondes are more fun.
Come on, trust me on that.
Yeah, trust me.
That would be fun for no one.
Okay, fine.
Okay.
Pam, the receptionist.
Pam, should I go for it?
Absolutely, you should.
Jackpot.
Just try to be cool.
I am cool.
Okay. Are you cool, really?
I'm cool. I'm cool. I'm so cool.
Tell me what is going on.
Martin from Stamford
was at one time in prison.
No! Be cool, be cool!
I am greatly concerned about
having a convict in the office.
And I do not care if that convict
is white, black, Asian, German
or some kind of halfsy.
I do not like criminals.
Oh, God!
All righty, let's get started.
What is she into?
I know Pam pretty well.
I know the things that she
likes, and just as important,
I know the things
that she hates.
So one of the things
that she likes is pranks
and the things
that she hates...
Frisbee-based competitions.
Are you kidding? She...
I started the main Frisbee
Golf Club at Cornell
where I went to college.
I live to frolf.
Lead off with that.
Okay...
She loves hunting.
She also loves those ads
for Six Flags with the old guy.
Got it.
Also, do you speak pig Latin?
Hey, Martin. How's it going?
Good.
Getting settled.
Ah, good, good. Good.
Just a second.
Hey, everybody, may I
have your attention, please?
I realize that a lot of you have
already heard that Martin, here,
has had some trouble
with the law.
But I just want to declare
publicly that I trust him completely
and that anybody who doesn't is
an ignorant, dumb person, okay?
As a matter of fact, you
show me a white man you trust
and I will show you a black
man that I trust even more.
Pam, tell me
a white person you trust.
My dad.
Danny Glover.
Yeah.
Jonas Salk.
Who?
Justin Timberlake?
Oh, please. Colin Powell.
Hey, I've got one.
Yeah.
Jesus.
Apollo Creed.
Close your eyes. Picture a
convict. What's he wearing?
Nothing special. Baseball
cap on backward, baggy pants.
He says something ordinary
like, "Yo, that's shizzle."
Okay, now slowly open
your eyes again.
Who are you picturing?
A black man?
Wrong. That was a white woman.
Surprised? Well, shame on you.
So, you all wanna know
what I was in for?
No, that's not cool.
You don't have to tell them.
I really don't mind.
It was stupid mistake.
I was working in finance and I
got involved in some insider trading.
So, I spent a little time
in the clink.
That is awesome.
I had Martin explain to me three
times what he got arrested for because
it sounds an awful lot like
what I do here every day.
What was prison like?
Not terrible. Boring.
We do the same thing every day.
But at least we get outdoors time.
You got outdoors time?
Two hours, every day.
Sometimes we'd play
pick-up football games...
Michael, why don't
we get outdoors time?
Yeah, some days
I never go outside.
Well, we are
running a business.
What was your cell like?
Not good.
It's a little bit bigger
than Michael's office,
but, you know, I really
only slept there, you know?
During the day
our time's our own.
They had classes. I took
some watercolor classes.
They have art classes?
Yeah.
Did they have
business classes there?
They did, taught by some
Harvard Business School guys.
A lot of the guys also
that were in the class,
the inmates,
a lot of them have gone on
to do extraordinary things
in business. Terrible things...
It kinda sounds like prison's
better than Dunder Mifflin.
Well, that's not true.
I would so rather be
in prison.
- Yeah.
- Prison sounds great.
No, you would not.
This place is not prison. This
place... It's way better than prison.
Baby. Hello, baby.
Here, you want
to play with this?
You can't give
paper clips to a baby.
He could swallow them. It's
okay. I've got tons of them.
You like that?
Pam-a-lama-ding-dong.
Listen, you're cute.
There is no getting around it.
So, I don't know if you like
country music,
but I was thinking
maybe one of these days
we could drive out to a field,
crank up some tunes,
smoke a few Macanudos,
maybe even toss a disc around.
Ut-way
ooh-day ooh-yay ink-thay, am-Pay?
Wow. I...
Shh.
Think about it.
I'll hit you back.
Wow. That was... Wow.
Okay! Listen up, everybody!
You guys said that prison
was better than this place.
And I heard you
loud and clear.
So, I am instituting some changes
to make this more like prison.
We are going to start with an
hour of outdoor time. So let's go!
Michael, it's freezing out.
I can't feel my toes.
Why don't we pump some iron?
Anybody wanna pump up?
What is that, like,
five pounds?
It's two-and-a-half.
I'm not going for bulk,
I'm going for tone.
I'm going back inside. Yeah,
it is freaking cold out here.
Anybody wants to stay out, you've
got about 27 minutes of rec time.
Oh, hey, man.
Hey.
Did you have TV in the joint?
Yeah, in the rec room.
Like a 10-inch
black and white?
Actually, our TV
was bigger than that one.
These people
don't realize how lucky they are.
This office is the American dream
and they would rather be in the hole.
Oh, Andy.
I thought of one last tack
you could take with Pam.
Yeah? What? Quick question.
Do you play the guitar?
I play the banjo.
Hold on, let me think
about that. Yes, that'll work.
But can you sing in a
sexy, high falsetto voice?
You know I can, my man!
Yep, that's perfect.
Hey.
Maybe I'll get my banjo
out of my car. Perfect.
What is going on?
I'm messing with Andy.
I'm sending him to all the women in
the office with just terrible information
on how to get them
to go out with him.
I love it. I want in.
Who's the target?
Oh, you know what? It was
gonna be Pam... Perfect.
But...
But what do I do?
Just give me an assignment.
Oh, you know what, though?
I feel like I
already sicced him on Pam.
We'll give her a break.
Let's think of someone else.
All right, everybody, there has been a lot
of name-calling against our office today,
corporate maligning, slurring,
much of it coming from one of you,
who claims that prison
is better than here.
And none of us can say, "Boo," because
none of us have ever been to prison.
Well, there's somebody
I'd like you to meet.
Somebody else
who has been to prison,
who can tell you
what it is really like.
I'm Prison Mike!
You know
why they call me Prison Mike?
Do you really expect us to
believe you're somebody else?
Do you really expect me to not
push you up against the wall, biatch?
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Hey, pass...
All right. Yay, yay, yay, yay. That's
just the way we talk in the clink.
Been a lot of fun talk about prison
today, but I am here to scare you straight.
I am here
to scare you straight!
In prison you are
somebody's bitch.
Oh, and you. You, my friend,
would be the belle of the ball.
Don't drop the soap.
Michael, please.
Where did you learn
all of this? Internet.
So, not prison.
And prison. It's 50-50. Both.
Look, prison stinks, is what I'm
saying. It's not like you can go home
and recharge your batteries
and come back in the morning
and be with your friends,
having fun in the office.
What did you do, Prison Mike?
I stole and I robbed
and I kidnapped the President's
son and held him for ransom.
That is quite the rap sheet,
Prison Mike.
And I never got caught,
neither.
Well, you were
in prison, but...
Prison Mike, what was
the food like in prison?
Gruel sandwiches. Gruel
omelets. Nothing but gruel.
Plus, you can eat
your own hair.
Wow. Prison sounds horrible.
Yeah, yeah. Well,
thank you, Andy. Thanks.
Prison Mike,
what's the very, very
worst thing about prison?
Don't
encourage him, Dwight.
The worst thing
about prison was the Dementors.
They were flying all over
the place and they were scary
and then they'd come down and they'd
suck the soul out of your body and it hurt!
Dementors like
in Harry Potter?
No, not Harry Potter.
There are no movies in prison.
This is my point. You
guys got it soft and cushy.
This place is freaking awesome!
The people are awesome.
Your boss is nice.
Everybody seems to get along.
People are tolerant.
People who would jump to
conclusions can redeem themselves.
Nobody is nobody's bitch.
I hope that this scared you,
and from me, Prison Mike to you,
I just wanna thank you for listening to me
and letting me be a part of your life today.
"Cause you got a good life!
You got a good life, a good life.
So what do you think? It
doesn't sound so great, does it?
Wow. Thank you.
That must have been hard for
you to relive that. Both of you.
Yeah, that wasn't really
at all my experience.
There's certain elements
of what you performed
I've seen on television,
but it didn't remind me
of my time in prison.
Okay. Okay, fine.
You guys think prison
is so great. All right.
Well, here you go.
Okay, Michael,
come on, let us out.
No! If you think prison is so
wonderful, then enjoy prison.
Are we gonna...
They are such babies.
I am going
to leave them in there
until they can appreciate
what it's like to have freedom.
And if this doesn't bother
them, then I am out of ideas.
Hey,
let us out of here.
Hey! I have...
Shh.
This is Toby.
Hey, Pam.
Where're you calling from?
Michael, why is everyone
locked in the conference room?
They were very disrespectful
to me and to the office
and Martin has had
a bad influence.
To think that I gave him
the benefit of the doubt. It's...
Well, you're gonna have to
let them out, or I will, okay?
You know what, Toby? I am
teaching them a lesson, so...
You know they're teasing you.
I mean, obviously this is a much
nicer place than an actual prison.
We get paid to be here.
We go home afterwards
and have social lives.
And we have parties here.
They're teasing you
to be funny.
Okay, nutcases,
get out of there.
Good work. Long day. Really long.
Why don't you guys head home early.
Time off for good behavior!
Good job. Enjoy your freedoms.
Martin went from being
a new guy from Stamford
to the convict, to my friend,
back to a convict,
then to kind of a nuisance, actually,
if we could be completely honest,
and finally, to a quitter.
And I will not miss him.
And that is not because
he is black.
So we've
been told and some choose to believe it
But I know they're wrong
wait and see
'Cause one day we'll find it
The ainbow-ray anection-cay
The lovers,
the dreamers and me!