So, do you
want to see it or not?
I don't know. They're,
like, Friday night crowds...
Oh, my God.
You're, like, agoraphobic.
Agoraphobic?
Yeah.
Really.
You would rather sit on your
couch and watch a Phillies game
than go out to a movie
with your awesome girlfriend.
Absolutely correct.
Later, Jim.
Kev, have a good weekend.
Yeah, sure.
Bye.
Okay, so this is
what's gonna happen.
You're going to suck it up.
Here we go.
And we're gonna go to dinner.
Okay.
And then we're gonna go
to the movies. Sounds good.
Hey, Halpert.
Hey.
Roy! Roy!
God!
Pam, please call security.
Every day for eight years,
I have brought pepper
spray into this office
to protect myself
and my fellow employees.
And every day,
for eight years,
people have laughed at me.
Well, who's laughing now?
No need for consternation.
Everything is under control.
Michael, last Friday,
one of your employees
attacked another
employee in your office.
It was a crime
of passion, Jan.
Not a disgruntled employee.
Everyone here is
extremely gruntled.
Is Toby there?
No.
I'm here, Jan.
What is the situation, Toby?
Well,
we fired Roy, obviously.
And Jim won't press charges
against Roy or the company.
Thank God.
Yeah.
But now, apparently, Darryl
has some issue with this...
No, he has been wanting a
raise for a couple of months,
and he's just using
this Roy thing as leverage.
Well, are you gonna
take care of this?
Yeppers.
What did I tell
you about "yeppers"?
I don't remember.
I told you not to say it.
Do you remember that?
Yesh.
I really don't
want to talk about it.
I don't mean to be rude.
But I just, I don't want
to comment on what happened.
It sucked.
I guess all
things considered,
I was lucky
Dwight was there.
And Roy was lucky that
Dwight only used pepper spray,
and not the nunchakus
or the throwing stars.
Hey, man, I never got a chance
to thank you for stopping Roy.
Thank you.
"Thank you" not necessary
and thus not accepted.
I saw someone breaking
the law and I interceded.
Okay.
Got you something.
Don't want it.
You don't know what it is.
Don't want it, won't open it,
don't need it, won't take it.
Citizens do not accept prizes
for being citizens.
It was a little glass display
case for his bobblehead.
That would have made
his evening, I think.
He saves my life, I get
him a box for his desk toy.
Even-Steven.
No, don't call me a hero.
Do you know who
the real heroes are?
The guys who wake
up every morning
and go into
their normal jobs,
and get a distress call
from the Commissioner
and take off their glasses
and change into capes
and fly around fighting crime.
Those are the real heroes.
Angela, Roy's check.
He's coming in
later to pick it up.
Man, I cannot believe
I missed the fight.
It was crazy.
Man.
You saw it?
Describe it, please.
Well...
I heard some shouting, and I
look over and Roy's by reception,
and you could just tell
he's gonna punch somebody.
Jim says something, Roy stops
over there, all of a sudden, bam,
Roy goes down and Dwight's
standing there like an action hero.
Oh.
It was insane.
Well, good for Dwight.
Okay, I want you to be
Darryl and ask me for a raise
because I need to try out some
of these negotiation tactics on you.
Where'd you get that?
Wikipedia.
Wikipedia is
the best thing ever.
Anyone in the world can write
anything they want about any subject,
so you know you are getting
the best possible information.
Okay, Darryl,
ask me for a raise.
Hey, Mike, since Roy
left I've been doing
a lot more work
and I need a raise.
Well,
that's interesting, Darryl.
I think that
maybe you should...
Can't hear you.
What I'm saying is that...
Still nothing.
Okay. See what I did?
No.
By leaning back
and by whispering,
I established
a dominant physical position.
Nice.
Okay, let's try another one.
Okay.
Walking out of
the room unexpectedly.
And what happens in this one?
That's a surprise.
Okay.
Go ahead,
ask me for a raise.
Can I have a raise?
Sex. Steve Martin. Teri Hatcher.
What?
Well, what did you say?
I didn't say anything. I was
waiting to see what would happen.
No, it's...
It sounded interesting,
what you were gonna...
I saw the perpetrator advance
towards the victim at a high rate of speed.
His head was thrown back,
his shoulder and arm cocked,
indicating an attack position.
Perp grabbed the victim.
I removed my weapon
from its secure hiding place.
Which is where?
Irrelevant.
Discharged it at a distance
of a little over a meter
into the perpetrator's
eyes, nose and face area,
rendering him utterly
and completely disabled.
Then I contacted
the authorities.
The end.
Thanks, Dwight.
That is the bravest
thing I have ever heard.
I can't imagine
what I would have done.
I can.
You would have left
me to fend for myself.
Like the time we were
on the Ferris wheel,
and that kid dropped a milkshake
on me and you just laughed.
Well, that was funny.
That's why.
Oh, it was?
Okay, well, the next time that you
get scared that you think a murderer
is in your apartment
in the middle of the night,
and you call me
to calm you down...
Okay, you know what, I...
Could you stop? ...you
can just call somebody else
because I'm not going to
do it anymore, Ryan. I'm not.
Well, don't talk to me
about calling...
There's a bunch
of people back here.
I call you in the middle
of the night... Guys.
...to tell you
that I love you.
I don't think Michael intended to punish
me by putting Ryan back here with Kelly.
But if he did
intend that...
Wow.
Genius.
Yeah?
You ready for me?
Yes, yeah.
Absolutely. Have a seat.
You know what, actually, let's
go into the conference room.
Okay.
No, you know what,
let's stay here.
Let's go.
Yeah, let's go to
the conference room.
Tactic number six.
Change the location of the
meeting at the last second.
Totally throws them off.
Number 14,
declining to speak first.
Makes them feel
uncomfortable, puts you in control.
I am declining
to speak first.
Okay, I'll start.
It's pretty simple, really.
I think I deserve a raise.
I'm scheduled to
get one in six months,
but I'd like that
to be moved up to now.
Darryl, you are
a good worker and a good man.
I just...
You know, times are tight,
and I just don't
think corporate's
going to go for
this right now.
Are you wearing lady clothes?
What?
Those look like lady pants.
No. This is a power suit.
That there is
a woman's suit.
I do not buy
women's clothes.
Do not make
that mistake again.
I'm going to call Roy,
man.
Okay. All right.
This is going to
make him feel better.
This is too good.
All right.
You know what,
Pam, would you please
tell Darryl that this
is not a woman's suit?
Oh, my God.
That's a woman's suit.
You're wearing
a woman's suit?
I do...
I wear men's suits. Okay?
I got this out of a bin.
There were these
huge bins of clothes,
and everybody was riffling
through them like crazy.
And I grabbed one.
And it fit.
So I don't think that this is
totally just a woman's suit.
At the very least,
it's bisexual.
Who makes it?
It is mysterious, because the
buttons are on the wrong side.
That's the mystery.
Look, it's got shoulder pads.
And did you see that lining?
Okay.
Did you see that?
Would you stop it, please?
So none of that
tipped you off?
It's European, okay?
It's a European cut.
Michael, the pants
don't have any pockets.
No, they don't, see?
Italians don't wear pockets.
It's been a really
rough couple of days.
This helps a little.
Hey, maybe you want to
come over and raid my closet?
No, I don't want to do that
because I'm twice your size anyway.
Yeah, he look
like Hillary Clinton.
Let's just do this in 15.
Okay, can you stand
right there for one second?
I got to send
some e-mails.
Negotiations are
all about controlling things,
about being
in the driver's seat.
And you make one
tiny mistake, you're dead.
I made one tiny mistake.
I wore women's clothes.
So, Karen, how do you feel that
Roy tried to kick your boyfriend's ass
over another woman?
I feel great, Kevin.
Thank you.
You must have been scared
out of your mind.
Well, you know,
it happened so fast,
I didn't really
have time to be scared.
What happened, exactly?
I wasn't here. So I haven't
really heard the whole story.
Well, Jim and I were talking.
And Roy walked in,
looking super angry.
And he's a big dude,
you know?
And all of a sudden,
Jim pushed me out of the way
and Roy cocked his fist.
And then?
And then, bam, Dwight sprays
him and knocks him on his butt.
Goodness.
When I heard Jim
and Pam had kissed,
my reaction was to have lots of
long talks with Jim about our feelings.
Roy just attacked him.
I'm not sure which
one Jim hated more.
Let's get down
to business.
Why don't you tell me why
you think you deserve a raise.
Well, it's simple, Mike.
I mean, we merged
these two branches, right?
So now we're shipping twice
as many orders as we used to.
And with Roy gone,
we've got a smaller crew.
And I'm picking up
all of his slack,
so I think I should be
compensated fairly by getting a raise.
Well, those are
very good points.
What? I can't hear you.
Those are very
good points.
I can't...
What, Mike? Are you...
You make a very
compelling argument.
Sorry I almost
got you Killed.
Yeah.
That was nuts.
He could have broken your
nose or something. Crazy.
It's just so stupid. I mean, getting
back with Roy and everything.
I mean,
what I was thinking, right?
No, I mean, you guys really
seem to have a strong connection.
Not anymore.
It's completely over now.
We'll see.
I'm sure you guys will find your
way back to one another someday.
Jim.
I am really sorry.
Oh, yeah,
Don't worry about it.
I'm going to give
you a piece of paper.
I want you to write down
how much you want.
Then I want you to slide it
back across the desk to me.
Why can't I just tell you?
Because that is the way
these things are done in films.
Now slide it. Yes.
There you go.
Oh, come on. Be serious.
I am serious, Mike.
That's a 10-percent raise.
That's what I want.
I can't give you that.
I don't make this much.
Come on, be for real, Mike.
I don't.
I'll prove it to you.
There is a pay stub.
Are you serious?
You're earning this?
Plus perks. Yes.
Mike, this is barely
more than I make.
You've been here
ten years, dawg.
Fourteen years.
No, please, please don't.
I'm sorry, Mike. Some mofos
got to hear about this one.
Okay. Let's take 15 again.
A boss' salary
isn't just about money.
It is about perks. It...
For example, every year
I get a $100 gas card.
Can't put
a price tag on that.
Okay. If you don't want
a gift, at least let me
buy you a beer or
lunch or something.
When Han Solo returns to the
Death Star in the Millennium Falcon,
and shoots down the TIE
fighters and saves the Rebel cause,
do you think he does so
for a free beer?
Boy, I... "
And why are you so interested
in buying me something, Jim?
What's your angle?
It's like when he annoys me
and I want to screw with him
to get him back,
he never sees it coming.
But now I want
to be nice to him
and actually
give him something,
and he's like an eel.
I just can't grab onto him.
It's infuriating.
Maybe you just feel guilty
about all the pranks.
No.
Yes.
That's probably what it is.
So what do I do?
I don't know.
Maybe you should
go back out there
and sell paper so
we can go on a trip.
Michael?
Here's the $15 I owe you.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I heard you might need it,
SO...
Here's the $40 you gave me.
I didn't give you $40.
In a way, you did.
Yeah. I heard how
much Michael makes.
I still think
he's way overpaid.
Fourteen years.
Fourteen.
I know.
Okay, all right, I got to go.
Late.
Okay. Okay.
Here's the straight dope.
No tricks, no Wikipedia.
What?
I talked to corporate
and they told me that
I can only give you
a five-percent raise.
That's 'cause of you, Mike.
They're not going to give the
working man more than the boss.
Well, what am I
supposed to do?
Get your own raise.
You've got to get out
there and earn, son.
I'm not going to go out
and ask for a raise right now.
That is ridiculous.
Well, when they merged
the two branches together,
they put you in charge.
Okay? And we're shipping
more now than we ever have.
That's true.
Yeah, that's true.
You got to call
your girl and get paid.
Show her who wears the pants
in the relationship.
You know what, I should.
Yeah, you should.
I've been a loyal
employee for a long time.
Fourteen years long.
You know what,
I deserve a bump.
Make it happen, Captain.
I am making it happen,
Sergeant.
I remember it was very late
at night, like 11:00, 11:30.
Big fella comes in screaming
about God knows what.
I think maybe
Halpert had stolen his car,
something like that.
So the big fella pulls out
a sock filled with nickels.
Then Schrute grabs a can
of hairspray and a lighter...
You're useless.
Well, why don't we talk
next month after the quarter ends?
No, Jan.
I've never asked
for a raise in 14 years.
This is long overdue.
I want to do it today.
Today?
All right, well, if you want to do it
today, we should do it in person,
and can you
get here by 5:007?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll leave right away.
Great.
And listen, because of
our, you know, situation,
we're going to need to
have a third party present.
Yes. I'm bringing Darryl.
Darryl from the warehouse?
Mmm-hmm.
No, Michael, we...
We need an HR rep,
so I think you
should just bring Toby.
Hey, I'd rather kill myself.
Michael,
he's your branch's HR rep...
No, Toby is terrible.
...and we need
someone else in the room...
Toby is the worst
human being I've ever known.
...because of our
relationship. Michael!
Either Toby comes
with you or we don't do it.
Fine.
You are so mean.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Yes, you do,
Ryan Bailey Howard.
You called me stupid.
No. I said...
Toby, come on, let's go.
Where?
I'm going to smack you in the head
with a hammer. Come on, let's go.
What is so stupid about
wanting to name a baby Usher?
All right.
Usher Jennifer Hudson Kapour.
Don't you see
why that's insane?
Oh, so I'm crazy now?
Comfortable, Mike?
Yeah.
What about you, man,
you comfortable?
No.
Don't ever touch
a black man's radio.
Chris Tucker, Rush Hour.
I won't touch yours,
by the way.
Thank you.
I haven't been to
New York in a long time.
Big Apple.
Maybe I'll stay overnight.
I got a cousin
who lives down there.
How will we get home?
Oh, you can stay, too.
He's got a big place.
Maybe I'll stay.
It's not that big.
Buses, though,
will get you home quick.
And then all of a sudden Dwight
stood up and was like, "No!"
Then what did he do?
Well, you should just read
the report that Toby did.
He took everyone's stories.
Dunder Mifflin, customer
service. This is Kelly.
Oh, yeah, I can totally
help you with that.
Okay. Let me just
get the folder out.
Okay, it seems here that you
ordered 12,000 reams of paper.
Oh, 12 reams?
Hey, guys.
Jan is ready for you.
Okay.
Okay. Bring it home now.
And don't forget the new
black-man phrase I taught you.
Pippety poppety,
give me the zoppety.
Yes, sir.
Remember that.
I'll be right outside
if you need me.
All right.
Yeah. I taught
Mike some new phrases.
I want him to
get the raise.
I just can't help myself.
Hey, man...
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Can I, like, see you after
work for coffee or something?
I don't know.
Please.
I just got some stuff
I got to say to you.
Jim.
Roy. Look out!
Thanks, Kev.
I'm good, though.
Thank you, Hunter.
Hello. Come in.
Okay.
Who is the boy toy?
That's my new assistant.
Were you going to tell me that
you hired James Van Der Beek?
I have to call you the second
I get a new assistant now?
Be nice to get a memo.
We are lovers.
Hi, Jan.
Hi, Toby.
First...
First off, Michael,
this is a salary negotiation.
All matters regarding
our personal relationship
have to be set aside.
Are we clear?
Bippety, boppety.
Right now, we can offer you
a six-percent raise.
Six percent?
After all we've been through?
Oh, God.
I got you jade earrings.
Michael.
No.
No. No.
Michael.
You're going to
play it like this?
You give me a good raise
Or No more sex.
What are you writing,
perv-ball?
Just preparing
for the deposition.
This may the first time that a
male subordinate has attempted
to get a modest,
scheduled raise
by threatening to withhold
sex from a female superior.
It will be
a groundbreaking case
when it
inevitably goes to trial.
I'm so sorry, Pammy.
I mean, I wasn't going
to do anything, but then...
I kept thinking
about you two together.
I just thought you guys
were really good friends
or maybe he was
gay or something.
Not that that's wrong.
I'm sorry, too.
I just... I think that we both
made some bad choices.
So, you going to
start dating Halpert then?
No.
No. He has a girlfriend.
Oh, yeah.
Wait a minute, you broke
up our wedding for the guy.
No.
There were a lot of reasons.
What, you're not even
going to try to go out with him?
I don't get you, Pam.
I know.
What's this?
What's what?
"Certificate of Bravery from
the Scranton Police Department
"recognizing outstanding citizenship
from a very brave young man,
"Dwight K. Schrute."
Wow. I guess word got around.
That's a nice honor.
Please. They hand
these out to little kids.
Look, there's a teddy bear
in a policeman's cap.
Didn't think you'd notice.
Why don't you just take that
pen and stab me in the heart?
This is me, Jan.
This is me.
Okay.
Michael, please.
You know, why don't
we just take a break?
Okay.
This is...
This is going nowhere.
No. No. No.
You do not try
tactic number eight on me.
I invented
tactic number eight.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay, Toby,
how about if you...
Sure.
Great.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
Was a weird day.
I accidentally cross-dressed.
And then Darryl made me feel
bad for not making any money.
And then I had to ride
up here with stupid Toby.
And then your assistant
Is all young and hot and I...
Okay, Michael.
I can offer you
a 12-percent raise,
but you have
got to ask for 15.
That's ridiculous.
I'm never going to...
No, just...
I just need you to ask for it so I
can record that you asked for it.
Okay?
Ah so.
All right, Levinson,
here's the rub.
I would like
a 15-percent raise.
No, but we can offer you 12.
But you just said 15.
Negotiation is an art.
Back and forth.
Give and take.
And today, both Darryl
and I took something.
Higher salaries.
Win, win, win.
But, you know, life is
about more than just salary.
It's about perks.
Like having sex with Jan...
Michael.
So, you and Bob are looking
at a historical house?
Near the river.
How many bedrooms?
Four.
Dwight. Dwight.
I've been doing some
very interesting reading.
Really?
Tales of bravery.
Good stuff?
I was thinking tonight
we could read it together.
That sounds
fun.
I...
...will never say a word.
And now we are even.
I graduated
from anger management
the same way
I graduated from Cornell.
On time.
Now I'm back, got a second
chance and I'm not going to blow it.
So, look out,
Dunder Mifflin.
I mean "look out"
in a fun way.
You know, not like,
"I'm going to hurt you."
Hey, guys, guess who's back?
Oh, God!
No need to thank me.
I'm not a hero.
I'm a mere defender
of the office.
You know who's a real hero?
Hiro from Heroes.
That's a hero.
Also Bono.