Hello, Son.
If you're watching this,
that means I'm already dead.
Life is a... How do you
know it's gonna be a boy?
How... Would you stop
interrupting, please?
Yesterday,
I was scraping some gunk
off my wall sockets
with a metal fork
and I gave myself
the nastiest shock.
And when I came to,
I had an epiphery.
Life is precious.
And if I die,
I want my son
to know the dealio.
The dealio of life.
Here are some things
that I want to teach you
that your mother
won't be able to.
To jump-start a car,
first, pop the hood.
Then you take these bad boys and
clip them anywhere on the engine.
Then, you take these
and clip them wherever.
Number eight, learn how
to take off a woman's bra.
What...
We will demonstrate on Pam.
No.
And...
Come on.
You just twist your hand
until something breaks.
Ow!
Well, you get the picture.
Thanks, Pam.
And remember, no matter what,
I will always love you.
What if he's a murderer?
He's not gonna be a murderer.
Maybe that's how you die?
You know what, Dwight,
do you want to do this or no?
I wanna do this.
Okay.
From the top. Ready? Three...
Action.
Hello, everyone.
As you know, we are six days
away from Phyllis' wedding.
So get your suits to the dry
cleaners and get your hair did.
And Karen,
you might wanna invest
in a dress or
a skirt of some kind
if you don't
already have one.
This may be
Phyllis' only wedding ever.
It's my job to insure that none
of you look like ragamuffins.
So I am
instituting prima nocta.
Prima nocta, I believe,
from the movie Braveheart
and confirmed on Wikipedia,
is when the king
got to deflower
every new bride on
her wedding night.
So...
I'm sorry, I had a very
different understanding
as to what prima nocta meant.
I'm trying to get everyone
excited about Phyllis' wedding
because I want her to get
people excited about my wedding
when the time comes,
which won't be hard,
because it's
gonna be awesome.
A lot better than hers,
that's for sure.
It'll probably be on a boat.
What's up, spinsters?
Nothing.
You know,
this is a luncheon shower.
Girls only.
No problem.
The guys are having a little
shindig of their own
in {he warehouse
from 2:30103:15.
It is the only time
that Bob was available.
Sort of a guys' night out.
A G.N.O., if you will.
A gno.
Actually, it's more
of a guys' afternoon in.
A G.A.I. A gay.
Not... Not... It's
not gay. It's just a...
It's a bridal shower for guys.
A guy shower.
An hour-long
shower with guys.
I guess Jim and I
have had a little bit
of a rough patch for
the past couple weeks,
but we had some
really good talks
and, actually now, I think
that we're better than ever.
Karen and I had
a long talk last night
and the night before that
and every night for
the last five nights.
Something's up
with Jim and Karen.
Not that I've
been eavesdropping.
It's not really
any of my business.
But I've gotten pretty good at
reading the back of Jim's neck.
Halpert!
Tall, queer,
handsome as ever.
"Hey, everybody,
it's me, Jim."
Hello, hello.
Todd Packer.
Karen Filippelli,
Jim's girlfriend.
Shut up!
Shut it!
That's rude.
Either this chick is a dude
or Halpert got scared straight.
Yes! Yes!
There...
What happened? What?
Oh, God...
Quick! Somebody help!
Help the man!
No! No! No!
I can't believe
you're not gonna be there.
It's gonna be good.
It's gonna be a great
bachelor party, man.
I have a full day
of sales calls.
You should get out of them.
Oh, God.
It's the only time
he can do it.
2:30 to 3:15.
It's gonna be great.
We're going to be
doing some darts,
we're gonna be
grilling up some steaks.
Got some pie,
going to be very delicious.
And what kind of
stripper did you get?
I did not order a stripper.
What do you mean you
didn't order a stripper?
No...
You ever even been
to a bachelor party?
Not personally, no.
Mike, okay. A stripper
is Bachelor Party 101.
I... I...
If you don't get a stripper,
your party's gonna suck.
I can't get a stripper here.
Sexual harassment.
Get one for the girls, too.
That evens it out.
Like, you know,
separate but equal.
So that's what that means.
Okay, everybody,
a slight change of plans.
We are still going to
be having two parties,
but each is going to get a
little extra dose of naughty.
All right!
Okay.
What?
Okay, co-ed naked strippers
in this office, for realsies.
Under no circumstance
should a man
strip off his clothes
in this office.
Shut up, Angela!
Hey.
Hey!
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah. Why?
Well,
you seem a little tired.
Yeah, well, I guess there's
been a couple of late nights.
Karen and I have
been up talking.
You should get more sleep.
Yeah, I know I should.
Never underestimate the power
of a good night's sleep.
No, I'm sure you're right.
When I get eight hours
compared to like, six hours,
it's like, big difference.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
You've got to
get your REM cycle
going with the whole
sleeping better than not.
Good advice, Beesly.
Thanks.
See you out there?
Yeah.
Don't fall asleep
at your desk!
Oh, my God.
Okay. We are off.
Ryan and I are going
to go get some supplies
and I need you to handle
hiring the strippers.
Absolutely not.
I'm on it.
Well, get on it
and make it happen.
Ruddy cheeks, thick calves,
no tats, no moles.
No tats.
No, tats.
Of course, I want...
Stop. That's disgusting.
Leave me alone and get
the male stripper. Fine.
I knew you would, Nancy.
Sally.
No preference.
What do you think,
redhead or brunette?
Blonde.
Nice.
Do you have any blonde women?
He hasn't even
said a word yet.
Just giggling.
Got you. Got... Whoa!
Yes?
Are you okay?
I'm in...
I'm in the sex shop.
Got you.
Okay, so they
have Albert Einstein,
Ben Franklin or
SpongeBob SquarePants.
SquarePants?
Yep, SpongeBob SquarePants.
And you think
that'd be sexy?
Michael referred me to a male
strip club called Banana Slings.
Instead, I called the Scholastic
Speakers of Pennsylvania.
Hold the door, please!
Thank you.
Hello.
You wearing a thong?
What?
Sparkling cider is very good.
I think that's champagne.
Hello, ladies.
Who, here, is a history buff?
I-
Who's a fan of buff naked?
Without further ado,
the one, the only, the
sexy, Mr. Benjamin Franklin!
Thank you for that
introduction, Mr. Scott!
And good afternoon, fine
gentlewomen of Dunder Mifflin.
Half pants, right,
Mr. Franklin?
Knickers, in fact. Yes.
He's in his knickers.
Mr. Franklin,
I would say you are probably
one of the sexiest
presidents ever.
Well, actually,
I never was President.
Yes, but Ben Franklin was.
I'm here to teach you
a little bit about my life
and the era of
the Founding Fathers...
And when they came
over on the Mayflower.
Wait.
This is the entertainment?
Yeah, all right, so,
I want you to give him
your undivided attention.
And Mr. Franklin. If any
of these ladies misbehave,
I give you
permission to spank them,
especially that one.
Have you ever
seen a stripper before?
Yes.
Jennifer Garner
portrayed one on Alias.
It was one of
her many aliases.
Yeah, me neither.
Hi.
I'm Elizabeth. I'm the
dancer that was requested.
Okay.
I specifically
ordered a stripper.
I'm the stripper.
Oh, okay. Good.
Well, in the future, please
identify yourself as such.
Oh, God.
Okay.
"Is she hot?"
Text back, "Kind of."
It was a warm
June evening in 1752,
the night of my
fateful kite flight...
Mr. Franklin?
Yes.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I have a lovely wife,
Deborah.
But don't you also
have girlfriends in Paris?
Like, a lot of them?
Well, that is
a gray area of my life.
Okay? So it was
a warm June evening...
Look at that.
Nothing like grilling
in the great outdoors.
Is it the same grill
you grilled your foot on?
No.
Yes, but I got
all the foot off of it.
Oh, gross.
Okay, Ben Franklin.
Ben Franklin tied
a cherry stem in his mouth!
Well, that is because
I am a Renaissance man.
Ben Franklin? Do you wear
boxers, briefs or pantaloons?
Well, you're very saucy.
Guys! Beef,
it's what's for dinner.
Who wants some man meat?
I do! I want some man meat!
Michael, Dwight
would like your man meat.
Well, then,
my man meat he shall have.
There you go.
Deliciosity.
Of course.
Here we go.
So I guess, you have the Ben
Franklin wig and the costume
and you figure, "How can
I put this to practical use?"
Well, I'd like to
think that his dad
was a Ben Franklin
impersonator,
and he really
pressured him into it.
Hey, I wanted to talk to you.
I know this is
weird or whatever,
but Jim told me
about you guys.
What do you mean?
Well, that you kissed.
And we talked it through
and it's totally fine.
It's not a big deal,
it's just a kiss.
But you're not
still interested in him?
Oh, yeah.
Really?
Oh, no! I was
confused by your phrasing.
You should definitely
go out with Jim.
I mean,
you're going out with Jim.
I'm not going out with Jim.
You're dating him,
which is awesome,
because you guys
are great together.
Okay.
And I'm not into Jim.
Yeah.
So, well, good.
Sorry.
What are you sorry about?
What?
Nothing. I was just
thinking of something else.
Okay, the game is No-Limit
Deuce-To-Seven Lowball.
Blinds 25/50.
Nickels are worth 10,
dimes, 25, and quarters, 50.
Nothing wild.
I call shuffle! Here we go.
Michael...
Gentlemen,
the entertainment is here.
Everybody, I'd like to
introduce you to Elizabeth.
Hi, guys.
That's a nice outfit.
I hear there's
an important meeting here.
I'm not really
into strippers.
You know what I find sexy?
Pam's art.
She's an artist
and I appreciate that.
It's very moving
and sexy, the art.
Hit it!
So where's the groom?
Oh, he's right there.
There he is.
Absolutely not.
That's all you,
that's all you.
Okay! All right, I'll do it.
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's do this thing.
Yeah? What do I...
Just sit on down.
All right.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, here we go. All right!
Yes!
Not bad! Not bad!
You smell nice, like Tide.
What's that?
You smell like
Tide detergent.
Do you use Tide detergent?
I have a girlfriend, so...
I bet she'd be jealous!
Yeah, she probably...
Yeah, she would be.
You know what?
Okay. Excuse me.
This is sick, please.
Stop it, stop it.
Turn off the music,
because this is wrong.
This is wrong! This is wrong.
I have a girlfriend. I...
And you are engaged
and I'm sure you have a boyfriend
in prison or something, so...
Let's just clear out, okay?
Shame on you.
Go back to work!
Elizabeth,
I want you to sit here.
When the phone rings,
answer it.
You want me to answer phones
with my clothes on?
We hired you for three hours'
work, and we're gonna get it.
I love your poster.
Thank you.
You know,
I invented electricity.
I know.
Well, I'm sensing a little
electricity right here.
Didn't Ben Franklin
have syphilis?
Yes, but I don't.
My name is Gordon.
On one hand, I want to be honest
with Jan and tell her the truth.
On the other hand, I'm
afraid she's gonna dump me.
You know, Michael, I
fathered an illegitimate son.
Really?
But I kept all this
from my wife, Deborah.
These things only serve
to upset the women.
They are the gentler sex.
Wow.
Ben Franklin, you're
really kind of a sleazebag.
Stripper?
Could I ask you
a question about women?
Should I tell my girlfriend
that you danced up on me?
"Secrets, secrets are no fun.
"Secrets,
secrets hurt someone."
Wow.
Thank you.
Care for
a piece of chocolate?
Chocolate?
Where did you acquire it?
That is a delicacy
in the Amazon,
but it has not yet been
imported to the United States.
Who is the king of Austria?
Joseph II.
Who is the king of Prussia?
Friedrich Wilhelm III.
Who is the king of England?
Why, the tyrant,
King George, of course!
I don't care what Jim says.
That is not
the real Ben Franklin.
I am 99% sure.
Michael, I left
a meeting. What is so urgent?
Are you... Are you okay?
Not really.
Look, I don't know how
to say this, so I just will.
Okay.
I went to a bachelor party
and things got
a little out of hand.
When... When did...
When, last night?
No, today at work.
You went to
a bachelor party at work?
Yes, I kind of arranged it.
Well, I don't even think
the stripper was that hot.
Did you guys
think she was hot?
Kelly, don't do this.
Do what?
I just asked you a question.
You know
what you're doing.
Anyway, you know who was
totally flirting with Ben Franklin? Pam.
Really? Looks like
I hired the right guy.
I'm glad. Any real
potential there, Beesly?
Yeah, right.
God, I need a boyfriend.
You know, Ryan, I'm...
I'm totally
ready to be set up
with one of your
business school friends.
Whenever.
Okay.
Oh, my God, I would
get so fat if I worked here.
Yeah? I lose
my appetite all the time.
You could strip, you know.
Thanks.
So you don't want to
end our relationship?
I'm closer to firing you.
That is so sweet.
You are the best GD girlfriend
in the world. Do you know that?
I'll talk to you later.
You are. You are.
So you know who turned
out to be kind of a creep?
Ben Franklin.
And, Elizabeth, the stripper, gave
me great advice which rhymed.
It really makes you wonder how
Ben Franklin can become President,
but someone like
Elizabeth can't.
Are you near-sighted
or far-sighted?
Both. That's why I
invented the bifocals.