Oh, damn.
I lost another file.
Gonna have to reboot, again.
Hey, Dwight,
do you want an Altoid?
What do you think?
In school, we learned
about this scientist
who trained dogs to salivate
at the sound of a bell
by feeding them
whenever a bell rang.
So,
for the past couple weeks,
I've been conducting
a similar experiment.
Dwight, want an Altoid?
Okay.
Altoid?
Sure.
Mint, Dwight?
"Mint, Dwight?"
Yes.
What are you doing?
I...
What?
I don't know. I...
My mouth tastes
so bad all of a sudden.
Always the bridesmaids,
right, ladies?
Okay, for this next
one, everybody hop out.
Just Phyllis and Dad.
Actually, let's bring Mom
back in and the sisters
and you and you and you.
Great.
Phyllis is getting
married and I am in the wedding party.
She has asked me to push her
father's wheelchair down the aisle.
So, basically, I am
co-giving away the bride.
Since I pay her salary
it is like I'm paying for the
wedding, which I'm happy to do.
It's a big day for Phyllis,
but it's an even
bigger day for me.
Employer of the Bride.
Yes.
I put Michael in my wedding.
It was the only way
I could think to get
six weeks off
for my honeymoon.
No one else has ever
gotten six weeks before.
Phyllis ended up using the exact
same invitations as Roy and me.
So, it was kind of like being
invited to my own wedding.
And I was like, "Wait,
I thought I called that off?"
So, what's in the box?
A toaster.
You?
Unbelievable.
Hello, Angela.
Hi, Dwight.
You look as beautiful
as the Queen of England.
Thank you.
Don't linger. Break left.
Left.
The Schrutes
have their own traditions.
We usually marry
standing in our own graves.
It makes the funerals
very romantic,
but the weddings
are a bleak affair.
- Those flowers are nice.
- Yeah.
"P and R"?
Phyllis and Robert?
Oh, of course.
Also, Pam and Roy.
There she is.
I swear, Phyllis,
you are as beautiful
as the first day you started
work at Dunder Mifflin.
Thanks, Michael.
That's sweet.
Same as when you
said it outside.
How you doing?
Are you excited?
Yes, very.
Me, too.
If you need to vomit,
that is okay. I did.
Do you want to
talk about tonight?
No.
Because I know you're probably
worried about pleasing Bob.
A lot of pressure.
Phyllis,
did you break wind?
It's okay if you did,
it's a very natural reaction.
It's your wedding,
and you're nervous...
That wasn't me.
Okay.
I'm sure that Bob...
Wow, that is...
That is pungent.
I lost my train of thought.
Are you set on
that hairstyle?
I thought it was...
Michael, no... Here, let me.
I don't need your help.
Thank you, no.
Just cover up
that bald patch.
Michael, please.
I just need some time alone.
Okay. Okay.
You might be
surprised to learn that
I've only been to
one other wedding.
It's actually
a very cute story.
My mom was marrying Jeff, and
they asked me to be ring bearer.
And I was
understandably emotional
and somehow
my pants became wet.
I hate you!
A long story short, Jeff's
dog ended up as ring bearer.
And the irony is that,
after the ceremony
that dog peed on everything
and nobody said boo.
Why are all these
people here?
There's too many
people on this Earth.
We need a new plague.
Who are all these people?
You know what?
I bet a lot of them
are wedding crashers.
No way.
Did you ever see that movie?
Of course I saw it.
I saw Wedding Crashers
accidentally.
I bought
a ticket for Grizzly Man
and went into
the wrong theater.
After an hour, I figured I
was in the wrong theater,
but I kept waiting.
Because that's the
thing about bear attacks,
they come when
you least expect it.
You know, I just wish...
I wish I had
the investigative powers
to actually smoke some of
these guys out, you know?
Once again, Jim,
I will take care of this.
I will locate the wedding
crashers and report them to Phyllis.
That way I won't
have to get her a gift.
Hi, I'm Kevin.
Where did you find her?
At the gym.
Right.
The gym...
Could you scoot over?
You're on my dress.
I thought you're not supposed
to wear white to a wedding.
I know,
but there was an emergency.
I look really good
in white.
This strapping, young lad sitting
here is Phyllis' father, Elbert,
and he is quite
the ladies' man.
Aren't you, Elbert? Huh?
Ring bearer.
I could have done better.
I will do better.
I am going to be better.
I can't believe
I'm actually doing this.
Are you ready for this,
Elbert? I am.
Let's do it!
That's my dress.
It's...
This is...
Me walking
Phyllis down the aisle
was supposed to be
the highlight of the wedding.
And now,
the wedding has no highlight.
I can't believe I pushed that
guy's lazy ass around all day
until he was ready to
stand up and steal the show.
That's...
Well, I've got news for you,
Elbert, if that's your real name,
the show's not over.
And do you, Phyllis, take Bob
Vance, Vance Refrigeration,
to be your
lawfully wedded husband?
I do.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I present to you,
for the first time as a couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Bob Vance!
And do you, Bob, take Phyllis
to be your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
You may now kiss the bride.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for the first time as a couple,
Mr. and Mrs. Bob Vance!
That's what
I'm talking about!
Congratulations, Phyllis.
You look lovely.
Thank you.
Your dress is very white.
It's so white,
my eyes are burning.
Thanks, Angela.
Congratulations, Bob.
You're a good man.
But just know,
if you ever lay a finger
on Phyllis, I will kill you.
If you ever lay a finger
on Phyllis, I'll kill you.
Agreed. No fingers
will be laid on Phyllis.
Oh, decided to
sit down again, huh?
Great.
Bet you can hear me, too?
Best of luck, Phyllis.
Also, I'm gonna need to see
a copy of the guest manifest
as well as
photographs of the caterers.
I don't have that, Dwight.
Damn it, Phyllis!
Are you all right?
This must be
so awful for you.
What do you mean?
Well, this is supposed
to be your wedding.
Oh!
No, that's actually fine.
There's no way it's fine.
I'm sorry.
If I was you,
I would just, like,
freak out and
get really drunk
and then tell
someone I was pregnant.
Okay. That's a lot
of good ideas. Thanks.
Excuse me, sir, how do
you know the happy couple?
Who?
The bride and groom.
What are their names?
I don't... I'm not sure...
I get it. I get it.
Come on, freeloader.
Let's move it.
Come on. Come on.
Okay, okay.
Where are we going?
You've got to find yourself
another wedding to crash, my friend.
Phyllis? Are you
happy with everything?
What can I do to
make it more perfecter?
It's beautiful.
Why don't you find your seat
and enjoy the buffet.
I'm already on it.
The chicken?
Totally undercooked.
I sent it back.
It's fish.
I will take care of that.
I do. I know a fair amount
about fine food and drink.
This is a white.
No, this is not
our first wedding.
This is the third wedding
that Scrantonicity has played.
We also played our bassist's
wedding and our guitarist's wedding.
Attention, everyone.
Attention, please.
I'm supposed to ask
if anyone has seen Uncle Al.
He is old and has
brown eyes and dementia.
His family is very concerned.
It's a very
serious situation.
Roxanne
You don't have to
put on your red light
Those days are over...
Hey.
I know I don't normally
notice these kind of things,
but this wedding's
really nice.
I mean,
the flowers and stuff.
Phyllis has got
some great taste.
You're kidding me, right?
I know you probably aren't
gonna remember this, but,
those color roses,
I got you those
color roses for our prom.
Roy, I picked those flowers.
Phyllis just stole all of
my ideas for our wedding.
I guess I wasn't really too
involved in the planning.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Well, you think
it sucks for you?
I'm the one who actually
wanted to get married.
Phyllis,
you're a wonderful woman.
And you're
a hell of a bowler!
Cheers.
Cheers!
Thank you, Randy.
That was great. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Hi I'm Michael Scott.
And, for the next 40 minutes,
I am going to be
your tour guide through
the lives of Phyllis Lapin
and Bob Vance,
one of the great, seemingly
impossible, love stories of our time.
My name is Michael Scott.
Webster's
dictionary defines wedding
as "the fusing of two metals
with a hot torch.”
Well, you know something?
I think you guys
are two medals,
gold medals.
For those of you
who don't know me,
I'm Michael Scott,
Phyllis' boss.
To quote from
The Princess Bride,
"Marriage..."”
The most important part of
a speech is the opening line.
When time is not a factor, I like to
try out three or four different ones.
Phyllis and Bob, their
celebrity couple name would be
Flob.
You look at her, and she's
kind of matronly today,
but back in high school, I swear
her nickname was Easy Rider.
Now, as for Bob. Bob Vance...
Okay, that's enough. Thanks.
...is a guy...
Thanks, Michael.
Give me the mike.
He works...
Okay, hold on, hold on...
Look...
I didn't say anything when Phyllis's
dad upstaged me at the ceremony.
And I think you
owe me this, okay?
Give me the microphone.
No, I'm not going to.
Michael,
give me the microphone.
It's okay. You're out
of here. Okay, good.
Yeah, you're out of here.
You're...
I hate you!
A year has passed
since I wrote my note
Hey.
When are we gonna get to see some
of those famous Beesly dance moves?
I'm pacing myself.
Come on.
Get out there. Give the
people what they want.
No. I'm such a dorky dancer.
I know.
And it's very cute.
Hypothetically, if I thought
Pam was interested, then,
no,
it's totally hypothetical.
Come on.
I can't let you in, Michael.
Dwight, just... No. It's
Bob and Phyllis's orders.
Look, I just wanted to go in and
quietly sit, and have a piece of cake.
I'm not even gonna dance,
one song, maybe...
You are a real life wedding
crasher and I must bounce you.
I'm sorry,
it gives me no pleasure.
Okay.
You remember me
when the west wind moves
Upon the fields of barley
You'll forget
the sun in his jealous way
As we walk in fields of gold
So she took her love
For to gaze...
Even after you're gone
And I know that you love...
Hey!
They're playing
our song, huh?
Yeah, that's weird.
I thought they only
played The Police.
I know. I...
I gave them 20 bucks.
You wanna dance?
Dreams last so long
Even after you're gone
And I know
That you love me
And soon you will see
You were meant for me
And I was meant for you
Hey, you wanna
get out of here?
Here's a non-hypothetical,
I'm really happy
I'm with Karen.
Every little thing
she does is magic
Everything she do
just turns me on
Even though my
life before was tragic
Now I know my
love for her goes on
One, two, three!
Toby... Yeah!
I just want Phyllis
to have a great day.
Phyllis and you
will be great together.
We are great together.
We are a great team.
The Celtics
were a great team.
Yes. Yes, they were.
Robert Parish...
I should talk to her. I don't
want this to ruin her honeymoon.
Well, nobody ever helped me.
I had to do it myself.
Even the doctor didn't know.
Dude, keep it together.
I listened to you
for a half an hour
even though most of that
stuff went right over my head.
Hey!
Yeah!
Phyllis?
Phyllis, wait, please.
I'm sorry. I just...
I just wanted to make
this a day to remember.
You found Uncle All
Yeah, yeah.
He's kind of a weirdo.
Thank you, Michael.
You're... You're welcome.
They say that your
wedding day goes by in such a flash
that you're lucky if you even
get a piece of your own cake.
I say, that's crazy.
I say, "Let them eat cake."
Margaret Thatcher
said that about marriage.
Smart broad.
Be careful with the... No!
Oh, wow!
Phyllis. Phyllis, come on.
You look like a clown.
Here. Oh, get me. Get me!