I'm hungry.
Movie Monday!
The only cure I know for the
Monday blues is Varsity Blues.
Let's go! Let's go,
let's go, let's go!
Take a seat down there.
Second from the end.
All right.
Everybody here? Yes!
Popcorn, anyone?
Yes, please! Thank you.
Anyone else?
No.
Movie Monday
started with training videos.
But we went through those pretty
fast. Then we watched a medical video.
Since then, it's been half-hour
installments of various movies,
with the exception
of an episode of Entourage,
which Michael made us
watch six times.
Entourage.
Kevin? Would you like to do
the scenes from last week?
Yes.
Why him?
Don't whine. Get the windows.
Previously on Varsity Blues...
Okay, Billy Bob got a head
injury, but Coach made him play.
So then Lance, he gets sacked
and he's out for the year.
Hello?
Not everyone approves
of Movie Monday.
I won't say who.
I don't approve. I don't.
Hello?
Let's go after that title now.
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
Hi, Jan. Hope you
brought the Milk Duds.
How would a movie
increase productivity, Michael?
How on Earth would it do that?
People work faster after.
Magically?
No.
They have to, to make up for the
time they lost watching the movie.
No.
Do I need to hire
a babysitter for you, Michael?
Kitchen.
Some little 14-year old girl
whose job it is, is to limit...
Michael is going
to get us all fired.
You sat back and let him
play that dumb movie
and now Jan is peeved off and
we're all going to lose our jobs.
That's not going to happen.
You know she has it
out for him now!
That's not his fault!
He had to follow his heart.
Ever since Michael
dumped Jan for Carole,
Jan's been
bitching out on him.
Reject a woman, and she will never let it
go. One of the many defects of their kind.
Also weak arms.
Dwight, you should
be running this office.
Michael would never let me.
It's not up to Michael,
it's Jan's call.
Talk to her.
I could never do that.
Fine! Sit back and do nothing
and let us all get fired.
I know that patience and loyalty
are good and virtuous traits,
but sometimes I just think
you need to grow a pair.
At the Stamford branch, they all
play this World War II videogame
called Call of Duty.
And they're all
really into it.
I'm told that it started
as a teambuilding exercise.
Unfortunately,
I really suck at it.
We didn't play many videogames
in Scranton.
Instead, we'd do stuff like...
Pam and I would sometimes hum
the same high-pitched note
and try to get Dwight to make
an appointment with an ear doctor.
And Pam called it
Pretendonitis.
Hey, Kelly,
my stuff just got here.
Oh! Oh, my God!
Kelly really likes
to online shop.
So, I felt like I wanted
some new clothes.
I mean, I just...
I wanted to...
It's just, I felt like it was time
to maybe, just get new clothes.
Okay.
I love it!
Really? I don't know.
No, you haven't even
tried it on yet. Try it on.
Not at work. I'll try it on...
Fashion show.
Fashion show at lunch!
No...
Fashion show,
fashion show at lunch.
Fashion show! Fashion show!
Fashion show at lunch!
Why did you do that?
I'm just killing Germans
any way I can.
We're on the German team.
Shoot the British.
Wait, are we playing teams?
Yeah.
Hello?
Is this Jan?
Who is this?
This is Dwight Schrute.
I am calling about
an extremely sensitive matter.
You should talk to Michael
and he'll talk to me,
and that way we don't have to
speak to each other.
It's about Michael.
What about him?
I can't talk here.
It's too sensitive.
It's not about
a surprise party, is it?
No, but we should discuss that
another time.
Look, I'm already an hour outside of
Scranton, Dwight, I'm not coming back.
Pull over at Exit 40.
There is
a Liz Claiborne outlet.
I know you like that store. Go
inside and shop until I can meet you.
How do you know
I like that store?
Many of your blouses
are Claibornes.
How do you know that?
It's part of my job.
No, it's not.
It's officially not.
Noted.
I'm going to the dentist.
Okay.
I have to have
an emergency crown put in.
Yes.
It's a new dentist.
He's far. I might
be gone three hours.
Three hours? Wow! Have fun.
Did you get anything good?
Yeah.
New blouse? Halter-top?
Camisole? Teddy?
I could save the branch.
Really?
If you let me run it.
Okay.
Okay, I can run it?
What would you do differently?
Mostly get rid of waste,
which is half the people there.
And clean house.
Right here, it's all for me.
Thank you.
Dwight, you must feel strongly
to speak with me this way,
behind Michael's back, and turn
on so many of your co-workers.
The decision to turn
on Michael was difficult.
But once I did it,
I didn't look back.
And mostly I feel
that Michael would approve.
It's really what's best
for the branch.
And I could care less
about my co-workers.
So, here we are.
It's all on the table.
I want the branch.
And I await your decision.
Oh, by the way, there's a new
Ann Taylor outlet store near here.
I know you like
their earrings.
Where is it?
Michael!
Hi.
I had a very interesting conversation
with one of your employees.
Oh, that's nice.
No, it wasn't.
Dwight just told me that he thinks
he can run the branch better than you.
What?
You were at the dentist?
You can't have people
undermining you.
Get control of your
branch immediately. Okay.
What was Dwight thinking?
That he could turn Jan against me?
She's my ex-lover-ish.
Wow!
It's so sexy! You look so hot.
It's really something.
It's too much.
What?
I'm gonna return it.
No. You have to keep it today,
just see how you feel.
Hi.
You look nice.
Thanks.
Isn't that, like,
your third soda today?
Yeah, I think we can be a
big help to your company.
Okay, see you next week. Bye.
Again?
Scared?
Call of Duty.
Andy, Jim, can I see you in the
conference room for a minute?
Now?
Yes, now.
Put the game on hold,
everyone.
This is not working, okay? We
are getting slaughtered out there.
It's the new guy.
Oh, I'm sorry, I don't know
what we're talking about.
See what I mean?
We just need a strategy, okay?
We're gonna set up a trap
in the gunroom. All right?
Jim, are you using
the MP40 or the .44?
Sniper rifle?
Snipe...
What?
Jim! In Carentan? Are you
playing for the other team?
You don't snipe
in Carentan, okay?
It's saboteur! Saboteur!
Andy, it's not...
I'm gonna kill you for real.
This game, the game is over.
I'm really going to shoot you.
Hey, Dwight.
Do you want an M&M?
No, thanks. I'm stuffed.
No, seriously, you should have
an M&M, they're really good.
Okay.
Good, huh?
So good.
Hey, I thought you weren't supposed
to eat anything for a couple of hours
after you've had
a crown put in.
They have this new kind
of quick-drying bonding. So...
Sounds like a good dentist.
Oh, yeah.
What's his name?
Crentist.
Your dentist's name
is Crentist?
Yeah.
Sounds a lot like dentist.
Maybe that's why
he became a dentist.
Let me see your teeth.
Let me see them.
You should floss them.
I know.
Well, then.
I'm glad you're okay.
Business is like a jungle.
And I am like a tiger.
And Dwight is like a monkey that
stabs the tiger in the back with a stick.
Does the tiger
fire the monkey?
Does the tiger transfer the
monkey to another branch?
Pun.
There's no way of knowing what
goes on inside the tiger's head.
We don't have the technology.
Dwight, can I talk to you
for a second?
Wow. This is tough!
What?
What is it?
Well...
I just got off
the phone with Jan.
And...
She demoted me.
Yeah.
You know what the craziest part of
this is? She demoted me to your job.
And she said that you should be
expecting a call later from corporate,
and that...
I guess that means that you are going to be
acting manager of Dunder Mifflin, Scranton.
I can't believe this news.
That... Wow!
Yeah.
I told her I didn't know
whether you'd want to do it
because you've always
been so loyal to me.
You've been
my most trusted ally.
You said that?
Yup, I did. I did.
But I think you should do it.
Well, gosh, if you think
I should then I will.
Perfect. Well, we're settled.
All right.
Well, then you are now
Acting Manager
of Dunder Mifflin,
Scranton branch,
and I am
Assistant Regional Manager.
Assistant to
the Regional Manager.
Thank you, Michael, for
staying on, I really appreciate it.
Hey, hey. Oh...
I can't imagine
this place without you.
Can't you? That's so nice.
Well, I guess we should
go tell the troops.
Yeah, when I'm ready, Mike.
Okay, let's do it.
Hey, hi, hello, everybody.
I have some good news
and I have some bad news.
I am being replaced as
your leader by Dwight.
You're kidding.
You might think that I am
kidding, and I understand that.
Congratulations, Dwight.
Thank you, Angela.
But, why Dwight?
Because Dwight never lies.
How does that qualify him
to run a branch?
Because that's all it takes.
Okay, Dwight, would you like to say a
few words to everybody about loyalty?
Thank you, Michael.
I just want to say, to the few of you
who will remain under my employ,
that I intend to lead you
into the black with ferocity!
Michael? What will you do?
Oh, I'll be fine.
Do you have any savings?
No, no, I don't. But...
Michael, you might
lose your condo.
I won't. I won't.
I have this little old vacuum
cleaner that's broken.
If Dwight doesn't work out,
maybe that could be manager.
Maybe I'll quit.
It's really happening.
Yes.
We can make a difference here.
I will make a difference here.
You alone?
"Cause I thought
together we were...
Oh, please! Don't be naive.
But you can be
in charge of the women.
Look how cute he is.
And he's trying to shoot
with a smoke grenade.
I'm sorry, what are you
whispering about me?
No, nothing. Just
concentrate on turning around.
Yeah, I'm trying, I just...
Just tap "S" then "D."
Oh.
Any last words? No?
What?
Wow!
Psychopath.
What?
I'm just looking.
Please go back to your desk.
In a minute.
Well, I remember why
I dress the way I do at work.
But I'm gonna
keep the clothes.
I mean, it'll just be cool to have some
after-work clothes that aren't pajamas.
Well, I guess it's time that I turn
over the keys to the famous Sebring.
No, thank you.
It's a corporate lease,
Dwight, you've earned it.
No, thanks.
What?
Not my style.
But you said you liked it.
You've always admired it. And...
But that was before. I'm thinking
about getting something German,
something with
decent gas mileage.
Plus, that convertible is a
ridiculous choice for this climate.
Take it back.
No.
That's my car.
What did you...
That's my car!
Yes.
I know, Dwight, I know.
I know, I know.
You know what?
Jan called me
about your little meeting!
No.
I know what you did.
You... The Sebring's cool...
I made the whole thing up,
Dwight!
It's cool,
the Sebring's cool...
Oh, do you? Do you like it?
And has a cassette and a CD.
How dare you?
How dare you, Dwight?
Don't fire me.
Please, don't...
Give me one good reason why I
shouldn't fire you right here on the spot?
I have excellent
sales numbers!
Not good enough!
I'll do anything! Anything!
Please, I'll do your laundry
for a month!
For a year!
I have a laundry machine!
I'm sorry. Anything... I'll...
Please? Please?
I don't know if I can trust
you anymore. You can't.
You can't, but I promise
I'll never betray you again.
What can I do, Michael?
What can I do?
You can get up.
What?
Get up.
And you can hug it out, bitch.
"Hug it out, bitch."”
That is what men say to each
other after a fight. They hug it out.
And in doing so,
they just let it go.
And walk away,
and they're done.
Not a good idea to say that to a
woman, however, I have found.
Doesn't translate.
Yup, yup, we hugged it out.
But it turns out
I was still a little angry
and so I felt I needed to
punish him just a little bit more.
And I'm making him
do my laundry for a year.