It's kind of blurry.
That's better.
Question, what kind
of bear is best?
That's a ridiculous question.
False. Black bear.
Well, that's debatable.
There are basically
two schools of thought.
Fact, bears eat beets.
Bears, beets,
Battlestar Galactica.
Bears do not...
What is going on?
What are you doing?
Last week, I was in a drug
store and I saw these glasses.
Four dollars.
And it only cost me $7 to
recreate the rest of the ensemble
and that's a grand total of
$11.
You know what? Imitation is
the most sincere form of flattery.
So I thank you.
Identity theft is
not a joke, Jim!
Millions of families
suffer every year!
Michael!
Oh, that's funny. Michael!
Yes, I understand.
Can I transfer you
to customer relations?
Absolutely. I couldn't be
more sorry about this...
I know, I know. We're all
trying to get to the bottom of it.
Yes, I'm upset.
Don't I sound upset?
Okay.
It is disgusting.
I totally agree.
Well, we're going to be
recalling all of that paper.
We have a crisis.
Apparently, a disgruntled
employee at the paper mill
decided that it would be funny
to put an obscene watermark
on our 24-pound
cream letter stock.
Five-hundred boxes
has gone out
with the image of
a beloved cartoon duck
performing unspeakable acts
upon a certain cartoon mouse
that a lot of people like.
I've never been a fan.
Everybody in here, stat.
No time to lose.
Cri-man squa, F and C,
double-time.
"Cri-man squa"?
Crisis management squad.
"F and C, double-time"?
Front and center. Twice as
fast as you would normally go.
Any other questions?
One more.
Why are you talking like that?
To save time, Jim.
Actually, I think you could make
the argument that it wastes time.
Yeah,
she has a good point.
I mean, for example,
with the last thing you said,
by the time you explained
it... Okay, okay, okay...
...it actually took up more
time. You know what?
Forget it! Where is Creed?
Creed.
Here.
Quality assurance. Your job.
I really think you screwed
the pooch on this one, Creed.
Because of you, the entire
company is in jeopardy.
Every week, I'm supposed to take
four hours and do a quality spot-check
at the paper mill.
And of course the one year
I blow it off, this happens.
We have a lot of angry customers out there.
This puts us at threat level midnight.
Accounting, you are on
customer service duty today.
That's not really our job.
Midnight, Oscar!
Don't worry. Kelly will be
training you first.
Kelly's training us?
This day is bananas
B-A-N-A-N-A-S
B-A-N-A...
I don't have a headache.
I'm just preparing.
Jim. Big fire in your house.
Your client, Dunmore High School,
sent out their prom
invitations on this paper.
Went home to all the kids.
Yeah, I got a call in already.
No, no, no. Not good enough.
This is a keystone account.
I want you
in the school in person.
All right.
I want you to bring a partner.
I'll go.
No, sweet cheeks.
We need somebody
who's actually made a sale.
Andy, you go.
William Dolittle at
your service, a.k.a. Will Do.
Yeah, I'm definitely
going to go alone.
No! No! I need
two men on this!
That's what she said. No time!
But she did. No time! Guys!
Get on this! Dwight,
I want you to be in charge
of the press conference.
Yes! You are entering
the no-spin zone!
We're having a press
conference? No, Pam.
The press is just going to
find out by themselves.
Not.
Here's the thing,
when a company screws up,
best thing to do is
call a press conference.
Alert the media and then
you control the story.
Wait for them to find out,
and the story controls you.
That's what happened to O.J.
I have invited Barbara Allen,
one of our oldest clients,
to come in here and meet
with me for a personal apology.
The press wants a story?
I will give them a story.
Oh, did the press
ask for a story?
Here is your headline,
"Scranton Area Paper Company"
"Dunder Mifflin Apologizes
to Valued Client."
"Some Companies Still Know
How Business is Done."
Okay?
Battle stations, everybody!
Let's go! Go! Go, go, go, go, go!
Yes. Hello. Creed Bratton, quality
assurance, Dunder Mifflin, Scranton.
I was supposed to meet with one
of your floor managers last week
for a quality inspection,
and he or she wasn't there,
and I'm trying to
remember who it was.
Who wasn't there last week?
Debbie Brown.
And which day was that?
Wednesday the 11th. Perfect.
The only difference between
me and a homeless man is this job.
I will do whatever
it takes to survive.
Like I did when
I was a homeless man.
Look, I know the reason that
you guys became accountants
is because you're not good at
interacting with people. But guess what?
From now on,
you guys are no longer losers.
So give yourselves
a round of applause.
I wonder how many phone calls
you're missing
while you're teaching us
to answer calls.
I know, right? Probably a lot.
Can you just tell us what
we need to do SO we can go?
Okay, Angela,
I love your enthusiasm!
All you need to know how to do
is pick up the phone and say,
"Customer service, this is
Kelly." Except don't say, "Kelly."
Say your own name.
Or if you're bored,
you could just make up a name.
Like, one time,
I said I was Bridget Jones
and I talked
like this for the whole conversation.
Oh! Can I be Australian, mate?
Absolutely!
Hello, mate!
I
like ice cream. I need a boyfriend.
I like ice cream, too, mate!
Alligators. Dingo babies.
Beer me.
What's that?
Hand me that water.
I always say, "Beer me."
Gets a laugh
like a quarter of the time.
So how's what's her name?
You know her name.
Who? Karen? Yeah. She's
only one of my oldest friends.
How's the apartment hanging?
It's fine.
Nice.
Check out this sunshine, man.
Global warming, right?
Today was supposed
to be really cold I bet.
What about music?
You have any music?
Yeah, you should have said so.
Give me the
beat boys and free my soul
I want to get lost in your
rock and roll and drift away
Give me the beat boys
and free my little ol' soul
I was thinking more like
a CD or... A CD?
Your call, dude. My girlfriend
made me an awesome mix.
Beer me that disc.
Lord, beer me strength.
So, Tuna, when we get in there,
let's do a really good job, okay?
Did that really
need to be said?
Well, not everything
a guy says needs to be said.
Sometimes it's just about
the music of a conversation.
What the...
Why is my girlfriend here?
Oh, she that teacher
in the white?
No, she's a part-time
frozen yogurt chef.
Which one is she?
The one in the green hoodie.
Wow.
I wonder if she's like a
guidance counselor or something.
No. I don't think so.
She's, like,
probably a tutor... Nope.
She probably teaches...
No.
There's no...
Okay, press conference in 45.
Dwight, make sure this place looks nice.
On it.
Okay, Karen, Ryan,
Pam, center stage.
Pam, run a comb
through your hair.
First rule in roadside beet sales,
put the most attractive beets on top.
The ones that make you pull
the car over and go, "Wow.
"I need this beet right now."
Those are the money beets.
Hey. Look sharp. Hey. Hi.
Hello, Dwight Schrute.
And you must be
from the Washington Post.
Scranton Times.
Chad Lite,
Lighter Side of Life.
And breaking corporate news.
And obits.
Oh, dear God.
Okay.
Here are your credentials.
You've been granted level
three security clearance.
Don't get too excited. That's
out of 20. Right this way.
Regional Manager Michael Scott
will be addressing the client
in the pressroom shortly.
Have a seat.
Can I get you a beverage?
Yeah, I'd like a...
Great.
Oh.
Andy, you know what?
We don't have a lot of time,
so we should probably...
Jamie!
Andy... Oh...
What are you doing here?
Andy?
Are you a student here?
Oh, yeah.
You never told me
you were in high school!
This is weird.
I got to go to Spanish.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
I had no idea.
Well, that's not going
to hold up in court.
We didn't do
anything illegal.
Except knock over a mailbox
with her friends.
Sir... Yes, you have
a valid point...
Okay.
...and I'm sorry.
Yes.
No, I am so sorry.
Really? Dixon City?
- I have an aunt in Carbondale.
- Excuse me?
Well, I don't see
how that's our fault.
And I've already told you the official
position of Dunder Mifflin is apologetic,
so I don't know
what you want from me.
Okay, first, I just want to say
that you are doing so good.
Look, you have
So many good qualities,
that the one that you might
want to work on is apologizing.
When I went over Wednesday
for the spot-check,
I get a call from
Debbie Brown
saying she has an
emergency dentist appointment.
Emergency dentist appointment?
Now I'm told she told her
manager she had the flu.
I'm a trusting guy,
but I just wish Debbie Brown had
been there. We would've caught this.
Yes.
I'll be sure
someone returns your call.
I'm so sorry. Bye.
Hello, I'm looking
for Michael Scott.
Mrs. Allen is
our most important client.
Because every client
is our most important client.
Even though she's a pretty
unimportant client, really.
And so, with the eyes
of the nation upon us,
I would like to say
that Dunder Mifflin
truly regrets
this unfortunate incident.
And as a gesture
of gratitude
for your continued
loyalty, Mrs. Allen,
I would like to present you
with this novelty check
for six months of free paper or
25 reams, whichever comes first.
You look good in this.
So, let us consider
this matter ended.
Well, it isn't ended. I'm very
angry. I could have lost business.
I know.
I know you are angry
and we are truly, truly sorry.
I don't accept your apology.
The watermark was obscene
and horrifying.
Well, we are extremely sorry.
I don't accept.
I'll be with you in a moment.
All right.
Who was that guy she
was talking to at her locker?
Not important
because you're not dating her,
because it's a felony.
But who was that guy?
Probably another
high school student.
The issue with the watermark
IS very serious.
Absolutely.
We teach our students
that character counts.
And you should.
You don't teach it
well enough.
One of your students
is a bitch.
Know what? Andy is having
a real rough day today.
I want to take out an ad
in your yearbook.
Full page, two words.
"Good luck."
That's not what I had in mind.
- Ask where he's from.
- Absolutely.
Where are you from?
Ohio? That's nice.
So what do you want?
He's upset about
the watermark.
Okay, great. Now, just tell him
that it was an unfortunate error
and we are doing everything we
can do to fix it and that you're sorry.
It was an unfortunate error.
We're fixing it.
And you already got
your money back.
And you're sorry.
And the company has already apologized,
so you can take that apology or not.
I think he had Tourette's
or something!
We are going to do everything
humanly possible
to ensure that this
never happens again.
Well, it doesn't help.
Why?
Because it already
happened to me.
The watermark,
it's a one-time thing.
I don't care!
It was disgusting.
Cartoon characters
having sex?
May I point out that the sex
appeared to be consensual?
Both animals were smiling.
Okay.
I grew up on a farm.
I have seen animals having sex
in every position imaginable.
Goat on chicken.
Chicken on goat.
Couple of chickens doing a
goat. Couple of pigs watching.
Whoever drew this
got it exactly right.
What can I do for you?
All right. For starters, I
think that you should resign.
Okay. Well, wasn't
really my fault.
The guys at the paper mill...
You're the head... The guy at
the paper mill's... No, no, no.
You're the head of the company!
I'm the head of the company?
Yes, and that makes it
your responsibility...
No, I'm a regional manager!
...and so you should lose
your job! No... What? Okay.
This is insane.
You can get out of here.
Get out. That's insane.
Fine.
I will give this to somebody
who will appreciate it.
It's non-transferable.
Doesn't matter. Out please!
I'm calling the
Better Business Bureau!
Yeah, well I'm calling
the Ungrateful Biatch Hotline!
Did you get all that?
Everything.
We've gotta do something.
This is all spinning out of
control, Pam. This is just not...
It's just the
Scranton Times.
No, then Newsweek
picks it up
and then CNN does a story about it
and then YouTube gets a hold of it.
You know what?
I really think the whole thing
is just going to blow over
in like a week or two.
You're right.
It will blow over.
But it's not going to take
a week or two.
Do you know what this is for?
Yes.
Michael likes me to run the camera
when he makes his apology videos.
He says he needs
a woman's touch.
Okay, I think that's good.
Hello, I am Michael Scott, regional
manager of Dunder Mifflin, Scranton.
By now, you're probably sick
of hearing about Dunder Mifflin
and our embarrassing
watermark boner.
Let me tell you something.
Something from the heart.
I am not leaving this office.
It will take a SWAT team to remove me
from this office and maybe not even then.
You could never withstand
a SWAT team.
That's how devoted
I am to this job.
I'm just saying...
I know.
They would flank you,
throw in a concussion grenade.
I understand that, Dwight.
You'd be on the ground...
Do you think you're taking it
a little... ...blind, deaf, dumb.
...literally, Dwight?
If you wanted to be...
And now we're wasting tape.
I'm going to have to
cut this all out.
Can you say cut...
Cut.
...so I'll know where to...
Cut. I'm asking
Pam to do it, please.
Cut.
Okay. Ready?
Kevin, what's four plus seven?
Eleven.
Yeah, well, you didn't know that
when you filled out this payroll form.
Yeah? Well, at least I didn't
suck at customer relations.
Oh, yes! Facial.
Yes.
You two are apes.
I expect you to
apologize for that, Angela.
I'm sorry that
you're both morons!
Oh, but you still said,
“I'm sorry."
I called you morons.
Still said it.
Still said it, so...
Five, four, three...
There is no way I will resign.
It wouldn't be fair. Not to
the good workers I work with,
not to my clients,
and especially not to me.
Let's not forget who this whole
resigning business is about anyway.
If I could leave you with one
thought, remember, it wasn't me.
They're trying to make me
an escape goat.
If I am fired, I swear to God,
that every single piece of
copier paper in this town
is going to have
the F-word on it.
The F-word.
You have one day.
One day for what?
That's...
They always give an ultimatum.
Okay.
Good? Cut?
Cut.
That was your best
apology video ever.
I thought so, too.
I got a farewell card
for Debbie Brown.
I thought maybe you'd like to sign it.
Maybe throw a couple of bucks in there.
Unfortunately,
she's got some children.
I feel terrible about Debbie
Brown. She got fired because of Dwight.
So I thought I'd pass around
a goodbye card.
Maybe everyone could put in a
couple of bucks to help her through
these difficult times.
Why do bad things always
happen to the good people?
It's tragic.
It is just tragic.
You want music?
I don't care.
Come on, man. Just give it a couple
of days. I think you'll be all right.
Yeah.
You know what? I don't...
Sweet.
Pam.
Hey, Dwight.
You look really nice today.
I look like an idiot!
Hey, Karen.
Hey, Dwight. Looking sharp.
Yeah, that's 'cause I'm
your boyfriend, Jim Halpert.
Hey, Karen.
Wanna get together later
and have sexual intercourse
'cause you're my girlfriend?
Do you?
No.
Okay.
I'm good. Thanks.
Look at that.
I'm Jim Halpert.
Spot on.
A little comment.