Good morning, Pam.
Oh, welcome back, Andy.
Drew. I'm Drew now.
Oh, Drew. Sorry.
Apology not accepted.
Because it wasn't even
necessary in the first place.
Several weeks ago, Andy
Bernard had an incident.
But after five weeks
in anger management,
I'm back, and I've got
a new attitude and a new name
and a bunch of
new techniques
for dealing
with the grumpies.
Morning, Jim,
Hey, Andy.
How are you, man?
Good. Drew.
What's that?
You can call me Drew.
No, I'm not gonna
call you that.
Cool.
I can't control what you do.
I can only control what I do.
Andy.
Drew.
Dwight.
How's it going, man?
Yes. I have decided to shun Andy
Bernard for the next three years.
Which I'm looking forward to.
It's an Amish technique.
It's like slapping
someone with silence.
I was shunned from the age
of four until my sixth birthday
for not saving the excess oil
from a can of tuna.
Jim, could you please
inform Andy Bernard
that he is being shunned?
Andy, Dwight says welcome
back and that he could use a hug.
Okay. Tell him
that that's not true.
Dwight says that
he actually doesn't know
one single fact
about bear attacks.
Okay. No, Jim.
You guys.
Tell him that bears can
climb faster than they can run.
Jim, tell him!
Andy... No, it's too far.
Damn you.
Today is
safety training day.
Toby is leading
ours upstairs.
But I am giving everyone
a little bit of a treat.
We are going to listen in on Darryl's
presentation at the warehouse.
And if I know Darryl,
it gonna to be zoppity.
Now,
this is the forklift.
You need a license
to operate this machine.
That means the upstairs
office workers can't drive it.
Quiz. Mike.
Should you
drive the forklift?
I can and I have.
No, no, no!
I said, "Should you?"
You should not drive it.
You should not
drive the forklift.
You understand? You're
not allowed to drive the forklift.
It's not safe.
You don't have a license.
Guys, I'm not the only one
who's driven the forklift.
Pudge has
driven the forklift.
Madge.
I thought your name
was Pudge.
No.
It's always been Madge.
Okay.
Her.
Her? Yes, "Her" is qualified to work
a dangerous machine. You are not.
Okay?
Fine.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
We do safety training every
year or after an accident.
We've never made it
a full year.
This particular time,
I was reaching
for a supply box
on the top shelf
when one office worker,
who shall remain nameless,
kicked the ladder out
from under me and yelled...
Hey, Darryl,
how's it hanging?
And I fell and
busted my ankle and...
I'm legitimately
scared for my workers.
The baler can
flatten a car engine.
It can cut off
your arm and crush
your entire body
without skipping a beat.
Yeah!
How many people a year
do you think get their arms
cut off in a baler?
Bale 'er?
I hardly know her.
Damn it, Michael,
pay attention, man.
Anybody want
to take a guess?
Five bucks says
it's over fifty.
You really want to bet?
Anybody?
Ever since March Madness
ended, I am so bored.
How many?
Okay. You're on.
Ten people. Michael.
Ten people.
Would you like
to be one of them?
No, don't worry about it.
We'll just go double or nothing.
On what?
I don't know.
I'll figure something out.
Nice. What are you
guys talking about?
These are very
dangerous machines
down here and
the upstairs workers...
Michael?
...should not go
anywhere near them.
Yes. Yes.
But it wouldn't be the
worst thing in the world...
It would be the worst thing
in the world. It would.
What the hell is wrong
with this man? Very much so.
It's a big red
trash compactor.
It's not a trash compactor!
It's very dangerous, okay.
Don't disrespect a baler,
Mike.
All right, all right,
I got it! I got it!
Only on the rarest of
occasions would I go near...
No, you don't touch it!
There is no occasion
for you to go near
this stuff, okay?
Toby now has the floor
and he is going to
try not to screw this up
like everything
else in his life.
Let me rephrase that.
I believe that you
can do safety training
and make it sound
just as good as Darryl.
Here we go!
Okay, one thing
you're going to want to
look out for is
carpal tunnel syndrome.
It's recommended that
you take a 10-minute break
from typing every hour.
For your circulation,
you're going to
want to get up
out of your chairs
and move around for
about 10 minutes every hour.
Yes. Good. Fine.
Like stretching and...
Yeah, your computer screen
can be a big strain on your eyes,
so it's also recommended that you step
away for about 10 minutes every hour.
Wow? That is...
That time really adds up.
That's like a half an hour,
every hour?
Take them at the same time.
Okay. You know what? You're
making it sound kind of lame.
So skip ahead to
the really dangerous stuff.
Like sometimes computers
can explode, can they not?
No. No.
You always want to
keep a sweater or cardigan
of some sort
in case it gets drafty.
What about
a long-sleeved tee?
That will work.
- Long johns?
- A shawl?
You know,
anything that warms you.
Okay, you know what,
I think that everybody
is going to vomit
due to boredom.
Sorry. He is very lame.
Let's see.
Seasonal affective disorder.
A depression that
includes weight gain,
fatigue, irritability, brought
on by the low light of winter.
Thank God we only had
a baler to deal with.
Yeah, that dim light
is a bitch, ain't it?
Okay. Guys, you know what?
I didn't interrupt when you
were having your presentation.
Actually, you did.
Yes.
Okay. Let's do another one.
This is a good one.
A particular concern for
office workers
is a sedimentary lifestyle
which can contribute...
Sedentary.
Yes. Which can
contribute to heart disease.
Heart disease Kills
more people than balers.
That's called having
a fat butt, Michael.
No. No, it's sedentary.
Yeah,
that's fat butt disease.
That's what you suffer from?
You have fat butt disease,
Michael?
Excuse me, sea monster, you
weigh like a thousand pounds.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I bet you'd like to swim with
this sea monster, wouldn't you?
Ryan!
Dude, please tell
your girl to shut up.
What?
Kelly, you've insulted
the gentleman.
Please apologize.
Are you kidding me?
All right,
we out of here.
Darryl, I did not walk out
in the middle of yours, so...
Yeah, but ours was real,
Michael.
Yes.
That's what we've been
trying to tell you, Mike.
It's serious down there.
We do dangerous stuff, man.
This is shenanigans, foolishness.
Nerf ball.
You live a sweet
little nerfy life
sitting on your biscuit
never having to risk it.
Okay.
What?
So, Nerf isn't cool anymore?
Darryl thinks he's such a
man because he works in a warehouse.
Well, big deal!
I worked in a warehouse.
Men's Wearhouse.
I was a greeter.
I'd like to see
Darryl greet people.
He'd probably make
them feel like wimps.
Not me, I...
Hello, I'm Michael.
Welcome to Men's Wearhouse.
We have a special
on khaki pants today.
This is one example.
Ten.
Really? Ten?
That's your guess?
You're
a professional accountant.
There's, like,
10 green ones.
Forty-two.
I'm going to say 50.
Don't be that person.
51.
Oh, come on. That is lame.
It's a strategy.
It's called being smart.
Thank you.
Oh, jeez.
I don't know how the whole
betting thing started,
but it's fun.
Ten.
Ten's out.
Damn it!
Forty-seven, 48,
forty-nine. Jim wins.
That is not fair.
He has spent hours up here
at reception with you.
Hours and hours.
Okay. Okay.
No, constantly.
Like for years.
Okay.
Pam, depression is as
scary as a baler, right?
I don't
understand the question.
Working in an office can lead to
depression, which can lead to suicide.
I mean this is
really serious stuff.
Yeah.
Nobody commits suicide
because they work with a baler.
And yet those guys
are making fun of me,
calling me a Nerf.
That...
It's really hard to
demonstrate depression.
Their safety training
had visuals.
Yeah.
You are so right.
They have visual aids
and all we had were the facts.
You don't go to
the science museum
and get handed
a pamphlet on electricity.
You go the science museum and
you put your hand on a metal ball
and your hair
sticks up straight.
And you know science.
So, you're okay?
Indubitably.
They used props,
they used visual aids
and they just made
us look like dopes.
Idiots!
God, what are we going to do?
I don't know. I don't know.
Because you know
what our killer is?
Depression.
Wolves.
Visual aids.
Yes.
A quilt. A depression quilt.
No time to sew a quilt.
I got it.
Get me the number for
the Giant Big Box Toy Store.
You may be asking yourself
what am I doing
on a trampoline?
Well, I thought I'd
bounce here for a while,
relieve some stress
and then move on with my day.
Not. Here's a plan.
Dwight is going to gather
all of the officer workers
and all of the warehouse guys
and we're going to have
another safety seminar.
Only this time,
where's Michael?
Oh, my God,
he is on the roof.
And now I have
got their attention.
I tell them about the cold
hard facts of depression.
And then I say, "Hey,
you ever seen a suicide?"
And I jump.
And they freak out.
And they get to see
the dangers of depression
with their own eyes.
Nice side note,
they might think,
"Hey, I should have
been nicer to Michael."
But that's not
why I'm doing this.
Then I land on the trampoline,
take a couple
extra bounces for fun.
I climb off,
walk around the corner,
ta-freaking-da.
So then the next movie
moves to the top of the queue.
So number five
becomes number four,
number six
becomes number five,
number three becomes
number two, etcetera, etcetera.
And let's just say
that I just sent back
Love Actually,
which was awesome.
And they sent me Uptown
Girls, which is also awesome.
But guess what, now I want
to see Love Actually again,
but it's at
the bottom of the queue.
Oh, no, what do I do?
What I do is this.
I go online,
I go click, click, click
and I change
the order of the queue,
so that I can see Love
Actually as soon as I want to.
It's so easy, Ryan.
Do you really not
know how Netflix works?
I guess I forgot.
You're such a ditz.
Ryan, well done.
Two minutes, 42 seconds.
Additionally, Pam,
you win $10
because she said
"awesome" 12 times.
And Jim, you win $5 because she
mentioned six romantic comedies.
Okay, let's do this thing!
I'll go summon the troops!
Maybe we should
test this first.
Letterman style.
Throw a TV over or...
We measured it once.
Go buy some watermelons.
Seedless?
Just...
Creed is eating an apple.
I found a potato.
Hey, Creed.
Hey.
Yes!
Here you go.
What?
Nice!
I don't know this place
as well as I thought I did.
I'm getting cleaned out.
Ready?
Let's do it.
Drop that sucker.
Yeah! Bingo!
Deactivate the car alarm,
clean up the mess.
Okay.
Find out whose car that is.
If it's Stanley's, call the
offices of James P. Albini,
see If he handles
hate crimes.
Got it.
Also, take apart the
trampoline. Stick it in the baler.
We're not allowed
to use the baler.
Have Padge do it
or the sea monster.
I'm on it.
I'm temporarily
lifting the shun.
Thank you.
It means nothing. I need
you to do something for me.
Anything.
Okay, calm down.
I need you to acquire an
inflatable house and/or castle.
You mean a Moonbounce.
What do you think?
You've got an hour.
I'm going to need petty cash.
Shunning resumed.
Do you want a drawbridge?
Un-shun.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Re-shun.
Oh, yeah, this is much better.
It's safer.
Excellent decision.
Yes.
Thank you for seeing that.
When you land, try and
land like an eight-year-old.
These bouncy castles
are not designed for adults.
I don't know
if I want to do this.
Want to do another test?
I got plenty of
watermelons in my trunk.
No.
No more.
The tests are going terrible.
If we keep doing them, I'm
not going to want to jump.
This is about doing,
not thinking.
Right!
Doing!
Totally doing!
Let's rock and roll!
Rock and roll!
Yeah! That's right,
I'm not thinking!
Yes! Yeah!
Michael is awesome
Jumping off the roof
Bouncing on a bouncy thing
Show them who is boss
Rip a hole in the sun!
I am ready to do this!
I'm ready to make a point!
Hey! Guys, listen up,
Michael is up on the roof
and acting strange.
What's the situation?
Un-shun. I think he's suffering
from depression. Re-shun.
Okay, when is the shunning
thing going to end?
Un-shun. Never. Re-shun.
I think he wants
you all to come out
to the parking lot
and watch him die.
Is it nice outside?
It's gorgeous. Let's go!
Do I need my jacket?
No, it really is.
It's very nice.
Come on!
Will I be too warm
in a long-sleeved tee?
Everyone's going to be fine in
exactly what they're wearing! Let's go!
Let's go!
Come on! Hurry up, you guys!
My life!
Oh, my life!
Michael, what's wrong?
Everything's wrong.
The stress of
my modern office
has caused me to go
into a depression!
Depression? Isn't that just a
fancy word for feeling bummed out?
Dwight, you ignorant slut.
Depression is
a very serious illness.
Over 32,000 people
commit suicide every year
according to a 2004 study.
Is that the last year
the data was available?
Yes.
My head is in
such pain and turmoil.
Don't do anything rash.
Dwight,
where are the warehouse guys?
I didn't...
I didn't think you
needed them for this part.
Okay. That's...
You said to just...
That's the whole point,
dummy.
Okay. I'm on it.
Okay?
Attention,
blue-collar workers!
What are the odds that
this is in any way real?
I'd say, like, 10,000 to one.
Okay, I'd like 10
bucks on those odds.
If someone gives you 10,000
to one on anything, you take it.
If John Mellencamp
ever wins an Oscar,
I am going to be
a very rich dude.
Michael is up on the roof
and he's acting strange.
Oh, my life.
Michael, what's wrong?
Everything is wrong, Dwight.
The stress of my modern
office has made me depressed.
Depressed? Isn't that just a
fancy word for feeling bummed out?
Dwight, you ignorant slut!
Well, you know, the first
performance was a little off,
but I really think they hit
their stride in the second show.
I might even bring my parents
tomorrow to the matinee.
And that is why...
Oh, excuse me.
It's my favorite part.
...am going to
jump off this roof!
This is just offensive.
At least we're outside.
Hey, check it out,
there's a castle over there.
Oh, my God,
there is a castle.
No. There's nothing to
see over there, people.
There's nothing to see.
They found the castle,
Michael.
Damn it!
Oh, God. Oh, my God,
he's going to jump.
He's going to kill himself
pretending to kill himself.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Hey, Michael,
don't jump on
the bouncy castle.
You can't do that 'cause you're
going to get horribly, horribly injured.
Hey, Michael,
I have a present for you but
you have to come down and get it.
What is it?
Come down
and open it and you'll see.
Dwight, find out
what the present is.
Okay, I don't see anything.
She might be bluffing.
Dwight.
It's a...
A Repliee-Q-One-Expo
female robot.
They're only
available in Japan.
Dwight, you are such a liar.
Pam, really what is it?
Mike, this is
the opposite of safety.
You jump, you're going to
seriously hurt yourself.
You told me
that I lead a...
A cushy, wimpy Nerf life.
Yeah.
But I never said you
had nothing to live for.
What do I have to live for?
A lot of things.
You...
What about Jan?
Lovely, lovely, lovely Jan,
man.
It's going good, right?
It's complicated with Jan.
And I don't know where
I stand or what I want.
The sex isn't nearly
as good as it used to be.
Mike,
you're a very brave man.
I mean it takes
courage just to be you.
To get out of bed
every single day,
knowing full well
you got to be you.
Do you really mean that?
I couldn't do it.
I ain't that strong
and I ain't that brave.
I'm braver than you?
Way braver.
You Braveheart, man.
I Braveheart.
I am.
Come on down, okay?
Okay.
Pam, I'm coming
down to get my present.
An office is
as safe as the people in it.
And sometimes those people can
drive you to do crazy things
to show
the dangers of the office.
That's the danger
I found myself in today.
I saved a life.
My own.
Am I a hero?
I really can't say, but yes.