Brain teaser. I have two
coins, totaling 15 cents.
One of them is not a
nickel. What are they?
A dime and a nickel.
No. I said one of them
is not a nickel.
But the other one is.
I've heard that before.
Okay.
A man and his son get into a car
accident. They are rushed to the hospital.
The doctor says, "There is no
way I can operate on this boy..."
"Because he's my son." The
doctor is the boy's mother.
A man is found hanging
from the ceiling...
He stepped on a block of ice,
hung himself and the ice melted.
A hunter...
It's a polar bear, because
you're at the North Pole.
Damn it!
Tell me what
you did yesterday.
Nothing.
Nothing?
Yeah, nothing.
How was your day?
I don't care
how your day was, Michael.
Wow. Well, okay.
I don't care how your
day was either, Jan.
I was just asking you
because you asked me.
Why do you set me up
like that?
Tell me what
you did yesterday.
I worked.
And then I went home
to my condo,
and Carole came over
and we had sex.
Is that what you want to hear?
Never, ever, ever sleep
with your boss.
I'm so lucky that Jan and
I only got to second base.
Hi, Pam.
I'm great.
So, Pam, I'd like you
to keep a log
of everything Michael does,
hour-by-hour,
so that we can analyze it
at corporate, okay?
I don't know if I'm...
Thanks, Pam.
It's weird. Jan used to treat
Michael like he was a 10-year old.
But lately
it's like he's five.
So, you excited?
Yeah.
Very excited?
Yes, I'm very excited.
Extremely excited?
Just very? That's cool.
I have spent
a year here.
And I have to commit
or get out.
So, Dwight's the top salesman
in the company
and he's taking me
on my first sales call today.
And, I'm excited.
I am very excited.
Ryan hasn't made a sale yet.
But more importantly,
he hasn't made an ally yet.
Is he gonna be a slacker,
loser, wise-ass like Jim was,
or is he gonna join the
Dwight Army of Champions?
So, what if they're
not talking much?
Then does it make sense to
kind of lead the conversation?
You know, just till it gets to a point
where they are asking questions?
So where is the sales office?
When you are ready
to see the sales office,
the sales office will
present itself to you.
Your journey begins now.
Hey.
What?
My chair's squeaking.
Is it?
You took my chair.
No, I didn't.
I took back the chair that you took
from me, but I didn't take your chair.
When you get up, I'm just
gonna take it back anyway, so...
So I guess I can't get up?
Hey, Coselli. The Cos, Cosby.
Hey, hey, hey!
I love Jell-O Pudding Pops.
My son, Theo, loves
Jell-O Pudding Pops, too.
Do you know
where we are, temp?
I know where we're not.
I hold in my hand
a beet seed. Take it.
When you...
Damn it.
Hey, Big Tuna, can I
talk to you for a second?
Sure.
Can you stand up
and talk to me over there?
That's it? That's what
you came up with?
I am acting my heart out here.
Really?
Yeah, really.
You asked for my help,
so I helped.
Attention,
Scranton Business Park.
There will be
complimentary pretzels
available in the lobby
from now until 4:00,
as a thank you
to our loyal tenants.
Once a year,
they bring in a little cart,
and they give away
free pretzels.
It's really not a big deal.
To some people it is.
Productivity is important,
but how can I be productive,
if I have this one little thing in
my brain that I cannot get out?
And that one little thing
is a soft pretzel.
So, I'm just gonna have
my soft pretzel,
I'll get to work and
I'm gonna be super-productive.
Look out for me!
Oh, come on.
And just as you have planted
your seed in the ground,
I am going
to plant my seed in you.
I don't think you know
what you're saying.
It smells pretty bad,
doesn't it?
Uh-huh.
It's called bull crap and a client
can smell it from a mile away.
Gotcha.
Oh, hey, I forgot something
in my car. I'll be right back.
Okay.
Of course.
I wake up every
morning in a bed that's too small,
drive my daughter to a school
that's too expensive.
And then I go to work to a
job for which I get paid too little.
But, on pretzel day...
Well, I like pretzel day.
"Cause they were acting
all tough and everything,
Uh-huh.
But what they were
rapping about was cupcakes
and The Chronicles of Narnia.
God, who invented
cupcakes, right?
I don't know...
I want to kill them.
Hey, Phyllis,
what are you doing?
I'm just saying hi to Bob.
No, I think
you're cutting in line.
Well, settle down, Scott.
No, I'm not gonna settle down.
No way. Uh-uh.
Get in the back, please.
Boo!
Back in line.
Thank you.
That's right.
What a pair of marys.
This is pretzel day.
Hey, Dwight,
you're a great salesman.
Can you teach me? Sure, Ryan.
I'll make you kneel
in cow manure
and I'll abandon you
in a beet field.
Oh, that sounds great, Dwight.
I really appreciate that.
Thank you so much. A mentor...
Congratulations,
resourceful salesman.
You have passed the second
challenge. Welcome to Schrute farm!
Love me, love me
Say that you love me
Fool me, fool me
Stop.
Go on and fool me
Love me, love me
Say that you love me...
This is not fair. It's gonna
be in my head all day. Please.
Fool me, fool me
Go on and fool me
Love me, love me
Say that you love me
This is not
a proportionate response.
Fool me, fool me
Go on and fool me
I don't care about
anything but you
Whatever happened
to those guys?
Michael.
No cuts.
Oh, Pam, just the woman I'd
like to see. You read my mind...
Great, I thought
you might want to
use this time
to authorize some checks.
I thought that maybe
you could wait in line
for me while I go to
the bathroom?
You're an angel.
Hey, why don't you
just go up to your office
and get some work done
and I'll bring you a pretzel?
Because I like them a certain
way and if it gets screwed up
then this whole thing's blown.
You know, I just think
that it's really important
that you be productive today.
Pam, productivity starts with
patience and determination.
I'll be back.
It is time for your next test.
You have planted the beet seed.
You have walked the long,
lonely walk of loneliness...
Look, man,
I was in a frat in college,
so I know what you're doing.
I get it.
You know
what your problem is?
You know why
you haven't made any sales?
"Cause you think
you know everything.
You have to trust that
maybe there are other people
that can teach you things.
Are you ready to learn?
Are you ready
for the final test?
Yeah.
Come on!
Thank you.
Hi, please tell me you have
a sweet pretzel left.
We do.
Thank God.
And we have
18 different toppings.
We have sweet glaze,
cinnamon sugar,
chocolate, white chocolate,
fudge, M&Ms,
caramel dip, mint chip,
chocolate chip,
marshmallows, nuts,
toffee nuts, coconut,
peanut butter drizzle,
Oreo, sprinkles,
cotton candy bits
and powdered sugar.
Is there any way that
you could do all of them?
The works. You got it.
All right! Thank you.
Please be seated.
What was that?
Pay no attention
to the spirits
that haunt
this hallowed ground.
Is that your cousin Mose?
Yes.
Mose is my cousin
and he lives here.
He will always be
my best friend.
Unless things go well
with Ryan today,
in which case, I won't hang
out with Mose so much anymore.
What is the greatest danger
facing Dunder Mifflin?
Outsourcing and consolidation
of competition.
Wrong. Flash floods.
What is the true cause
of Robert Mifflin's suicide?
Depression?
Wrong. He hated himself.
What is the Dharma Initiative?
I can't believe that Ryan is not
back yet. Where could they be?
Sales take a long time.
Oh, my God, I'm so worried.
I'm sure
Dwight will protect him.
I don't know,
Dwight's so weird.
He's not weird,
he's just individualistic.
No, he's a freak.
You're a freak!
Final question,
young Ryan Howard.
What
is Michael Scott's
greatest fear?
Loneliness.
Maybe women.
Wrong.
He's not afraid of anything.
Also, I would have
accepted snakes.
Fear is what it's all about.
You cannot sell
while undergoing fear.
You need to vanquish fear!
One must wrestle fear
to the ground.
You will now wrestle
my cousin Mose!
No. Okay. It's over,
this is over. Okay?
All right, wrestle him
to the ground!
No. You're a freak.
No, just... It's the final...
I'm not doing this anymore.
It's part of the challenge.
This is over. Goodbye.
Ryan, don't...
Ryan, you don't have to wrestle
him. Ryan, just get in the coffin.
Ryan?
Bye, Ryan.
He seemed nice.
Where are all the animals?
Ryan, come on. I am sorry. I
am sorry. Mose is sorry, too.
Look, he sent over a basket with
eggs and some fat-back bacon,
and look,
something he whittled.
Are you still mad?
It's just...
Jim and I didn't get along
and I didn't want it to be
that way again.
You know,
I wanted us to be a team.
An unstoppable team that
competed against other teams.
Look, that's not
what I wanted, okay?
I just wanted
to go on a sales call.
Oh, screw gun, the sales call!
Hey!
Mr. Coselli? Hey, hey, hey,
the Cos. What's going on?
Do we have a deal? Deal or
no deal? Let's make a deal.
So what is the deal?
Establish time frames. Keep the
phrase "real dollars" in their heads.
And always keep
the power in the conversation.
That's why you're losing them
on the cold calls.
"Cause you say the word
"please" too much.
Wait, can you go back...
Michael always says,
"K-I-S-S."
"Keep It Simple Stupid," great
advice, hurts my feelings every time.
Okay, I'm going to
establish time frames.
Good.
I'm gonna put everything
in terms of real dollars.
Right.
I'm gonna ask a lot of questions
that all have positive answers.
Then I can say, "That would be
better" or, "We would like that."
That sort of thing.
Exactly, yeah. That's good.
I am going to try
to be confident but not cocky.
Oh, hey everyone!
I am officially streamlining
the efficiency of this corporation.
Second, I...
Second?
Yes, second, Toby.
Second, I am insisting
on increased accountability
from every single one of you.
Account... Michael,
what is going on?
And I will be
taking questions.
Did you have
a lot of sugar today, Michael?
What's on your suit?
Caramel dip.
But, one question
at a time, please.
Phyllis, Stanley,
I want you to switch desks.
I am going to re-organize
and restructure
the physical layout of the
office to maximize everything.
I think we're getting a lot done,
don't you, on paper at least?
And we are, after all,
a paper company, are we not?
Are we not? Are we not?
Are you with me?
Thank you very much.
They really didn't
like me.
They did not. But they
didn't have to say it to your face.
I don't get it. I don't get
what I did wrong.
Not everything's a lesson,
Ryan. Sometimes you just fail.
It's those online paper jerks.
The whole business is changing.
You know what?
They're gonna be screwed
once this whole Internet fad
is over.
What are you doing?
Oh, no, no, no!
No!
Ryan! Yes!
Ryan the temp, yeah!
Come on! Come on!
Courtesy of Dunder Mifflin!
Come on, drive!
You drive!
Dunder Mifflin,
this is Pam. Oh, hi, Jim.
He's on a sales call.
No message?
Bye, Jim.
Temp! Temp! Temp!
Ryan! Ryan! Ryan! Ryan! Yes!
Just think, that temp agency
could have sent you anywhere.
I think about that
all the time.
Good night, Pam.
Night.
Hey, what time is it?
Twenty past five.
AM. or P.M.?
P.M.
Oh, good.
These came for you, contracts,
Frank Coselli.
Oh, Coselli, with the Jell-O.
This is a huge sale.
Yes, right, good.
Night, Michael.
Good night.
Dunder Mifflin.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Hi.
I'm sorry, I forgot Kevin's
extension. It's a fantasy football thing.
And I was just gonna go
through the system
'cause I didn't think
you'd be there.
Why are you still there?
I had to work late.
Jan's making me keep a log of
everything Michael does all day.
Oh, wow!
Do you think you could
send me a copy of that?
Yeah, totally.
So...
Do you...
Oh, I'm sorry. Go ahead.
No, I...
Everything's pretty much
the same here.
Oh, good.
A little different.
What time is it there?
What time is it here?
We're in the same time zone.
Yeah, right.
How far away
did you think we were?
I don't know. It felt far.
Yeah, I have a question
for you.
What?
How many words per minute
does the average person type?
I type 90.
Shut up.
Mavis Beacon
doesn't even type 90.
It's true.
Okay, I said "average."
Seventy? How many do you type?
Forget it. I was just
about to brag. Forget it.
Come on. Tell me.
No. No.
You have to tell me now.
Sixty-five.
Okay, no need to laugh.
No, that's respectable.
Respectable?
So, okay, I'm watching
the movie, by myself.
Right.
Because I just wanted
a relaxing evening at home.
Okay.
And I'm freaking out.
Yeah.
That movie is so scary.
I know.
But I'm holding on
because I keep
waiting for Sandra Bullock
to show up.
No way! How do you confuse
28 Days with 28 Days Later?
Because I got it
at Blockbuster
and they don't put
the pictures on the box.
No,
you're making this up.
Would I make that up?
Yes.
Fancy new Beesly would make
that up. New apartment, new stories...
Oh, yeah,
my fancy new apartment.
I have one bedroom,
one bathroom and a closet.
And how many kitchens?
I have one kitchen.
Well, you got totally
taken for a ride, Beesly.
It's actually...
Most apartments
these days have like three...
Three kitchens?
Yes.
How are you gonna cook every
meal of the day in one kitchen?
Hey, Ryan, are you okay?
Pam?
Yeah.
Okay, bye!
Oh, yeah,
I should probably go, too...
Oh, no, I was...
I don't know what...
Do you have to go?
Yeah...
No, I should probably go, too.
Okay.
I mean...
Yeah.
Bye, Pam.
Bye, Jim.
Three hundred, sixty-four days
till the next pretzel day.