All right,
let's get started.
Oh, first off, we're supposed to
be pushing card stock this week.
So, let's push
card stock this week.
Also... What is this?
Tape recorder.
For what?
For recording.
Michael is on vacation and he
has asked me to record all meetings
and to type up
the transcripts.
Okay. Karen,
any news from that law firm?
Yeah, the deal closed yesterday.
It's a six-month commitment.
Oh, my God!
Dwight, what are you doing?
What?
You're not allowed to take off
your pants in the middle of the office.
I'm not. Dwight, you know
what, just back off, okay?
That's making
me uncomfortable.
This is sexual harassment,
by the way.
Oh, my God,
he's got a knife!
I do not have a knife.
No. Let the record show that Dwight
K. Schrute is now completely nude
and is holding a plastic
knife to Stanley's neck?
Let the record show
that Jim Halpert is a liar!
Dwight Schrute is now
wearing a baby's bonnet.
I am not.
Oh, Jim Carrey
just walked in.
Dwight, get his
autograph for Michael...
Jim Carrey did not
just walk in, okay?
Yes, he...
Dwight,
what is that on your stomach?
Is that a Muppet Babies
tattoo?
Oh, my God,
Karen, you're right.
That is Animal
from the Muppet Babies.
You can't see my stomach...
I am now chopping off
Phyllis' head with a chain saw!
Hey, mon!
Hey.
You have a bunch
of messages and...
That's nice.
Hannah quit
while you were gone.
I guess she memoed
to file some complaints
she had about
being a working mother,
and so you might
also have to be deposed.
Relax.
Just relax, okay?
Okay.
I'll get to all of it later.
It's kind of serious.
Aren't you going to
ask me how Jamaica was?
Say it. Ask me.
How was Jamaica?
It was so good!
Hey, mon!
At Sandals, Jamaica, when
somebody says, "Hey, mon,"
everybody says,
"Hey, mon," back.
Oh, Michael,
I'm glad you're here.
Stanley. You know what?
It is really good
to see you, too.
My bonus check was $100
less than you promised.
Okay, well, payroll is
in charge of all of that...
They said
I should talk to you.
Well, I am just
getting settled in.
So I'm gonna...
I am not doing
a lick more work
until I get my
full bonus check.
You are not as much fun
as your Jamaican brothers,
mon.
You wanna talk about it?
Nope.
I still haven't
found an apartment yet.
I'm living in a hotel.
Yesterday, I saw a for-rent
sign down the street from Jim,
and he said he didn't think
it'd be such a good idea.
He said it would be
like we were living together
in different houses,
two blocks away.
Feelin' hot, hot, hot!
That's all I know so far,
but I'm gonna keep practicing.
It's good.
You know, I had never been
out of the country before now.
I got to see how Jamaicans
live. It is great.
You know, they just relax,
they party all the time.
It's kind of
an impoverished country.
Yeah.
Gosh. Great.
You know what, Pam?
Make a note.
I want us all to start having
piña coladas every day at 3:00.
Well, you can't today.
We're doing inventory.
Inventory's at
the end of December.
We couldn't do it without you,
SO we postponed.
I specifically went on
vacation so I would miss it.
Inventory is boring.
In the islands, they don't make
you do stuff like take inventory.
Why do you think SO many
businesses move to the Caymans?
Tonight, we are going
to have an inventory luau.
I want to bring back
a little slice of paradise
to the Dunder Mifflin
Warehouse Inventory.
So, Party Planning Committee,
get on it.
By the end of the day?
That's impossible.
The Jamaicans don't have
a word for "impossible".
Yep, it's English.
It's "impossible".
Michael, there's no
way we can do it in time.
How hard is a luau?
All you need are some
grass skirts, pineapple, poi,
tiki torches, suckling pig,
some fire dancers.
That's all you need.
Come on in!
Settle in.
Settling...
And settled. Good.
There is something I would
like to show everybody.
See this sign?
"No shirt.
No shoes. No problem."
This is an attitude I would
like all of you to have right here.
So what if we have to stay late
and do inventory? No problem.
Oh, my God. Is that Jan?
- What?
- Where?
- On the left.
No, no, no. That's...
Oh, my God...
No, that's a German woman
named Urgle Grue.
Jan told me to play it cool
and not tell anybody
because it could
get us both in trouble.
So, officially,
I did not see her.
But I did see Jan there
in our room
at night
and in the morning.
And that's all I'm gonna say.
Sex. Sex.
We had sex.
I had sex with her.
I had sex with Jan.
Hey, dude.
I just got back from Jamaica.
Big whoop.
I was in Hotlanta.
That whole town is waxed.
Yeah, that sounds amazing,
but you know what?
The lady, Jan Levinson,
wanted to go to Montego Bay.
You took The Ice Queen?
I don't buy it.
Well, I'm looking at a photo,
right now,
and, I'm telling you,
it could be in Maxim.
They wouldn't give you
a subscription to Maxim.
Oh, no?
No.
Okay. Well,
check this out.
I'm sending you some e-mail.
You got it?
What? No, I got nothing.
Check it again.
Hit refresh.
Yeah, Mike, still nothing.
Okay, wait a second.
I sent it to you at
packer@dundermifflin.com...
Packaging@dundermifflin.com...
Uh-oh.
Wait. I just got it
from somebody else.
Wow!
This is hot. Damn!
How do I get you
out of this picture?
Darryl?
Hey. Hi, where's Darryl?
He's in the office.
Okay.
Hi. Hey, man,
how's it going?
All right.
What's up, Mike?
That's great. Okay.
So did you get
an e-mail from me?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, that was supposed to
go to Packer, not Packaging.
Did you already forward it
to a whole bunch of people?
Uh-uh.
Okay.
Well, did you get the
second e-mail that I sent
explaining that the first
e-mail was a mistake
and that you
should delete it?
Yep.
Have you sent
that out to everyone?
Mike,
I'm very busy down here.
Yikes.
Already sent it to you,
my friend.
Fantastic.
Boring.
Call me if she rolls over.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
You sure?
Yeah. Yes.
I'm just in this, like,
stupid fight with Karen.
Oh!
You want to talk about it?
Really?
I have a special
assignment for you.
Who's the target?
A sensitive e-mail has
been released into the office.
It contains a file.
A picture.
The filename is
Jamaica Jan Sun Princess.
What's it of?
Not important.
Unless you're willing
to tell me everything,
I cannot accept
this assignment.
Okay, then forget it.
Okay, I accept it.
So, I don't know, I just feel like
we've been dating a month, right?
Same street, I think
that might be a little close.
A little bit much.
What?
How far away does she
live now, like, 10 minutes?
Yeah, I guess.
Honestly, I think you
should go easy on her.
No, I didn't mind helping
Jim with his problem.
That's what friends do.
I help Phyllis all the time.
Just yesterday, I untangled
a piece of tape from her hair.
So, yeah.
Hey, thanks a lot.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I mean,
it's better than listening
to Michael
play a conch shell,
which is what I was doing.
Oh, also,
Michael went to
Jamaica with Jan... Yeah.
How have we not
talked about this already?
I mean, what happened there?
Kidnapping?
Hey, I need to talk to you...
Not now, not ever.
...about you and Jan.
None of your business.
I wish that were true,
but it... It...
It seems from that
photo that two of you
have entered into
an intimate relationship.
That photo is my personal
property, and if you are telling me
that you went on my computer
and stole that photo,
then I am going
to call the cops.
Michael, nine different
people e-mailed me that photo,
including my ex-wife
and we don't talk.
Well, this is probably
the icebreaker you need.
You know,
for your own protection,
you should disclose
the relationship to HR.
I bet you would
love all the details,
wouldn't you,
you skeevy little perv?
All right. If you're
having a relationship
with your superior,
you must disclose it.
No, no.
No, I am not dating Jan.
She was very clear
about that.
Just two like souls
having a romantic time
in the most
romantic place on Earth.
Got enough, weirdo?
All right, thanks, Michael.
Okay.
Okay, we only have
three hours, people,
to plan a whole luau
and you're not helping.
What are
the ingredients of poi?
I've called every grocery store in
Scranton and no one sells whole pigs.
Did you try
the petting zoo?
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Just a second. Michael?
It's Jan on the phone.
Oh, God!
No, no, no. Hang up. Hang up.
Tell her I'm not here.
Don't... Don't...
I've ran out of gas.
I hit a deer. I hit...
I hit a deer with my car.
No. I hit a cat.
Tell her I hit a cat.
He'll call you back.
Okay. Great.
Do you think she bought it?
Okay.
Michael hit a deer?
Michael! Michael, there's an
emergency in the warehouse.
An accident?
Is somebody hurt?
No, it's...
It involves the photograph.
Oh, God! No, no, no.
Mike,
you're a rock star, man!
You are the man!
Yeah!
Well done!
All right. Okay.
Hit that corporate booty.
Nice to hit it!
Hello! Hi!
Attention, everyone.
Apparently, there is an
e-mail circulating around
that contains a very PG-13
rated picture of me and a woman.
Jan.
No, Kevin, a woman.
Maybe Jan, maybe...
Urgle Grue.
My point is
that if you get it,
I would ask that you just
delete it, sight unseen.
Let's be professional,
all right?
Feelin'...
Feelin' hot, hot, hot
Hey!
Hey.
What are you doing out here?
Island living, you know.
Jan called.
She's coming in
later to talk to you.
Did she say what it's about?
That's all she said.
Olé, olé, olé
olé, olé, olé
The people in the party,
hot, hot, hot
I think you dropped this.
You sure?
Definitely.
I have disconnected
the office T1 line.
I have ordered
that be taken down.
All right.
I've destroyed all printouts
from the bathroom.
There are copies
in the bathroom?
There were a lot of them.
All right.
I think I owe you one.
Sorry?
For talking
sense into Halpert.
The Days Inn Room 228 was
staring to get really depressing.
Yeah, I know,
don't worry about it.
I mean,
he was being ridiculous.
Yeah. But thanks, seriously.
Sure.
Okay.
Yes!
Yes, what'd I tell you?
I knew he'd turn up.
You see that?
This is the greatest night
of my life.
Who did this to you?
Where is he?
What?
No. It's not... It's nothing.
It's hot in here.
Yeah.
Thanks.
You don't need to stay here.
I know.
So you're PMSing
pretty bad, huh?
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Michael.
Hello.
Hi, Jan. You look
tan.
I was in Scottsdale,
visiting my sister.
Yeah? How was it?
Very sunny.
Family's important.
Michael. I would
like to speak with you
in your office, please.
Okay. Yep.
Why am I here, Michael?
In the last year,
I've gone through a divorce,
an identity theft,
a husband who
would not communicate.
This is neither
here nor there.
My psychiatrist thinks that I have
some self-destructive tendencies,
and that for once,
I should indulge them.
Are you following me?
Yes.
I think I owe it to myself
to find some kind of
happiness, you know?
I mean, even... Even if it
means lowering my expectations
or redefining
the word itself.
Okay, yeah...
This is the thing, you know?
I am attracted to you.
I don't... I don't
know why, I... But I am,
and I need to
follow my instincts.
At least, that's what
Dr. Perry thinks.
Who's Dr. Perry? I...
This is the point, okay?
You're wrong for me.
In...
In every way.
But I still...
Well, I...
...find myself wanting
to be with you.
And I to you,
in addition,
feel the same feelings
that you are, as well.
Good. Good.
So, thanks for coming by.
Yes...
I...
Oh. Good.
Okay.
Thank you for
taking the time.
Well, thanks for coming over.
I appreciate...
Wait 15 minutes, okay?
Then find an excuse and
meet me at your condo, okay?
Okay.
Jan?
You complete me.
Oh, God.
Hey.
You remember when we were
planning our honeymoon,
and you wanted to go to Hawaii
and I wanted to go to Mexico?
Yeah.
I was definitely right.
Oh, brother.
What am I gonna do?
I'm gonna hang it up at home.
I don't have a lot of art.