Can you confirm
that the straps are tight?
Yes.
But this seems a little...
And now the chains.
A lot of people think that
magic camp is just for kids.
And that's why so many other
people in my class were kids.
Self-fulfilling prophecy.
It's really for anybody with a
dream and a belief in magic,
and a little extra time
after school.
Magic, magic, magic.
And now, Michael
the Magic will attempt
to escape
from extreme bondage.
Can he do it?
I don't see how he can.
I know how.
He'll dislocate his shoulder
and slip his arm out.
No. No.
Everyone, now
count down with me.
Three...
Sorry. Sorry, quick thing.
So is it true that
if you can't get out,
you don't want anyone
to help you?
I will get out.
Oh, yes. I will.
So we shouldn't help you no matter
how much you might beg and plead?
No. All right. Just... This is getting
hot, so let's just do this, okay?
Ready! Three! Two! One!
Go!
Is everything okay, Michael?
Yes.
I cannot tell you
how I plan to escape
other than by using magic.
That is the magician's code.
Separately on
an unrelated note,
if you happen to find
a small brass key...
All right, ready? Come on,
guys. Early worm gets the worm.
Another worm, like,
are they friends?
That's, "Early bird
gets the worm."
Okay.
Pam, would you smell
my breath?
No. No.
Let me smell.
Good. Not great.
Michael, you go to parties all
the time. Why is tonight so special?
Well, tonight is so special
because my boss's
boss's boss, the CFO,
not his initials,
common mistake,
is having a little shindig
for all the managers
in the company.
And Jan and I are going
as a couple for the first time.
So it's kind of our
coming out party, really.
And that is why tonight
IS SO special.
Jimbo, last chance, carpool.
Oh, no thanks. I think
Karen and I will take my car.
You sure? Might be
a good idea... Yeah.
...if we all went together, we could
save some gas, have fun. Long trip.
Thanks.
Play some games?
Not... Yeah.
I Spy.
Why don't I wanna go?
Didn't expect to need a
reason. So, let me think here.
I don't know
any of these people.
It's an obligation.
I don't like talking paper
in my free time.
Or in my work time.
And did I use
the word "pointless"?
Thanks for inviting me along.
Oh, sure.
I really didn't give it
any thought.
Wait, should you be going?
- Hello, you.
- Michael?
Hey, buttercup.
I am on my way. I should
be there in about 15...
All right, let's just blow
this party off.
That's what she said.
Yeah.
Am I on speakerphone?
Yes, you are.
Is anybody else...
Hello, Jan!
Hi, Dwight. Okay, Michael,
take me off speakerphone.
No problem.
Okay, let's just go
to a motel and...
Okay.
...just, like, rip
into each other like we did
on that black sand beach
in Jamaica.
Okay, Jan?
Jan, this party is actually
a very big step for us.
Sol...
I'm still on speaker?
...1... I don't know.
Are the cameras there?
Maybe.
Okay. See you soon.
Okay. All right. Bye.
Talk to you later, Jan.
Hey, Michael left early.
So a bunch of us are gonna go
to Poor Richards for happy hour.
You should come.
I can't.
My brother, he just unloaded the
jet skis and he, kind of, took a bath,
SO we're gonna go
get hammered.
Okay. Well,
we're going to a bar.
Hey, you have to come
to stuff with me.
I'm serious.
If you're going to be
my boyfriend,
you have to do
boyfriend things.
Okay.
I've decided that I'm going
to be more honest.
I'm gonna start telling people
what I want directly.
So look out world 'cause old
Pammy is getting what she wants.
And don't call me Pammy.
Beauty.
Thank you, sir.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you.
You're dressed
exactly like the servants.
Shut up.
Okay, change shirts with me.
Wait.
I don't think
yours will fit me.
I don't care.
Oh, wow.
Here.
Don't put my jacket on...
Don't give me that.
That would have been
really embarrassing.
Yes.
Crisis averted.
Okay
That duck is so cute.
Hey, Pam.
Hey, guys.
Oscar. Angela.
Hi!
Actually, it's polite to arrive early.
And smart.
Only really good friends
show up early.
Ergo, de facto, go to a party
early, become a really good friend.
Oh, potato salad?
It's from both of us.
No, it's not.
Wonderful. Let's see
where we can put this.
Okay.
Oh, you know, you probably
want to leave the cover on
until the guests get here.
It's been sitting
in my car all day.
Sun beating down
on the mayonnaise.
Just... You never know.
Kevin, you and Stacy
set a date yet?
Yeah.
Oh, my God. When is it?
It's complicated.
I would appreciate
some space on this.
Hey!
Hey! You made it.
Well, you said
it was important, so...
It is.
How's it going?
What's up, Pam?
Hey, Kenny.
Sorry about the jet skis.
You guys all want
a round on me?
Yeah!
Yeah?
Let's get you a drink.
Thanks, man.
I'm thirsty.
No, thank you. Roy, I...
You should
get a round, Pam.
Oh, you know that line
on the top of the shrimp?
That's feces.
What you looking for?
You bring dip?
I'm sure that it's catered.
I need you
to sign these, Michael.
It's a waiver
of some of your rights.
You should read it carefully.
It releases the company in
the event that our relationship,
in your opinion or in reality,
interferes with work.
You get a copy, I get a copy
and a third copy goes to HR.
Awesome. I'm gonna frame mine.
I could frame yours, too.
You realize this is...
This is a legal document
that says you can't
sue the company...
Over our love.
I've never told you
that I love you.
You don't have to, Jan.
This contract says it all.
I am taking a calculated risk.
What's the upside?
I overcome my nausea,
fall deeply in love,
babies, normalcy,
no more self-loathing.
Downside?
I date Michael Scott publicly
and collapse in on myself
like a dying star.
What's this over the "I"?
It's a heart.
Why is this so hard?
That's what she said.
Oh, my God, what am I saying?
I love this woman!
Oh, God.
Michael, please.
Do you ever watch
Battlestar Galactica?
No? Then you're an idiot.
Hello, Michael.
Rachel! Boy,
you clean up good.
The place looks great with
all the lights on and everything.
Actually looks bigger with
people in it. It's weird. So...
Jan, glad you could make it.
Oh, of course.
Of course, David.
Do you remember Michael Scott
from the Scranton branch?
Of course, I do.
How are you, Michael?
Jan and I are lovers.
It feels so good
to finally say that out loud.
David, can I speak
to you privately
for just a moment, please?
Excuse me.
Okay.
No. Actually, one of these
is supposed to be a light.
Oh, sorry.
So did the merger
go smoothly or...
It did.
"Like butter."
Mike Myers, SNL.
You should ask Karen.
She was one of them.
I'm the only one left. Everybody
else was either fired or quit.
And there's one in anger
management. - Yeah.
But you're great now, right?
We're all great. Aren't we great?
We're good.
Michael,
please stop that, okay?
Can I get anyone anything?
I could go for an appe-teaser.
Martini, please.
Yep, Bagel Bites or something.
Rachel, your house
is beautiful.
Thank you.
What's the square footage?
About 5,000.
Does that include the garage?
Dwight, wow.
That's not appropriate.
I don't know.
It's a common question.
David, how much
did this house cost?
These old Colonials are great
when they're sound.
I'd love to
take a look around.
I'll show you around, sure.
Cool. Let's start
with the banisters.
Hey.
Do you see
that guy behind you
in the blue blazer
against the wall?
Yep.
That's Drake.
And just so, you know, I don't
want to be weird or anything,
but we used to date.
Okay. Cool.
Thanks for telling me.
And it didn't end well.
Got you. All right.
This was a gift
from Lee lacocca.
Twenty-year-old
single malt Scotch.
Here is to Mr. lacocca and his
failed experiment, the De Lorean.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Do you have any ice?
Sure.
How about
some Splenda?
One, two, three! Up Jenkins!
Down Jenkins!
Oh, I think I hear
the quarter over here.
Where?
On this side.
No, it is definitely
under one of these hands.
I, kind of, heard it
on Roy's side too.
No. It is here.
Not here. Not here. Not here.
Not here.
Good thing
you didn't listen to me.
Yeah. Close one.
Not here.
It's not here.
Okay, it's either
here or here.
Not here.
Oh, yes! Yes!
Nice job.
I can read you like a book.
Oh, yeah?
You can't keep
anything from me.
Bottoms up!
Hey, Creed.
Hey!
What's up, Creed?
What do you guys up to?
Hello.
You're the man, buddy.
I run a small fake ID company from
my car with a laminating machine
that I swiped
from the sheriff's station.
Yeah, these studs
are way too far apart.
What's in here?
That's a guest room.
Just the one window?
Oh, I must get that.
You'll have to excuse me.
Are those real pearls?
Yes. They're...
Good.
Well, it was nice meeting
you guys. Take care.
Well, if you're wondering why
his wife was staring daggers at me,
it's because I kind of saw him for a
little bit when they were separated.
Oh, didn't notice.
Really? I thought
it was so obvious.
I'm glad it didn't
make you uncomfortable.
No, it was before I
knew you, so it's fine.
This one really smells
like vanilla. Check that out.
That's nice.
You and the missus
should join us
in Sandals, Jamaica
next Christmas.
Michael, I think
David probably wants
to spend Christmas here
with his family.
Yeah. They don't
allow kids at Sandals.
They are persona
non grata there.
Oh, but it's fun.
It is an awesome place.
You would not believe
how low this girl can limbo.
It's crazy.
David, I'm sorry,
you're just going to have to
excuse us for just a couple minutes.
Sorry.
Okay. Okay.
Excuse me. What's going on?
What is it?
Sorry.
What's... What's the matter?
What... What did I...
Come on.
Just... Just... Just...
What are you doing?
Don't you know what I'm doing?
Yeah, but you could tell me.
Wow. What... What is that?
Why are we... Why are
we going in the bathroom?
I thought this was
where you liked your privacy.
Shut up.
What has gotten
into you? No, no, no.
What?
Come on, let's get back
to the party. Come on.
Wait, let me just take my dress
off. We're missing everybody.
Don't take that...
No, stop it! Stop it!
Jan! No! No! No!
Michael...
No means
"Please don't."
Means... Slam me up
against the wall right here.
I'm not going to slam you up
against anything.
You're acting inappropriate,
Jan. I want you so...
I'm acting inappropriate?
Yeah.
Forget it.
Get out of my way.
Here.
Hey!
Where have you been all night?
I was looking forward
to hanging out with you.
I was...
Hey, don't you have
a daughter?
Yes.
Oh, good. You're up.
Hey, who makes this chair?
I don't know.
It was here when I was born.
I want one.
It's really good, solid
construction. It's comfortable.
What is this, oak?
I don't know.
What do you know?
God, I hate these parties.
You wanna sneak out back
and shoot some hoops?
Meet me outside
in two minutes.
Now you stay here and have fun
'cause I'm going to go out back
and shoot hoops with David Wallace.
Okay.
Don't mention
that you and I are dating
'cause I think he might
still have feelings for me.
Wallace?
What the hell? Have you
dated, like, every guy here?
Wow.
Okay.
You got me.
I so got you.
So none of them?
Of course not.
I mean you're,
kind of, like, my first.
Really?
Oh, my God, it's so easy...
Okay.
...it's not even fun.
Hey, Jan.
Not too good.
Did you get a chance to try
Michael's homemade potato salad?
Rachel thinks that I
brought homemade potato salad.
But I just picked it up at
the supermarket. It's funny.
I wish I could make
potato salad that good.
It's just potatoes
and mayonnaise.
There's something wrong
with Jan.
What's...
What's with Jan and Michael?
I don't know...
Where to begin.
My ball.
The chimney's in decent shape.
Not great.
I found some termite damage
in a crawl space
and some structural flaws
in the foundation.
So, all in all,
it was a pretty fun
cocktail party.
What?
I want us to make it.
I want a fresh start.
That's awesome.
That's what I want.
Okay, but in order
for us to make it,
there can't be any secrets
between us.
I didn't...
I didn't do anything.
Ask anybody. I totally
could have and I didn't at all.
Just listen.
Remember that casino night
about a month
before we were supposed
to get married?
I kissed Jim.
What?
He told me how he felt
and I guess
I had feelings, too.
And we kissed.
Jim came on to you?
Just listen.
No, I am listening! That's
the problem, I'm listening!
Don't yell.
Don't yell?
This is over.
Yeah. You're right.
This is so over!
Are you kidding me, Pam?
Come on!
God!
Stupid jet skis!
Our first fight.
If this is about
what happened in the bathroom,
there was no place
to cuddle...
I feel sick.
You didn't have any of
the potato salad, did you?
You know, we were good when we
were just running around, you know?
In secret. It was wrong
and it was exciting,
and maybe it was a mistake
to take it public.
Well, if that's the way
you feel, my lady,
then you have hurt me greatly.
Michael...
Greatly.
Please don't cry.
I'm not going to cry.
I feel like it,
but I am not going to.
Why don't you just take
your stupid love contract
and tear it up
into a million pieces?
It was never a love
contract, Michael. Yeah.
And besides, I have
already given a copy to David.
It would be just as embarrassing
to get it back from him
as it was handing it to him...
I want the house, Jan.
I want the picket fence.
I want the ketchup fights and
the tickling and the giggling.
I didn't mean it, okay?
I was...
Whatever.
I was tired. I'm tired and I didn't eat
enough. And that's all. That was it.
That's it. You didn't mean it.
That's all. No, I didn't.
That's all. So...
I'm just saying
I didn't mean it.
Okay. Fine.
I love you, Jan.
Okay.
Don't break up, you guys.
You're great together.
Are they gonna call the cops?
No. I paid them off.
Jet ski money?
All of it.
I'm gonna kill Jim Halpert.