Hey, Kevin. Nice of you
to join us. Where were you?
My tire blew out
on the way here, Michael.
I almost died. I went
into this skid... Pop quiz.
What?
Why is today a special day?
I almost died.
Today is a special day
because I am being honored
as a visiting professor.
Special lecturer?
Emeritus, how did you put it?
You will be a guest speaker
in my
Emerging Enterprises class.
In business school, Kevin.
Business school.
Wow.
If you bring
your boss to class,
it automatically bumps you up
a full-letter grade.
So,
I'd be stupid
not to do it, right?
A boss is like a teacher.
And I am like
the cool teacher.
Like Mr. Handell.
Mr. Handell would hang out
with us,
and he would tell us
awesome jokes.
And he actually hooked up
with one of the students,
and then, like,
12 other kids came forward.
It was in all the papers.
Really ruined
eighth grade for us.
Here we go. College road show.
Gotta bring our A game.
What is the most inspiring
thing I ever said to you?
"Don't be an idiot."
Changed my life.
Whenever I'm about
to do something,
I think,
"Would an idiot do that?"
And if they would,
I do not do that thing.
Will they throw their
hats, you think? What?
A lot of times,
at a school or naval academy,
after a rousing speech,
the crowd will throw its hats
high into the air.
You understand, nobody's
graduating. Yeah, I know. I know.
I'm just saying,
if they did throw their hats,
I've got a great line
for that.
May your hats fly
as high your dreams!
That was a pretty good line.
I'm just...
It doesn't apply. I understand!
Wow! Relax, spazzy boy!
Sometimes you're such a
little spaz! God, I'm driving!
Hey!
Quit it.
We have fun!
I can't wait
for your art show tonight.
Okay, just so you know,
it's just the students from
my class in a little studio.
I wouldn't miss it for
the world. Thanks.
I'm really happy
to be back with Roy.
I think it shows maturity,
maturity and dignity.
Is that braggy?
I don't mean it to be braggy.
Love you!
You, too.
Pam's with Roy,
I'm with Karen,
and Brangelina is
with Frangelina. Moving on!
I can't believe
you're back together with Roy.
Oh, yeah. We have such
a solid foundation, you know.
Oh, my God,
you're so in love now.
Yeah. You should come
to my art show, by the way.
Art show!
I mean, it's not a big deal,
but I think a lot of people from
the office are gonna be there.
Yeah. Definitely,
I'll be there. For sure.
Campus. Brings back SO many
memories that I would have made.
Hey, Frisbee! Check that out!
What do you say we get our
frizz on before class? Come on.
Yeah!
Dude!
Oh, my God.
Animal stool.
Dwight, what are you doing?
Solving a mystery, if that's
quite all right with you!
Come to papa!
Okay, ladies and gentlemen.
What we have here is a bird
that has been trapped
in a vent.
Fortunately,
I have found it before...
Bat! Get it out!
Bat! Bat!
Oh, my God!
Bat!
What do you mean...
No, I won't remain calm!
There it goes!
Goodbye.
God, this is Angela Martin.
Please don't let that stupid
thing come anywhere near me.
Please make it go away!
Okay. This is it. Ryan
is doing my intro right now.
Dunder Mifflin can't compete
with the modern chains,
and management is unwilling
or unable to adapt.
Their customers
are dying off...
I can't hear what he's saying,
but he looks like
he's really into it.
We have a bat in the office.
Simple solution would be
to open a window,
if we had windows
that could open.
Poop is raining
from the ceilings.
Poop.
Okay, thanks.
Animal Control
will be here at 6:00.
At 6:007?
No, that is unacceptable.
Okay, Jim. You are the
number two in this office.
You need to step up
and show some leadership!
I'm sorry, what'd you say?
So weird.
What? What's so weird?
The bat... I mean,
I know I felt it bite me,
but look, there's no mark.
I feel so tingly,
so strangely powerful.
Oh, well.
And now, without further ado,
I present the regional manager
of Dunder Mifflin, Scranton,
Michael Scott.
Hello, everyone,
I am Michael Scott...
Hello, I'm Brandon Fidalgo,
CEO of The Teaching Company.
These...
And I'd like to start today
by inspiring you.
May I borrow someone's
textbook, please?
Thank you.
What have we here?
Ooh, economics.
Very, very interesting.
You cannot learn from books.
Replace these pages
with life lessons,
and then you will have a book
that is worth
its weight in gold.
I know, those are expensive,
but the lesson is priceless.
Good.
All right,
I think you're inspired.
Shall we proceed?
There are four kinds
of business,
tourism, food service,
railroads and sales.
And hospitals/manufacturing.
And air travel.
This is your job, Halpert.
Ow!
What happened?
That bread on your desk. I
just picked it up. It's white hot.
But, Jim, this garlic
bread is cold. What?
No, it burned me, I...
Bizarre.
No.
No. One crisis at a time.
If a vampire bat
was in the U.S.,
it would make sense
for it to come
to a "Sylvania,"
like Pennsylvania.
Now, that doesn't mean
that Jim is gonna
become a vampire.
Only that he carries
the vampiric germ.
So, you want to start a
business. How do you start?
What do you need? Well,
first of all, you need a building.
And secondly, you need supply,
you need something to sell.
Now, this could be anything.
It could be a thingamajig
or a who's-he-what's-he
or a Whatchamacallit.
Now, you need to sell those
in order to have a PayDay.
And if you sell
enough of them,
you will make a 100 GRAND.
Satisfied?
This looks great.
I'd love to be there,
but my daughter's play
is tonight.
Damn it!
You know, one of the other
parents will probably videotape it.
So...
Oh, no, you should go.
Well, it's important
to support local art.
You know?
And what they do is not art.
Okay, I'm seeing some
confused faces out there.
Let me slow down a little bit,
break this down.
Okay.
The more stickers you sell,
the more profit,
fancy word for money,
you have to buy PlayStations
and Beanie Babies...
Michael...
...and products!
What we normally do here is
more of a question and answer thing.
Well, okay... I'm just kind
of getting going...
Yeah, I know.
All right, okay.
Well, we can do questions.
Okay, very good. First hand up.
Sir, as a company that
primarily distributes paper,
how have you adapted
your business model
to function in an increasingly
paperless world?
We can't overestimate
the value of computers.
Yes, they are great for playing
games and forwarding funny e-mails,
but real business
is done on paper, okay?
Write that down.
Hey, Jim, here's the aspirin
you wanted.
Oh, thank God. I've such
a headache from that glare.
What glare?
The glare off Angela's
crucifix. It's blinding.
I don't have a lot
of experience with vampires,
but I have hunted werewolves.
I shot one once,
but by the time I got to it,
it had turned back
into my neighbor's dog.
Extraordinary events call
for extraordinary actions.
Will you form an allegiance...
Sure.
...to use sudden violence?
Okay.
Do you have the tools
to turn a wooden mop handle
into a stake?
What size?
What do you say to a customer
who wants to leave you
for the convenience and
savings of a nationwide chain?
I say,
"You will miss our service
"and I absolutely guarantee
you'll come back."
Has anyone ever come back?
We don't want them back.
They're stupid.
How far has your Herfindahl
Index declined since the merger?
Nice try. How's your
Polack-says-what Index?
What?
Thanks, Kowalski.
Can we get back on track here?
By your own
employee's calculation,
you'll be obsolete
in the next five to ten years.
Wait. Ryan said that?
What are you doing?
You better not hurt that little
bat. Animals can't feel pain.
Don't hurt that bat, Creed!
It's a living thing
with feelings and a family!
Flush him towards the door.
On my go! Now!
Bat!
Kill it! Kill it! Kill it!
I am a hero.
Yeah, sure. You know business.
Sitting up here in your ivory
tower and your ebony tower.
Well, you know what?
I tell you one thing,
Dunder Mifflin is here to stay!
But how can you compete
against a company
with the resources
of a nationwide chain?
David will always
beat Goliath!
But there's five Goliaths.
There's Staples, OfficeMax...
Yeah, yeah.
You know what else
is facing five Goliaths?
America. Al-Qaeda.
Global warming. Sex predators.
Mercury poisoning.
So do we just give up?
Is that what we're
learning in business school?
But in the big picture,
you have...
Dunder Mifflin
is the big picture!
Can't you understand that?
No, you can't, you're {00 young.
Ryan has never made a sale.
And he started a fire,
trying to make a cheesy pita.
And everybody thinks he's a
tease. Well, you know what?
He doesn't know anything
and neither do you.
So, suck on that!
It wasn't personal.
Business is always personal.
It's the most personal thing
in the world.
When we get back to the
office, pack your things.
Pack my... You heard
me. Pack your things.
I really want to come out!
Good night, Mary Beth!
So, you're cool to just wait
here for Animal Control?
Animal Control?
I've been controlling animals
since I was six.
Cool. Okay.
I'm gonna go home and
lie down, draw the shades.
There's just
so much sun in here.
Bye, Dwight.
Goodbye, Jim.
And good luck.
Jim is on a path now,
an eternal journey,
and I wish him well.
But I have a destiny
in this realm.
Specifically, in the kitchen.
And it's all
from the same series.
Called Impressions.
Not that I would call myself
an impressionist per se.
But maybe one day.
I hope so.
I still need, you know,
my breakthrough or whatever.
- Hey, babe.
- Hey!
How are you?
Good.
I brought my brother.
Hey, Kenny.
Hey, Pam.
Hey.
How about this, huh?
I show up with my brother
and no one from work is here.
That's pretty cool, huh?
Magic time.
My hair!
Get off! Get off me!
Get it off me! Get off me!
Hold still, woman!
Get it off!
I got it! I got it!
You're welcome.
It's cool if I go, right? I
mean, I looked at all of them.
Yeah. I'll just...
I'll drive myself home.
To my place?
Maybe. I'm a little tired.
Your art was the
prettiest art of all the art.
Thank you.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I was just trying
to do my presentation.
And, of course I was wrong
to suggest that Dunder Mifflin
might ever go out of business.
But you don't have to fire me.
Fire you? No, no, no.
You are moving to the annex.
To the annex?
Where Kelly is?
A good manager
doesn't fire people.
He hires people
and inspires people.
People, Ryan.
And people will never go
out of business.
You're the one who said
we needed more culture.
This is culture to you?
It's her first try.
Yeah. On Van Gogh's
first try,
he drew the hands
of the peasants.
Meaning what?
Meaning real art takes
courage, okay, and honesty.
Well, those aren't
Pam'sstrong points.
Yeah, exactly.
That's why this is motel art.
Thanks for coming.
Pamcasso!
Sorry I'm late. I had to race
across town. Oh, Michael.
Wow!
You did these? Freehand?
Yep.
My God,
these could be tracings.
Look at this one. Wow!
You nailed it.
How much?
What do you mean?
I don't see a price.
You want to buy it?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, we have to have it
for the office.
I mean, there's my window.
And there's my car!
Is that your car?
That is our building.
And we sell paper.
I am really proud of you.
Thank you.
What?
Do you have something
in your pocket?
A Chunky.
Do you want half?
No, thank you.
Okay.
It is a message.
It is an inspiration.
It is a source of beauty.
And without paper,
it could not have happened.
Unless you had a camera.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh,
my God! It's only temporary, okay?
Don't get excited.
I won't. I won't. I won't.
I won't. I won't! I won't!
I won't! I won't! I won't!
I won't! I won't!