David...
Oh, Michael...
Are we all set?
Isn't our interview tomorrow?
Yes. I just happened to be
in the neighborhood.
Thought I'd drop in
and say hello.
Just happened to be
in midtown Manhattan?
Thought I'd catch a show.
In the middle of a workday?
No.
You know what, since I'm here,
let me ask you a few questions
about the job.
Okay. How many people
are you interviewing?
We're only interviewing
branch managers
and some lower-level
company people.
Ah, well, good.
Out of curiosity,
are you interviewing anyone
who has been here
longer than I have
or manages more people?
I don't think so.
Great. One more question.
When you merged those
branches, who did you put in charge?
I believe
we put you in charge.
Ah, great.
No further questions.
Okay, Michael.
Okay.
I'm really looking forward
to our interview.
And I'm really looking forward
to working with you.
I have got it made in the
shade. I know this company.
The other branch managers are
total morons.
Hey, Pam, yeah, I forgot
what day the interview was.
I drove
to New York accidentally.
Be, like, three hours late.
See, I have 600...
Yeah, I don't have... Hey.
Hey, Kev.
What's different about you?
You look worse.
Thank you.
You got a haircut.
It's sexy hot.
Turn around.
Oh.
Come on.
No.
No, thanks.
Do it!
Look at that do!
What's up, Big Haircut?
You are no longer Big Tuna.
From henceforth,
you shall be known
as Big Haircut.
Andy.
What is it, Big Haircut?
No. Sorry, I can't
hear you, Big Haircut.
Yep.
What?
Karen suggested that I get a
haircut for the interview tomorrow,
so that I could look
presentable and not,
as she so lovingly
puts it, homeless.
Hey. I think it looks great.
Thanks, Pam.
After I had my little outburst
at the beach,
Jim was really nice about it.
He just basically said
that he missed
my friendship, too,
and I would always
mean a lot to him.
And I understand
where he's coming from.
For the record,
I am not embarrassed at all.
It needed to be said
and I said it
and it only took me
three years
to summon the courage.
So, thank you.
Yeah?
You wanted to see me?
Yes.
The time has come
to name my own replacement.
So...
Please hand this letter
of congratulations
to Dwight K. Schrute.
But that's my name.
"Dwight,
congratulations, a-wipe."
"Don't screw the pooch."
Thank you.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you, Michael.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Hey, stop crying.
Thank you.
Hey.
About the beach...
It's okay.
We all say things
without thinking.
Oh, no. It's not that.
I've actually been thinking
that for a long time
and I'm glad I said it.
I just am sorry
if it made you feel weird.
Oh. Okay.
Pam is kind of a bitch.
Hey, what if we leave tonight?
Grab a bite, get a hotel room,
enjoy the city a little bit?
I just have
so much paperwork to do.
Wow. Done. Okay, let's do it.
So I was wondering if Karen
and I could get off a few hours early
because we wanted to
spend the night in the city.
Why, so you can do it?
Whoops.
No, well,
I was thinking that, actually,
we can all leave tomorrow
and do a convoy, you know?
Convoys are really fun.
Pull up next to each other,
give each other the finger.
Moon each other.
We're going to go tonight,
but we're going to see you
there tomorrow morning, right?
All right.
All right. Your loss.
Wait, how would you moon us
if you were driving?
Cruise control.
So, Jim, who do you think
is hotter, Pam or Karen?
Yeah, I'm not going to talk
about this now. Pam is taller.
You sure?
Yes.
She has bigger breasts, too.
Wow.
But I think Karen
has a prettier face.
What else?
Well, I mean, Pam's face
is really pretty, too.
It's a very tough call.
Really tough call.
Yeah.
You know what, why don't
you take the rest of the day
and figure it out
and then come back
and tell me what you've got.
Will do.
All right.
Yes.
Hey, Pam,
I've been meaning to say something
to you. I really miss our friendship.
That's very funny. I've never
heard you talk that much.
I thought it was Kelly.
Are you kidding?
I would never have done that.
It was Patheticville.
no offense, Pam.
You know what,
don't even worry about it.
Everyone was so drunk, I bet no
one even remembers what you said.
I remember.
I blogged the whole thing.
www.creedthoughts.gov.
www/creedthoughts.
Check it out.
Last year, Creed asked me
how to set up a blog.
Wanting to protect the world from
being exposed to Creed's brain,
I opened up a Word document
on his computer
and put an address at the top.
I've read some of it.
Even for the Internet,
it's pretty shocking.
There they are,
the accounting department.
I shall miss your humility and
your promptly printed checks.
Do you think
it's going to be weird
working with Jan in New York?
No. Not at all. I haven't talked
to Jan since we broke up.
And I think if she had something
to say, she would have called me.
Maybe you should talk to
her before... No, no, no, no.
You know what,
it's a done deal.
I basically
have the job already.
There's nothing she can do to
stop it now. I already sold my condo.
- Michael.
- What?
Why? I'm sorry
that just doesn't make sense.
Yes. Why... Who
gave you that advice?
Yeah, Michael,
you should never...
...sell your condo.
I have to buy another place.
But you said
you were in debt.
I'm not. You're not sure
that you have the job.
I sold it on eBay. The buyer
was very motivated as was I.
It went for 80%
of what I paid.
Sold in record time.
How would you like
to spend the night
with the regional manager
of Dunder Mifflin, Scranton?
No, Dwight,
I don't care if that's
how they consolidated power
in ancient Rome, I'm...
No, no. Not Michael.
Me. I'm taking his job.
Not now.
Goodbye, Kelly Kapour.
Jim, Jim, Jim.
Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim.
Oh, hey, Dwight.
I am going to be
your new boss.
It is my greatest dream
come true.
Welcome to the Hotel Hell.
Check-in time is now.
Checkout time is never.
Does my room have cable?
And the sheets are made
of fire. Can I change rooms?
Sorry, we're all booked up.
Hell convention in town.
Can I have a late checkout?
I'll have to talk to the manager.
You're not the manager?
Even in your own fantasy?
I'm the owner.
The co-owner. With Satan.
Okay.
Just so I understand it,
in your wildest fantasy,
you are in Hell
and you are co-running
a bed and breakfast
with the Devil.
Yeah, but I haven't told
you my salary yet. Go.
$80,000 a year.
Once I am officially
regional manager,
my first order of business
will be to demote Jim Halpert.
So I will need
a new number two.
My ideal choice?
Jack Bauer.
But he is unavailable,
fictional, and overqualified.
I will see you
at the interview.
Yes, you will.
Who is D. Abramson?
He's from that company
in Pittsburgh. Michael.
Why are you here?
How are you?
I'm good. How are you, Janet?
I'm... I'm great.
It's good to see you.
Can we... Can we talk
privately for a minute?
Why privately?
I just... I don't...
I don't like the way
that we left things.
Okay, sure. Fine. Why
don't you wait in my office?
I have some important
business matters to take care of.
Okay.
Pam, DEFCON 10.
Houston, we have a problem.
What do you want me to do?
I may need some
immediate assistance.
If you would slowly and quietly gather
the ladies in the conference room,
Phyllis, Angela, Karen.
What about Meredith?
She's an alternate.
So, how you been?
I'm good.
Good. Good.
Good.
Yeah.
Sorry to drop by
unexpectedly. I...
I tried calling, but I kept
getting voicemail. Weird.
Yeah. I didn't get
both of your messages.
So, Michael needs us
in the conference room.
Oh, is it Jan again?
Hey, before I leave tonight,
would you mind making half a dozen
copies of Jim's and my sales reports
for our interviews tomorrow?
Sure.
Thanks.
I really hope you get the job.
After you ended everything
with us, I went on a vacation
to kind of clear my mind.
Sounds good. Sounds fun.
It was. Yeah, it was good.
I think I should just...
Get right to the
point, you know. Okay.
I... I feel good
about myself
for the first time
in a really long time,
and I've made some
big changes in my life,
and I miss you.
I want us
to get back together.
Would you excuse
me for a second? Oh.
DEFCON 20.
She wants to get back together.
What are you going to do?
I don't know. hat's why
you're here. Help me. Please.
Would you want to
get back together with her?
No. No.
What do I do? Just don't
get back together with her.
What if she makes me?
How can she make you
get back together with her?
She made me do a lot of things
I didn't want to do.
This was
a terrible relationship.
You were not happy
when you were with her.
I wasn't.
You're so much happier now.
Just go in there and
be strong. You're right.
You are absolutely right.
I need to go in there and tell
her that we can't be together.
Right.
Wow.
Do it.
I'm in a very good
place right now.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Go.
Okay. Jan,
we need to talk.
Jan is in
a different place right now.
And it is a sign of maturity
to give people second chances.
So I'm going to hear her out.
Oh, my God.
Yeah. Bigger actually.
That's crazy.
Oh, my God. Can you
believe that? Unbelievable.
Wow! She could put
the cup right there.
I know.
No, it's fine.
I'm sure it must have been
weird for Jim
when Roy and I
were joking around
that one time.
I would
never do that.
Waste of money.
In my experience,
guys are way more attracted to
the back of you than to the front.
I love fake boobs.
Oftentimes you find them
on strippers.
I find it offensive.
Au naturel, baby.
That's how I like them.
Swing low, sweet chariots.
So, there are a lot of things
I would like to do differently.
Yeah. I feel like when
we first got together,
that I had a problem
with my priorities.
First stop, priorities.
And if we could talk about a way to
approach a possible reconciliation.
Let's get back together.
No. No, no, no.
I'll tell you this,
it is not because
of the boob job.
Excuse me, boob enhancement.
That would be shallow. And
this is the opposite of shallow.
This is
emotionally magnificent.
Okay, everyone, listen up!
Time to begin
the interview process.
Andrew Bernard.
Save the best for first.
All right, you guys,
see you later. Wish us luck.
No. Hey, hey,
do not wish them luck.
Do not wish them luck. All luck
must be wished unto Michael.
Good luck, you guys.
Good luck.
What did I say?
Thanks.
I'm happy for him.
I hope he gets the job.
I really just want him
to be happy.
And I know that sounds cliche,
and I know saying it
sounds cliche sounds cliche.
Maybe I'm being cliche. I don't
care because I am what I am.
That's Popeye.
I am going to
begin this process
with a simple test of
intelligence and mental dexterity.
What is the best color?
White.
Because it contains
all other colors.
Wrong. Black.
It is the most dominant.
How do you make a table?
You make a chair,
but you don't sit on it.
What is the capital of Maine?
The capital of Maine
is Montpelier, Vermont,
which is near Ithaca, New York
where I went to Cornell.
Okay, also,
moratorium on Cornell talk.
Don't want to hear about it.
Forget your personal history and
learn the history of this company.
Should not be a problem.
I minored in history
in the Ivy League school
which I attended.
You're not off to a very
good start, Bernard. I agree.
But in another way,
I am off to a very good start,
wouldn't you say?
I am a great interviewee. Why?
Because I have something
no one else has, my brain,
which I use to my advantage
when advantageous.
Time! No, you failed.
Damn it!
This interview is over.
I'll let you know.
Hey, thank you so much for
driving me down for my interview.
Totally. No problem.
What are you interviewing for,
by the way?
My assistant? Or...
Oh, you know, I'm going to
have a congratulations Karen party
tomorrow night at a friend's
house. Oh, wow. That sounds fun.
Is your friend named Karen,
too? What did she accomplish?
No. I'm sorry, I should
have been clearer. It's for me.
Because I'm going
to get the job. Oh.
How remarkable.
Thanks.
Wait, wait a second.
Let me check one more thing.
Okay.
Very good.
All right, well,
I have to get back.
But I will see you
in New York tomorrow, right?
Yes, indeed.
Good luck with your interview.
Thank you.
Bye.
So I guess we're getting
back together. What happened?
Your advice was good,
but Jan's was bigger.
Here's the sitch.
Two weeks ago, I was in the
worst relationship of my life.
She treated me poorly, we
didn't connect, I was miserable.
Now, I'm in the best relationship
of my life with the same woman.
Love is a mystery.
So, we have all night.
Where do you want to go first?
I don't know.
How about the UN?
How often do you come here?
Every time my sixth grade
class was on a field trip.
I think you're really going to
enjoy this, adult Jim.
Hey, everybody,
the next time you see me I
will be working for corporate.
Starting tomorrow, Dwight
Schrute will be running the branch.
So without further ado,
I would like to start
saying my goodbyes.
For everything
you've done
You know I'm bound
Okay.
I'm bound
to thank you for it...
Good night
and good luck.
Who's ready to work?
Yeah. We went
to the Spotted Pig for dinner.
It's in the Village.
Karen knew it.
And then we
second acted Spamalot.
That's when you sneak in at
intermission with all the smokers.
And then we went to a bar
that used to be a church.
Oh, and at this one bar,
I swear I saw Lorne Michaels.
That wasn't him.
So what's going to happen
with us when I get this job?
Oh, you mean,
when I get the job?
Well, if you get the job,
then I'd move here with you.
Would you move with me?
I'm not stupid, okay?
I was at the beach.
We don't have a future
in Scranton.
There's one too many
people there.
You mean, Kevin?
Exactly.
No, but you get it, right?
I can't stay there.
Yeah. I do.
Come on.
How are you guys doing?
Need anything?
No. We're good. Thanks.
I have been here a bunch of
times, so I know where everything is.
Know everybody's names.
If you need to know
somebody's name, just ask me.
Well, who's that?
That is Beardy.
Beardy?
I'm going to introduce myself.
No, no. That's not his real name.
That's just
what I call him. So...
I am by far the most qualified
person they're interviewing.
Jim and Karen are here,
which is cute.
They're like kid actors tagging
along with Daddy on the big audition,
hoping to be discovered, except
Daddy is the best actor around.
Daddy is Meryl Streep.
Michael is gone.
Hail to the chief.
My first order of business,
make Andrew Bernard
my number two.
My first order
of business, accept.
As if you have a choice. Duh.
Opportunity of a lifetime.
Three months ago,
I was nowhere.
I was just a Cornell grad
in anger management.
Look where I am now.
Not bad.
Hey, Hunter.
What's up, my brother?
This is Hunter,
secretary extraordinaire.
Administrative assistant.
Jan in yet?
I think she's coming in later.
Could you give her a message
for me when she gets in?
Sure.
Just say I want to
squeeze them.
It's code. She'll know
what it means. Okay.
Oh, Hunter,
could you tell her...also?
You showed great leadership
potential at the coal walk,
even if you did follow it with that
embarrassing personal confession.
Thank you.
I had to make Andy my number
two. It's political, complicated.
You wouldn't understand.
I want you to be
assistant regional manager.
Really?
Well, in a sense.
Although, publicly,
I am going to retain the assistant
regional manager position.
You will be
your own assistant.
Correct. I need
someone I can trust.
But I would also like the title
to be secretly applied to you.
Just stripped off its
pomp and frills. Okay.
So you would be
the regional manager
and the assistant
regional manager,
Andy is your number two.
I would be the secret
assistant regional manager.
Let's call it secret assistant
to the regional manager.
Do you accept?
Absolutely I do.
I learned from Jim,
if Dwight ever asks you if
you accept something secret,
you reply, "Absolutely I do."
Hello, hello!
Michael, good to see you.
Good to see you.
Have a seat.
Here are the post-merger
performance tests that you asked for.
Great.
I've been meaning
to thank you, by the way.
You didn't lose a single
customer in the merger
and you still managed to trim
the budget. That is nice work.
So, let me ask you a question
right off the bat,
what do you think are your
greatest strengths as a manager?
Why don't I tell you what
my greatest weaknesses are?
I work too hard,
I care too much,
and sometimes I can be
too invested in my job.
Okay. And your strengths?
Well, my weaknesses
are actually strengths.
Oh. Yes. Very good.
There you go.
Very good.
Dwight is our new boss. No,
Michael's not going anywhere.
Then who do you think
will get the job? Karen.
She looks corporate.
Those little pantsuits.
I think
it's going to be Michael.
Do you really think
he's qualified for that job?
No, but he wasn't qualified for the
job he has now and he got that one.
Yeah.
Listen up. Come to the
center of the room, please.
This is a Schrute Buck.
When you have done
something good,
you will receive
one Schrute Buck.
One thousand Schrute Bucks
equals an extra five minutes for lunch.
What is the cash value
of a Schrute Buck?
Excellent question, Pam.
One one-hundredth of a cent.
So, 10,000
of your dollars is worth
one real dollar? Just...
Zip your lid.
Another announcement.
Michael wasted
an enormous amount
of the group's time
and patience
with non-work-related
ethnic celebrations
and parades of soft-minded
do-goodedness.
No longer.
No more meetings.
Amen.
Instead, today, I will begin my first
lecture in a long series of lectures
designed to increase your
knowledge on the world of paper.
Do we have to?
Yes. Michael is gone.
There's a new sheriff here in
these offices and his name is me.
Conference room,
10 seconds. All of you!
I literally cannot wait until I
see what Dwight has planned.
And I wish Jim were here.
What do you think
we can be doing better?
I've never been a big fan
of the name Dunder Mifflin.
I was thinking we could name
the company something like
Paper Great
or Great Paper's Our Passion.
We're great.
I don't know.
It could be good.
Or Super Duper Paper.
It's super duper.
I don't know.
Something like that.
Okay.
Thanks for coming in, Michael.
Thank you.
It is always a treat
when our paths cross.
So, oh, before I forget,
I wanted to let you know,
if you hadn't already heard,
Jan and I are back together.
So I may need to fill out
one of those
love documents again.
You're back together.
Yes.
And I am very excited about
the prospect of working under her.
Or on top of her.
That's not sexual. Just...
We're all professionals.
Okay.
Well, I thought it was clear in
the description of the position.
The job you're applying
for is Jan's job.
I don't understand.
So we're going to tag-team it?
No. We're letting Jan go.
Listen up.
Let's start
from the ground up.
Where does paper come from?
- Trees.
And where do trees grow?
Forests.
Soil.
Right.
We have in front of you here
seven different types
of Pennsylvania topsoil.
Now, what would you say is
the most important element
in the production
of aboveground leafy growth?
Probably phosphorus,
right? Wrong.
It's nitrogen.
Absorb this information.
Good. Now,
let us discuss precipitation.
Stanley, when rainfall occurs,
does it usually fall
in a liquid, solid,
or gaseous state?
Liquid.
Very good.
You have earned one
Schrute Buck. I don't want it.
Then you have been deducted
50 Schrute Bucks.
Make it 100.
Well...
Don't you want to earn
Schrute Bucks? No.
In fact, I'll give you a billion Stanley
Nickels if you never talk to me again.
What's the ratio of Stanley
Nickels to Schrute Bucks?
The same as the ratio
of unicorns to leprechauns.
Okay. That's it! Class is
canceled. Everybody out!
No, wait, what are you doing?
I'm punishing them.
No, no, no, no.
Class is not canceled.
This is so stupid.
Hey! Come on!
Let's listen
to Dwight's presentation.
What... What are you
winking for? Zip your lid!
So that's my basic five-year plan
and then after that who knows?
Okay.
Now, this may seem like
an odd question. Yeah?
What do you think
about Michael Scott?
He's a very nice man.
And he's very well-suited
for the job he has now.
This is off the record.
He would be a disaster.
Hey, you.
How was your interview?
Pretty good.
Yeah? Could have
gone better, I guess.
Oh. Well, I will put in a
good word for you. Cool.
Maybe you should do it sooner
rather than later.
What?
Let's just run away together.
Let's just run away to
Jamaica, live in a bungalow.
You have some savings, right? You
can pay off my debts. It would be fine.
We'd have fun. What's...
What's the matter? What...
What happened in there?
I can't tell you.
Tell me what?
You son of a bitch.
Jan, this isn't the time. I'm in
an interview... You're firing me?
Where the hell do you get off?
Frankly, it's overdue.
Your behavior in the last two
years has been completely erratic.
Erratic?
Recently you don't even show
an interest in your work.
You smoke constantly
in your office,
you spend most of the day
online shopping.
You disappear for hours
at a time, sometimes days,
always saying you're visiting
your sister in Scottsdale.
You go to Scranton
far more often than you...
Is it because of these?
Whoa, hey, whoa, Jan. Come on. Is
it... No, I want to know! I want to know!
Because if it is, then...
Then I will see you in court.
It's not. It's not.
Because he likes them, okay?
He likes them. And that is...
That is all I care about.
The time has come for you to
end your professional relationship
with this company.
You are clearly unstable.
Hey, you're unstable.
Yeah.
- We're all unstable.
- Okay, do you know what?
I'm just not leaving. I'm
not leaving. I'm not leaving.
David, I did not tell her.
It's like I'm staring into my
soul when I look at this wall.
It's like outer spac
without the stars.
It's so black. This is
going to look SO awesome.
It's so intimidating.
Anyone who come in here is
going to have to take me seriously.
Abandon all hope ye
who enter here.
Totally!
Bye, Hunter.
Bye.
Good luck with your band.
Oh, thank you... Don't let
them change you, okay?
So long...
So I am going to
give her a ride home.
Let me know about the job.
Actually, Michael,
I think we're going
to take it
in another direction.
Good. I'm glad we're
on the same page.
I have a lot of ideas
for new directions.
No, we're not
giving you the job.
You know what?
That is actually good
because I don't think I
could take my girlfriend's job.
That's not being
a good boyfriend.
So I respectfully withdraw
my name from consideration.
Do you accept my withdrawal?
I do.
Good. Very good. I'm glad
we are finally on the same page.
Still have my job
in Scranton, though?
Yes.
Good.
That's all I ever wanted.
These two, either one of them,
excellent candidates.
Wow.
That was some serious,
hardcore self-destruction.
Yeah.
I kind of feel bad
for her, though.
Don't. She's nuts.
Oh, man.
You know what,
this might take a while.
You really don't have to stay
if you don't want.
Okay, good because a bunch of my
friends are meeting downtown for lunch
and I was going to
meet them. So... All right.
Just call me when you're done.
Sure.
Good luck, Halpert.
Thank you.
Dunder Mifflin,
this is Grace. Sure.
Oh, God.
I mean
I just don't understand.
It's just so rude, you know.
I know. I know.
I mean, the absolute
nerve of that guy.
I am sorry about that.
That was terrible. Oh, just...
No, actually,
I think it's good.
You know, it's fine,
actually. I do.
I really think it's great
that it happened because,
you know, my work
has always been the thing
that's gotten in the way
of my happiness. So...
Yeah.
Well, it's...
No, don't cry.
It's going to be okay. Oh, I
know. I know. It's just... I'm sorry.
It's just these painkillers that I
started taking since the surgery.
Oh, they make my moods
totally unpredictable. Wow.
What am I going to do?
I don't know.
Well, I guess you could come
and stay at my condo.
I think I could back
out of the sale.
I would probably get
some negative feedback
on my eBay profile, but...
Live together. Actually, wait
a minute, this could be great.
This could be perfect.
You know, my full-time
job can be our relationship.
I can wear stretch pants and
wait for you to come home at 5:15.
It could work.
This could work, really.
I'll be back.
And I am back.
How did it go?
No, no, Pam.
I'm back
for good.
Kevin Nealon.
Everybody, may I have
your attention please?
It is with great honor
and privilege
that I announce to you,
I have officially
withdrawn my name
for consideration
from the corporate job.
I know, I know, I know.
Michael, what are you thinking?
You were a shoo-in. Well...
I got down there,
I nailed the interview
and the strangest
thing happened.
Why is my office black?
To intimidate my subordinates.
That's stupid.
It was Andy's idea.
You shouldn't have taken it.
Bad management.
Good thing I'm back.
Ryan, coffee.
I don't do that stuff anymore.
No. It's for me, bimbo.
Kids.
So I'm back
and I am never, ever,
going to leave.
I am going nowhere.
This place is like
the hospital where I was born,
my house,
my old age home
and my graveyard for my bones.
Did Karen get the job?
Back to work.
Still waiting on that coffee.
Pam, hello.
Dwight, hello.
I wanted to thank you
for helping me
when you held the title
of secret assistant
to the regional manager.
You served the office
with great dignity.
No, I don't know
what the future holds.
But I'm optimistic
and I had fun goofing around
with Dwight today.
Jim and I
are just too similar.
Maybe one day
I'll find my own Karen.
But, you... That is a...
You know, not...
A man. A man version.
But until then,
I can hold my head up.
I'm not gay.
I don't know how I feel
about hiring a Sixers fan.
I should leave.
Now, let me ask you
a question, Jim.
You're clearly
a very bright guy.
Thanks. Always hit your
numbers, personable.
You make a great impression
on everyone you meet.
I'm sorry, wait.
So is the question,
how did I get
to be so awesome?
Because I don't have
an answer for you.
Oh, hey, do you have
your quarterly numbers...
Yes. Absolutely.
...and questionnaire?
Sorry to make you fill that
thing out. Oh, no. Absolutely.
It's just a HR formality.
We have this
very irritating HR guy here.
He's probably the only person
you're not going to like.
Kendall.
So, first up.
There you go.
How do you think you'd
function here in New York?
What's that? Oh, great.
You know I just...
I really appreciate
the buildings
and the people, and there's
just an energy that New York has.
Not to mention
they have places
that are open past 8:00,
so that's a bonus.
You've been in the
Scranton branch a long time.
What have you liked most
about that place?
The friendships.
Okay.
Well, we want the person
who takes this position
to be here for the long haul.
So, long haul, where do
you see yourself in 10 years?
How are your feet?
Medium rare. Thanks.
The real reason that I went to
Stamford was because I wanted to be...
Not here.
I know.
And even though I came back,
I just feel like
I've never really come back.
Well, I wish you would.
Dunder Mifflin. This is Pam.
Just one moment.
I'll transfer you.
I haven't heard anything.
But I bet Jim got the job.
I mean, why wouldn't he?
He's totally qualified and smart.
Everyone loves him.
And if he never comes
back again,
that's okay.
We're friends. And I'm sure
we'll stay friends.
We just... We never
got the timing right.
You know, [ shot him down
and then he did
the same to me and...
But you know what, it's okay.
I'm totally fine.
Everything is going
to be totally... Pam.
Sorry.
Are you free
for dinner tonight?
Yes.
All right. Then it's a date.
I'm sorry.
What was the question?
So I know we left the other
day on a note of uncertainty,
but after some more thought,
I'm very pleased to be able
to offer you this job.
Great.
I'm so glad. We're all very
excited you're going to be joining us.
It'll be nice to have
another MBA around here.
I'm excited, too. Okay.
Who was that?
Nobody.
You and I are done.
What?