Hello, this is Dwight Schrute.
Hello?
Hello. This is Dwight.
Yes!
Hello? Hello?
We do have that.
Hold on one second.
Jim, what are you doing?
And how many would you like?
Hang that up right now.
Absolutely. I can get that
out to you immediately.
This man is an imposter.
Do not do business with him.
This is not Dwight Schrute.
Dwight left his cell phone on his desk,
so, naturally, I paired it to my headset.
Okay, fine, I'll just let
it go to voicemail.
Hello, this is Dwight.
Hey, is this Dwight?
Yes, it is.
Oh, my goodness,
you sound sexy.
Oh, thank you.
I've been working out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Pam! Pam!
You are not talking to Dwight right now!
You are talking to Jim.
Dwight?
No! Pam, I'm over here!
I'm confused.
Disconnect that right now.
You give me
your earpiece.
Can't do that.
Unsanitary.
Okay, you know what?
Fine.
I will reprogram my phone
to go to my office phone.
Done.
This is Dwight.
Oh, and I forwarded his
desk phone to mine.
Oh, hello, Mother.
Good news, I have married.
Tell Father.
Such a nice woman.
Today is
Toby Flenderson's last day.
I couldn't sleep last night.
I came in extra early.
So much energy.
There are certain days that you know you
will remember for the rest of your life,
and I just have a feeling that
today is one of those days.
Morning.
So here we go.
Just a matter of hours now
until his horrible-ness
has left the building.
I'm going to set
my watch alarm,
and...
Good morning, Kelly.
I can't believe this is your
last day. How do you feel?
Fine. Good.
I feel weird.
First thing on the agenda, actually,
the only thing on the agenda,
is the status of Toby's
going-away party.
We have a butter-cream cake
and a slide show of Toby.
Okay.
But so far we only have
two pictures of him.
Okay.
Well, this will not do.
Toby is going away forever,
and we need to do something
very, very special.
In some cultures,
when somebody leaves,
like New Orleans' culture,
they have a parade,
and they have a band, and
people party in the streets.
Do you mean leaves
as in dies?
You want us to throw Toby
a New Orleans funeral?
If the devil were to explode,
and evil were gone forever,
what sort of party
would you have?
Michael...
Like a beach blowout,
or a toga, a toga.
No, you know, no.
Toga!
You always do this.
We have a nice, modest party planned,
and then you come in and demand the world.
Let me be clear, there is simply no
money for anything other than a cake
and to develop
a few more slides,
although Toby
won't be in them.
I thought that you
might say that.
Every year, my sweet, sweet grandmother
sends me a check on my birthday for $50.
And lately, she has been sending
me, like, nine or ten checks a year.
As Nana starts to...
But I knew I should be
saving it for something.
I just didn't know what
I should be saving it for.
And then I had an awakening.
Michael, my motorcycle.
So I put the money in my shoe,
and then I forgot about it until now.
I want a party that makes me
feel like I'm flying through the air,
without this ugly weight
holding me down, you know?
I want an anti-gravity
machine. I saw it in a movie.
You drink a potion, and then
you just start floating all around.
So how much anti-gravity
potion do you want?
No. No, you know what? This is not
a Party Planning Committee anymore.
And I don't want your foot money,
and I feel uncomfortable participating.
Phyllis, can you do this?
Yes.
Hi. Can I help you?
Hi. Yes. I'm Holly Flax.
I was told to ask
for Mr. Flenderson.
As part of my last day,
I am training
the new human resources rep
in the ways of the company.
Again, the company has
allotted for this training one day.
So this is HR.
This is your desk.
I love the view.
Yeah. It's great. Isn't it?
Hey.
What?
Guess who just got into
the Pratt School of Design.
No way!
What did I say? I said that
they'd love those sketches!
Congratulations!
Oh, thank you.
I don't know why I doubted it,
because I'm so clearly awesome.
Yes. So,
when do you start?
I don't know.
I didn't read it carefully.
I just saw "Congratulations," and
I skimmed the list, I saw my name,
I came in here to tell
you and get a snack.
Wow. Busy morning.
So, you know, it means I have to
go to New York for three months.
It's not a big deal. I'll come
visit you, and you'll visit me.
It's only two hours
away. It'll be fine.
That part's going to suck,
but it'll be great.
Yeah. It sucks,
See how easy that is?
I wouldn't go if things
weren't so solid with Jim.
And down the road,
if we have a family,
I couldn't go then either,
so the timing's perfect.
And that is the first time I've
ever used the word perfect in here.
Hey, Stanley,
I want to introduce you...
Real good.
Toby's replacement.
Wow.
So what do we
know about her?
Well, we know that Toby
thinks she'll be great.
Now, strike one.
I hate her already.
I hate her, too.
Why do you hate her?
Because she stinks
with her ways and her head.
You know, Dwight, sometimes,
I don't know, I think you say
things just to agree with me.
Would that be
such a bad thing?
Yeah, it would.
Just have a thought.
Have an original thought.
Although, I will agree
that her head is weird.
You know what we need to do?
What?
We need to sell her
an elevator pass.
But our elevator
doesn't require a...
Exactly. Little
old-fashioned hazing.
Hi. Are there any local companies
that rent anti-gravity machines?
Anti-gravity machines?
That's right. Yeah.
What do they do exactly?
They make you feel lighter.
Anti-gravity...
Um...
Anti-depressant? I could put
you through to someone on that.
Okay.
Yeah?
Hey, Michael?
Oh, hey, do you
still work here?
I'd like to introduce you
to my replacement. Nah.
Come on.
No, I think I will pass.
Michael Scott, this is Holly.
Hi. Yeah, right.
Hi.
Okay, well, they hired a
female Toby. Good for the world.
Thank you, God,
for creating two of you.
Here's how things work here.
My job is to make the office fun.
Your job is to make the office lame,
and we have an eternal struggle, you and I,
and only one of us
can be the winner.
Spoiler alert,
I'm going to win.
Man, someone
doesn't like HR.
Yeah.
What did you do to him?
Nothing.
No, he tortured me
with his awfulness.
Yeah, I know
what you mean.
I nearly fell asleep when
he gave me a tour of the files.
Well, look, I'll let
you get back to work,
but I really look forward to
working with you, Mr. Scott.
You can... Michael.
Thanks to Toby, I have a very
strong prejudice against human resources.
I believe that the department is
a breeding ground for monsters.
What I failed to consider, though,
is that not all monsters are bad.
Like E.T.
Is Holly our
extraterrestrial? Maybe.
Or maybe she's just an awesome
woman from this planet.
The pleasure's all mine.
Thanks.
I'm really looking forward
to sitting down with you
and finding out more
about what you do here.
Any time,
Yeah. What do you do here?
Excuse me.
What is wrong with this woman?
She's asking about stuff
that's nobody's business.
What do I do?
Really, what do I do here?
I should have written it down.
Qua-something.
Qua... Quar...
Qua... Qual... Quar...
Quabity. Quabity assuance.
No, no, no, no,
but I'm getting close.
Have you been
introduced to Kevin?
No. Which one's Kevin?
He's here on a special work program.
He's slow, you know, in his brain.
Oh, good for you guys.
Yeah.
Hazing is a fun way to show a new
employee that she is not welcome or liked.
Accounting department, listen
up. Holly, human resources.
Angela, Oscar and Kevin.
Hello. Hello.
Hi.
What do you do?
I do the numbers.
Oh, good for you.
Do you want an M&M?
Oh, no. That is so sweet.
Thank you, though.
Yeah. I keep them here at my desk,
so that everybody doesn't take them.
Well, that is a very
safe place for them.
Yeah.
Here she is, Holly.
You know, if we hung
Holly from the ceiling,
we'd have to kiss
underneath her.
So, I know. Oh, sorry.
Question, are you real,
or are you a Holly-gram?
Nice. I've never heard
that one before, actually.
That's good.
I bet.
Are these guys
boring your ears off?
Oh, no, no, I...
What is your commute like?
How long does it take to get in?
Oh, uh... You know, I
should make you a mix.
Do you have a CD player?
Um... Yeah. Okay.
All right.
Thanks.
Great.
Do you like it?
It's a photo of everyone in the
office, so you can take it to Costa Rica.
You're not in it.
Well, I was taking
the picture.
I love it. I love it.
I would love a picture of the two
of us to also take to Costa Rica.
Sure. Do you have
a camera here?
Uh...
Does anyone have
a camera here?
No one has a camera here.
Okay.
I'm going...
I'll go get one. I'll just...
So I just got the fax.
Closing the sale, and it's big.
It is really big.
Congratulations.
Thanks...
Don't interrupt.
Congratulations on doing your job.
Did you enter the sale on the Web site?
Nope, I didn't.
I just logged it in...
All right, try to be
a team player here, Jim.
Log it in the Web site.
All right, well, it already
went through, so...
Don't worry about that.
Just re-log it.
Hello?
Hmm...
Jim?
I am downloading some N3P...
That's not it.
...music...
...for a CD mix tape...
Yep.
Close.
...for Holly.
And I'm looking for perfect
songs that work on two levels.
What are the two levels?
The two levels being,
welcome to Scranton,
and I love you.
Okay, let's start with
the "I love you" level.
Hey, what's the group that was
from Scranton and made it big?
Was that U2?
Yes.
You don't love Holly.
I think I do.
But you just met her.
Well, it's love
at first sight.
Actually, it was... No, it
was when I heard her voice.
It was love at first
see with my ears.
Okay. It doesn't
work like that.
Well, not a romantic.
Actually, I think I am.
And I have a little bit of
experience in office romance.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Like with who?
We've been through this.
Pam?
Yes. We are still dating,
and guess what, I took it slow.
Yeah, you took it too slow.
Well, we're really happy.
This thing with Holly
feels a lot like love to me.
And that's really sweet,
and you can think that,
but you don't say that out loud,
and you definitely don't say it to her.
I don't want her to get away.
I know. Here, Michael, you can court
her as you get to know her, you know?
I mean, the office is
a great place for that.
Pam and I, we got to know
each other right out there.
I mean, the first time we
joked around was at my desk.
And the first meal we ever had
was in the break room, actually.
We were at two separate
tables, and I remember that.
The first time we kissed,
even, was right outside and...
Look, all I'm saying is that you can
get to know someone really, really well,
like I did,
right here at work.
I was thinking fireworks for
the party. What do you think?
Oh, boy. I appreciate
your help, but I can't...
No, no, no. I just meant I wanted
to pay to have fireworks at the party.
Why would you do that?
Because I'm going
to miss Toby.
Yep. He's a heck of a guy, and I
think we should send him off right.
Doesn't matter. Here you go.
Really?
Well, we all want
a good party, right?
I'm going to
propose tonight.
Holy crap.
Hey, Kevin.
Hi.
Do you need some help?
I can't decide what to get.
Well, what do
you like to eat?
Well, I like pretzels,
but I really like chips.
Hmm.
Well, how much money
do you have there?
Okay, let's see.
Fifty... This is a button.
Fifty-five, sixty-five, okay,
you have seventy-five cents
so that means you could get
anything up in the top row.
Hmm.
I'm totally going
to bang Holly.
She is cute and helpful,
and she really seems into me.
Hey, Ryan. It's Jim.
Look, man, I don't know
what's gotten into you lately,
but you know what?
I really don't care,
because you're
trying to get rid of me,
and I bet you think I don't care enough
about this job to actually fight back,
but you're wrong,
because I do, and I will.
So you can keep trying to
push me out of this place,
but guess what,
I'm not going anywhere.
Damn it.
Hello, Holly.
Whoa, what are you
doing? You don't...
You don't have to do that. I mean,
we have already-put-together chairs.
That's how we buy
them, actually.
Trying to adjust the lumbar
support on Toby's chair,
and that made this
up-down lever thing not work,
and then I took the
whole chair apart,
and that is the story
of me on the floor.
It's pretty good, right? Yeah,
I'm going to sell the movie rights.
And the sequel, woman
stands at desk and works.
So, I have no idea
how you sit like that.
Yoga.
Sit on floor
and put together chair, we will.
Yoda.
Pass
curvy metal piece, you will.
So are you in town this
weekend? Because I'm not.
I'm not going to be in town.
I'm going out of town.
Oh, so you can't
make my orgy?
Kidding.
Kidding. Acting.
Acting.
Lovitz.
Yeah.
I did it.
What did you do?
I talked to her. Holly.
Just pleasantries, nothing, you know,
not like, "Do you want kids?" or religion,
or "What side of the
bed do you want?"
Hey, I can take either side
of the bed at this point.
Wow. Okay, so how
did that feel?
It was hard.
I wanted to kiss her.
I'm so glad you didn't.
Laying a base.
There you go.
There's plenty
of base-lying left, right?
Yeah.
Hey.
Hello, Angela.
Phyllis. You look like you're
going to have a heart attack.
Can I get a list
of your vendors?
I shredded it.
Why would you do that?
Gosh, I just don't know.
Why do you think?
Sorry.
What did you guys do?
Oh... There he is. I thought
you had gone home already.
Why don't you go home
and come back for the party?
Well, we still have to
do the exit interview.
Yes, we do.
I'll let you in on
a little secret.
I've been very much looking
forward to this moment.
Very, very much. I have
been steeped in anticipation.
Toby has been cruising
for a bruising for 12 years,
and I am now
his cruise director,
and my name is
Captain Bruising.
Wow, thanks, Michael,
I didn't expect you...
Can I just say that
of all the idiots
in all the idiot villages
in all the idiot worlds,
you stand alone, my friend.
Hello.
Hey. Hi. Good to see you.
Here?
I'm just having
a little exit interview.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I'm here.
No, no, no.
This is very boring stuff.
Why don't you take a tour?
Have you seen the bailer?
No, no. I'll look
at it later.
It's part of my job.
Okay.
Did you need me
to take notes?
Hey, Pam, stay.
Okay.
Um...
All right, well,
then I will proceed.
I just have some questions
that I was going to ask.
Um...
Who do you think you are?
I'm Toby.
Yeah. Correct.
Um...
What gives... What...
What gives you the right?
I brought the binder. Do
you want to take a little look?
Sure. You know what? That
sounds good. I'll take a little look-see.
Here we go.
Thank you.
"What would you improve
about Dunder Mifflin?"
At this point...
No, no, no, no.
I've got some ideas,
I guess. No, no, no.
I'm not asking it.
I'm just reading it out loud.
I'd like to hear the answer.
Well, let
me see. I would...
I'll kill you.
I guess everything's okay.
I made it this far, right?
What's the point?
Toby, why don't you
open your present?
No, no, no, no.
Hey! Hey! Hey! This
might not be what I think
that I don't even know is in there because
there are a lot of presents in my car,
and I don't know
which is which.
"Suck on this."
What the hell is that?
Michael.
That's... What do
you mean "Michael"?
That's not even my handwriting.
Hey, what the hell is going on here?
Who thought it
would be hysterical
to give Toby a rock
for his going-away gift?
You did.
You made me wrap it.
No!
Now, I thought it was over the
line. I just...
Okay. You know what that is?
You know what that is?
That is
a psyche.
Psyche. So that is not
my real gift to Toby.
So what is your gift?
My gift is forthcoming, Pam.
What is it?
I am going to give Toby...
Your watch?
Yes, I am.
That was it. How did
you know that?
I just knew.
How did you know?
Oh, that is so sweet.
Well, that's my watch.
Thanks. I'm going to
set it to Costa Rica time.
Hey, that's good.
It's the kid.
Look! Look! Look!
Hey, it's the temp!
- Look!
- Oh, my gosh.
- It's the temp.
- Wow.
- Is that the police?
- Yes.
Well, this is what happened.
Ryan's big project
was the Web site,
which wasn't doing
so well, so Ryan,
to give the impression
of sales, recorded them twice,
once as office sales
and once as Web site sales,
which is what we refer to in the
business as misleading the shareholders,
another good term is fraud.
The real crime,
I think, was the beard.
Oh, my God. Ryan. Oh, my God.
I cannot wait to
visit Ryan in prison.
I'm going to wear my hottest
track suit and get my hair done
and then be like, "Hi, Ryan."
And then all the other prisoners
are going to be like, "Damn,
Ryan, you got a hot ex-girlfriend.
"I would never have treated her so
bad when I was outside of prison."
Would you do me a favor
and connect me to Ryan?
Absolutely.
Right to voicemail.
Hey, Ryan, it's Jim.
You know what?
Totally disregard
that last voicemail,
because you obviously
have your hands tied.
Good luck.
What's protocol on this?
I normally do
nothing, I guess.
You shouldn't...
Michael, are you okay?
I'm just worried
about my friend.
Oh, God, of course you are.
Just... I'm fine.
I'm holding it together.
I have a business to run.
No, hey, stop.
I'm cool.
You can let yourself be
upset. He's your friend.
Look,
you know what I usually find?
Holly is sweet
and simple, like a lady baker.
I would not be
surprised to find out
that she had worked in
a bakery before coming here.
She has that kind of warmth.
I'm pretty sure she's baked
on a professional level.
Whoa.
Cool. A bouncy house.
Kevin, take your
shoes off first.
No anti-gravity
machine, huh?
Sorry, Michael. I don't
think they're real.
Ferris wheel's pretty
cool, though.
Wow. Look at
our parking lot.
Yeah. Who would
have thought?
Is Jim going
to propose tonight?
He is, isn't he?
No, he's not.
Is he?
It was a pretty good company,
but I just couldn't see a future there.
They kept hiring
from the outside.
It was easy to get in,
but impossible to rise up.
That's what she... A
lot of places are like that.
I think it's really cool
you hired Kevin.
Thanks.
Do you have it?
Almost.
Here we go, here we go.
Put it in!
I like...
That's my car.
Hey, what are you doing?
Mose! What the hell
is going on here?
Nothing you need
to know the details of!
There is a raccoon in
the car! No, there's not.
Dwight,
why did you do that?
It was playful hazing.
No! There's no such thing
as playful hazing.
Dwight, I want you to
look at Holly right now.
Everybody, I want you to
look at Holly right now,
and maybe if you look at her deeply
enough, you'll see what I see in her,
and that is that we are all
very lucky to have her here.
Holly is the best thing that
has happened to this company
since World War Ill.
Fifty years.
She is the best.
Take care of that,
all right?
- It's not rabid.
- Shh!
Thanks for
bringing that up.
Get it out. Come on.
Get it out. Get out.
I'm really sorry.
Michael, thank you so
much for saying that.
I feel so welcome here.
I just...
Excuse me.
Did you see that? Did you
see it? Did you see what...
Wowee.
Well, Jan didn't believe
in showing affection,
so sometimes I don't know how
to react when a girl touches me.
Oh...
I like it.
Hey, Mrs. Vance,
we're all out.
Hey, Kevin.
I need you to do me a solid and
go buy some more barbecue sauce.
Okay.
Cool.
You drive your own car?
Yep. This is my car.
Do you drive your own car?
Yep. Just like you.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Kevin, I'm really
proud of you.
All right, let's hear it
for Darryl and his band.
You know what, let's also give a shout
out to Phyllis for this awesome party.
Probably
the best one that we have ever had.
But the real reason that we
are here is to say goodbye
to a guy who we will probably
never ever see again.
Now, a lot of you know that I
am an accomplished song writer.
Song parody writer.
I've done things like
Beers in Heaven.
Classic.
Or Total Eclipse of the Fart.
Not my favorite. I like
that one. I like that one.
I love to sing them, but I am
not going to be doing that today.
I am going to be doing something
I wrote specifically for Toby.
Do you know Goodbye Stranger,
Supertramp?
Yeah.
It was early
morning yesterday
I was up before the dawn
And I really have
enjoyed my stay
Toby must be moving on
I'm going to miss Toby. He has a
nice calming presence in the office.
Goodbye, Toby
It's been nice
Hope you find your paradise
Don't tell him I said this, but I
always thought he was kind of cute.
Come tomorrow, feel no pain
Feel no pain
Toby
Toby, Toby, Toby's going away
See ya! He's out of here
Goodbye, Toby! Goodbye, Toby!
Not bad.
Oh, hey, thanks.
Someday I would love to hear
Beers in Heaven.
Oh, okay. Yeah.
Well, actually, too soon.
It's very sexual.
Sorry.
Kevin.
Kevin, where are you?
You missed my song, buddy.
Yeah, Michael I'm at Gerrity's.
You have to come down here.
Just pay for it, and we'll
reimburse you when you get back.
No, I brought my money.
Michael, there's something
that you need to see.
What is it?
Just hurry.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's at the
supermarket.
He needs me.
You know, the party,
driving to the supermarket.
It's a big day for him.
Yeah. That's true.
Don't move a muscle. I will
be back momentarily. All right?
You can drink, finish your drink,
and then I'll... Okay, I'll be back.
Well, it was
good to see you.
It was great to
see you, Jan.
Yeah. So...
Okay. Hello, Jan.
Oh, hello, Michael.
Wow, Kevin, really?
We're... Sorry, we're
in the middle of a party.
Is this why you
called me down here?
Yeah. Michael, I just...
I think you kids have
a lot to catch up on.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thanks, Kevin.
Wow. I can't believe it.
Look at you.
Are you nauseous?
Do you have cravings?
You never touched my Propecia
or my Accutane, did you?
No, I...
Good.
Good. Thank God, because
that's... Didn't touch that.
Wow. I am so happy.
I am so deliriously happy.
Why?
Because you are pregnant.
Yeah. And because
it obviously happened
when we were together,
and I am very...
Yeah, it did happen...
...proud.
...when we were together.
That's true, and... But you
are not...
You're not the dad.
You cheated on me
when I specifically
asked you not to?
No, I did not...
I did not cheat on you.
I did not.
Well, okay, so it's not mine,
and it's not somebody else's, so...
I know
the whole toilet seat
thing is a myth, so...
I went to a sperm bank.
You did?
Yeah.
When we were going out?
I don't understand. You
always used to be very cautious,
wearing two condoms.
I know.
You would rather have somebody
else's sperm than my sperm?
No. No, no. It's not
just any sperm bank.
I mean, it's really... This is
a really, really great place.
It's amazing, actually. I'm
going to bring you the catalog.
You should look through it.
It's... In fact, it's right next
to that little breakfast place
that you like in the city, where
you can draw on the tables.
IHOP.
If I was 22, and I had lots of
time to have lots of children,
then, sure, let's let Michael
have a shot at one of them,
but honestly, I need to
make this one count.
Oh, that's really good.
I feel so much better.
I just needed to get all
of that out on the table.
I'm glad you told me.
Look, I don't know what you're
going to be doing tomorrow,
but I have my Lamaze class in
Allentown, and you could come.
I usually, you know, use a
foam noodle instead of a partner.
Um...
I'll... I have to
think about it.
Okay.
My whole life I have
known two things.
I love sex,
and I want to have kids.
And I always thought that those
two things would go hand in hand,
but now I think it might
be one or the other.
Oh, look, they're starting.
Well, I hope you
had fun today,
because you are never ever
throwing a party again.
Hey.
Can I have your
attention, please?
I was waiting for the
right time to do this,
and [ can't think of a better
time than right now.
With the music playing
and all our friends around
and fireworks going off.
My parents are here,
Andrew and Ellen Bernard.
Thank you for sharing
in this joyous moment.
Ms. Angela Martin, will
you please join me on stage?
Okay. Then I will come
to you, my flower.
Damn it!
Angela, will you
do me the honor
of giving me your tiny
hand in marriage?
Okay.
Into the mike, sweetie.
I said okay.
She said yes.
And the crowd goes wild!
I've been carrying that ring
around in my wallet for six years,
because you don't know when
you're going to meet the right girl
and the moment's
going to be right.
And tonight,
with the fireworks
and the music and
everything, it was right.
Can I be your bridesmaid?
No.
Well,
it was my own fault.
Tuna!
I'm engaged.
I know.
That's awesome, man.
That's great.
Mr. Andrew Bernard.
It's got a nice ring to it.
Hey... Hey, you know,
I just realized,
I don't have a picture
of the two of us.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, could we?
Sure.
Meredith, do you mind?
This one.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Oh, let's do it again.
Pam, your smile is weird.
It's digital, so just take
as many as you want.
One, two, three.
I don't know. I just... I really thought
Jim was going to propose tonight.
Hey there.
Hey.
So, you missed
something really big.
Yeah?
Yeah, Andy proposed
to one of your accountants.
Oh, wow.
And that's as specific
as I can be
on my first day, but...
Well, I can see Andy
proposing to Angela.
I can also see him
proposing to Oscar.
Okay.
So, you know, somehow after all
those ribs, I'm still really hungry.
I don't know, I was thinking of
maybe going off-campus somewhere
and getting some dessert.
Oh, um...
Well, you know what, you
should go to the Glider Diner.
Ask Stanley about that.
He practically lives there.
Okay.
I'll go to the diner with you.
Oh, that would be great.
We can go eat pie.
I love pie.
Me, too.
Okay.
Have a good night.
Night.
Yeah, it was a good day.
I mean, first days are
always the hardest, right?
Well, I should go.
I got to buckle him in.
Well, this is it.
I am here to see you off.
Thanks.
Really, Michael?
Sorry. Corporate policy.
It's not.
You might take something.
I don't think he's
going to take anything.
Okay, security guard.
Some kind of alarm.
Okay.
Hi, Jan. It's Michael.
I just... I just want
to let you know
that I am going to go
to your Lamaze class tomorrow,
and if there's any details
you need to fill me in on,
like what exactly Lamaze is,
that would be great,
and I will see you
tomorrow morning.
I am going to be
kind of a daddy.
Party planning's a real high,
like a runner's high.
Oh, God!
What?