Yeah. Everything. It's all
good. It's all good. Phyllis.
Dancing babies.
I love it. I love it.
We are making a
commercial for Dunder Mifflin today,
our first ad ever.
Corporate purchased
some airtime in local markets
to spread the word
about Dunder Mifflin Infinity,
and they are even sending
up a professional ad company
to help us make it later.
So it's not too shabby.
Best ad ever?
Give me a
break, give me a break
Break me off
a piece of that
I am totally blanking.
What is the thing?
Nobody tell him.
What?
No. Why?
You got it.
You're so close.
Break
me off a piece of that
Applesauce
"Break me off a piece of that
applesauce." I don't think so.
A piece
of that Chrysler car
Nope.
Football cream
Okay.
It's football cream.
It's football cream. All
right, so, anybody else?
I'm taking a computer animation
class, so I can try to do a logo.
Look at that.
Even the receptionist is getting in on
the creativity. Very good. Very good.
Hello. Hello.
Hey. How you doing?
Michael Scott.
Hey, Michael.
Regional manager.
Hi, Michael. Nice to meet
you. Excited to talk ideas.
Us, too, man.
You know what,
I want this to be cutting
edge. I want it to be fast.
Quick cuts, you know?
Youthful, sort of a
MTV-on-crack
kind of thing.
That sounds great.
All right. Good. Well, this is
what we have to work with.
I would like you to meet
Andrew Bernard, the Nard Dog.
Who let
the Nard dog out?
He gives the best
back rubs in the office.
That's true, I give a mean back
rub. Also do good aromatherapy.
You just got
Nard-dogged!
Now, this gentleman right
here is the key to our urban vibe.
Urban? I grew
up in a small town.
What about me
seems urban to you?
Stanley is hilarious.
Phyllis is like
our Mrs. Butterworth.
Kind of a less
urban Aunt Jemima.
These are our accountants.
And as you can see, they
are very different sizes.
What you might
want to do is kind of
a Papa Bear, Mama
Bear, Baby Bear thing.
That might be
kind of fun.
Mama Bear.
Who else?
I think it's great that the
company's making a commercial,
because not very many
people have heard of us.
I mean, when I tell people
that I work at Dunder Mifflin,
they think that we sell mufflers
or muffins or mittens or...
And frankly all of those sound
better than paper, so I let it slide.
You playing
that game again?
Second Life is not a game. It is
a multi-user virtual environment.
It doesn't have
points or scores.
winners or losers.
Oh, it has losers.
I signed up for Second
Life about a year ago.
Back then, my life was so great
that I literally wanted a second one.
In my second life,
I was also a paper salesman
and I was also
named Dwight.
Absolutely everything
was the same.
Except I could fly.
Little girl in a field
holding a flower.
We zoom back to find
that she's in the desert
and the field
IS an oasis.
We zoom
back further,
the desert is a sandbox in
the world's largest resort hotel.
Zoom back further, the hotel
is actually the playground
of the world's
largest prison.
But we zoom back
further... Okay,
I can tell that your
time is valuable...
Actually,
I don't get paid by the hour
anymore, but thank you.
I get paid
by the year.
That all sounds really,
really ambitious. So...
Yeah. I know.
Why don't we show you what
we did with the Nashua branch?
Mmm...
Okay.
That's what Nashua
came up with?
That sucks. Wow.
That's what we
came up with.
Well, we can do
better than that.
Well, the main part of the ad
has to stay the same, actually.
Yeah, it's the last five seconds
where we have some leeway.
The waving?
Well, no, no. You don't have to be
waving. That was just what they did.
You guys can
be clapping
or sitting, standing
outside, inside, whatever.
And this is where you
really get to be creative.
I need some advice. I've been spending a
lot of time making out with Angela lately.
We've been necking.
But only necking. Right?
Not actually
kissing our mouths.
Just neck on neck.
It's just like rubbing/nuzzling
our necks together.
It's hot. I'm not gonna lie
to you, but it's a little weird.
But you seem like
a guy with answers.
So how do I fast track
this, get to first base?
We cannot
talk about this,
because someone
might hear us.
We'll use code names.
Angela can stay the same,
but we'll change Andy to Dwight.
That's not
different enough.
Dwike?
You have a call
from Eddie Murphy.
Hello.
MICHAEL IMITATING EDDIE MURPHY ON
SPEAKERPHONE: Shrek. Shrek. I'm a donkey.
I'm a donkey, Shrek.
I'm just kidding.
It's me. Hello, Ry.
What?
Okay, calm down.
I just have
a small problem.
I told you not to
call about small problems.
Yeah. Well, when I
call about big problems,
you don't like that either,
so make up your mind, kiddo.
Here is the deal, the ad guys that
you sent are locking me in a creative box
and sort of
ignoring my ideas.
That's good. They're
creative. You're not.
I'm creative, Ryan.
It's not part
of your job.
It's, like,
maybe you can COOK,
but that doesn't mean you
should start a restaurant.
Well, actually I can't cook
and I am starting a restaurant,
Mike's Cereal Shack.
I'm thinking we'll have as many
varieties as you can buy in the store.
Okay. I'm not really
interested in that right now.
I'm delegating creativity
to creative professionals.
It's a different
skill set.
Look, I wasn't good
at sales, right? Yeah!
But I'm good at managing
people who do sales.
Are you? I don't think you're
doing such a great job here,
suppressing ideas
and creativity.
All right, let me ask you this.
Tell me if you think this is creative.
When I was five,
I imagined that there was
such a thing as a unicorn.
And this was before I had
even heard of one or seen one.
I just drew
a picture of a horse
that could fly over rainbows
and had a huge spike in its head.
I was five,
five years old.
Couldn't even talk yet.
Hey, guys. You know what?
We cannot shoot this ad today.
Okay, when should we come back?
How about
never-hundred hours, sir?
Wait, we were
sent here to help...
I'm not gonna
argue with this guy.
Let's go.
Good luck, dude.
Hey, thanks.
Thank you.
Michael,
David Wallace.
What is this about
dismissing the ad people?
Yeah. I'm glad you called.
Ryan is being a little bitch again.
I'm on, Michael.
What's up,
my brother?
Listen, David, I would
like to do this ad in-house.
I want to use only the creativity
that we have right here in the office,
and I will send it to
you tomorrow morning.
Take a look at it. If you do
not think that it's ready to air,
send the ad agency
back down here
and we'll do it
on my dime.
This is weird.
I'm willing to stake
my entire reputation on it.
Okay. I'll see
you tomorrow.
Okay. -.
And thus Michael Scott
sealed his own destiny.
In a good way.
Has anyone ever come up to
you and said, "You're not creative"?
Yes.
Well, they're wrong.
You are creative.
You are damn creative,
each and every one of you.
You are so much
more creative
than all of the other dry, boring
morons that you work with.
Who are you talking to,
specifically?
I kind of know what it's
like to be in commercials.
My nickname in high school
used to be Kool-Aid Man.
When I was younger I always
wanted to be an actor in commercials,
then I realized
I had a brain.
I'm excited about doing the ad, but
I'm not really used to doing videos
with so many
people around.
We have three scenes
to film, big scenes.
We have a song to write,
so let's get cracking.
Kelly, I want you
to do makeup.
Oscar, I would like you to
do costume design, obviously.
Phyllis, I'd like you
to look around town
and see if we have any
celebrities in our local area.
Sue Grafton is at
the Steamtown Mall.
She's doing a book
signing right now.
Okay, okay. Phyllis, this
is what I want you to do.
I want you to go down to the
mall. I want you to get in line.
I want you to get her
to be in this commercial.
This would be a huge
coup, people. All right?
Do not take no for
an answer. Okay.
Does anyone actually know
what Sue Grafton looks like?
I mean is she hot, or...
She's crazy hot.
Well, then maybe we should just
use Angela and say she's Sue Grafton.
Would anyone notice?
That's not happening.
I find the mystery
genre disgusting.
I hate being titillated.
Bye, everyone.
Light it up, Phyllis.
Get her, Phyl.
Out of paper, out of stock
Those friendly faces
around the block
Break loose
from the chains
That are causing
you pain
Call Michael
and Stanley, Jim, Dwight, Creed
Call Andy and Kelly
For your business paper needs
Dunder Mifflin
The people person's
paper people
Dunder Mifflin
The people person's
paper people
Time out. Time out.
Time out. I thought...
I was under the impression
that this was going to be a rap.
What's rap?
Okay, Darryl, wow.
You need to learn a lot
about your own culture.
I'll make you a mix.
Great.
News flash. I got some juicy
updates on Operation Fallen Angel.
Remind me to
tell you later.
Hey.
No talk.
I'm animating.
Why don't we take a quick
10-second break from that
so I can show you
what's going on here.
Okay, this is Dwight's Second
Life. He's on it all the time.
So much so that his little guy
here has created his own world.
It's called
Second Second Life
for those people who want to be
removed even further from reality.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
He's really in pain.
Who's that?
Oh, it's just my
avatar guy. Whatever.
He looks
a lot like you.
Yeah. How much time
did you spend on that?
Not much. It's just for
tracking Dwight, so...
Right. You're a sports
writer in Philadelphia?
Nice build, too.
Yep.
You have a guitar
slung on your back.
I did not know
you played guitar.
I...
Why don't we go back to
the animation? No, no, no.
I want to see more of Philly
Jim. No, show me how this...
I want Philly Jim.
Show me
how this works.
Oh, boy.
Out of
paper, out of stock
Those friendly faces
around the block
Break loose from the chains
That are causing you pain
Call Michael, Stanley,
Jim, Dwight and Creed
Call Andy and Kelly
for your business paper needs
Call Dunder Mifflin
People
person's paper people
Dunder Mifflin
It's the people
person's paper people
Stop, stop, stop.
This is not me. This is
not... It's not my music.
You're right. It's
better than you. It's us.
Dunder Mifflin
The people person's
paper people
No, no, no. I
hate it! I hate it.
I don't hate it. I just don't
like it at all, and it's terrible.
You're on your own, Mike.
Okay, you know what?
Hold on, hold on, Darryl.
You just said
you hated it.
You said you hated it.
I said I hate the style.
Break me off
a piece of that lumber tar
Snickers bar
Okay. Wow. Wow.
This looks terrible.
Break me off a
piece of that Grey Poupon
Andy. Andy. This is a
pivotal scene in the ad.
And if we don't get this,
if we don't nail it,
we're gonna lose the
whole triumph of the moment.
The triumph of the will. Now,
God, what? What, Phyllis?
Well, I got in line
to buy Sue Grafton's book
and when it came
to my turn,
I asked her if she wanted to be in
the ad, and she said, "No, thank you."
But I wasn't supposed
to take no for an answer...
Attagirl.
...so I kept on asking,
and they finally threw me out of
the store in front of all my friends.
Okay.
Did you or did you
not get Sue Grafton?
No.
Oh, you're...
Can somebody give
her a tissue? Please?
I hope you're not killing yourself on
this, because I'm sure it's good enough
for Michael's ad that will
probably be seen by no one.
Maybe. But it's not
good enough for me yet.
Okay. Do you want me to stay?
No, no, you can
go home. I'm good.
Pam is staying late tonight
to achieve her dreams,
so I'm pretty
proud of her.
Unfortunately,
she was my ride home.
You coming?
I...
Piss or get
off the pot!
Dunder Mifflin.
This is Pam.
Good morning.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I
looked away for a second,
and Creed snatched
your hash browns.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I worked until
about 2:45 a.m.,
and then I had to decide if I wanted
to spend the night with Michael
editing in his office and Dwight
watching Michael edit in his office,
or drive home and probably
fall asleep at the wheel
and die in
a fiery car wreck.
I passed out on my
keyboard trying to decide.
Let me pour
you some bubbly,
because somebody got to
a whole new level last night.
Andy, I can't
hear this right now.
No. No. No.
This is good.
You know how we haven't
really gotten anywhere
that I want to get
to physically yet?
Well, last night,
that changed.
We're making out. I'm
kissing her neck and her cheek
and her ear lobe, and she's
not really kissing me back,
but she closes her
eyes and she's like,
"Oh, D. Oh, D."
She called you D?
Yeah.
D for Andy.
Oh, D.
Oh, D!
I'm about to send
the ad to corporate. And it is sent.
They'll probably watch
it right away. I would.
Okay.
Yes? Pam, please
clear my phone lines.
Certainly.
Okay, clear.
They could call
any second now.
Oh, God.
I better call.
Well, it's been tough.
The geniuses at corporate
rejected my commercial,
and tonight they are airing
the brain-dead version.
So welcome
one and all
to the world premiere
of corporate crap fest.
Hey, seemed
like a big hit.
No.
People are stupid.
People like waving.
Waving sells, not art.
The ad we made, our ad,
the real one,
was full of humor and full of depth
and full of heart, and it was real.
Hey, could you do me a favor?
Could you put that in the DVD player?
Hey, everybody, I just
want to welcome you all
to the premiere of the real
Dunder Mifflin commercial.
The Michael Scott
director's cut. Hope you like it.
It all
starts with an idea.
But you can never tell
where an idea will end up.
Because ideas spread.
They change, grow.
They connect us
with the world.
And in a fast-moving world,
where good news moves
at the speed of time,
and bad news isn't
always what it seems.
Because when push
comes to shove,
we all deserve
a second chance
lo score.
Dunder Mifflin. Limitless
paper in a paperless world.
Animation, all her,
by the way. Really?
Yeah, I just thought...
The animation was cool.
Thanks.
Hey, listen, you ever been
on a motorcycle because...
Michael, that was fun.
That was fun.
Next round of drinks
IS on me, people.
Claude Van Damme
Hair for men
Poison gas, NutraSweet
It's got to rhyme
with "piece."
Fancy Feast.
Break me off
a piece of that Fancy Feast
It's the cat food.
Nailed it.