Everybody, everybody, listen
up. I need your ideas now.
Ideas, please, right
now. Go, go! Come on!
Michael, we don't know
what you're talking about.
Wet cement outside.
It's drying fast.
Come on, this is a lifelong dream.
What do I write? What do I write?
Michael, you could
put your initials in it.
M.G.S. No.
Some idiot named Mark Greg Schputnick
will claim credit for it. I don't...
That is true. Once in a
lifetime opportunity, people.
- Come on!
- Well...
Here we go! Yes?
When I was
a little girl...
Okay.
Okay, do it! Come on,
great! Let's hear it!
We found some wet cement...
It's drying, it's drying. ...in
the park in our neighborhood...
All right,
come on!
Come on, Phyllis!
What did we write?
Oh! Come on!
No! Here it is.
You draw a picture.
"Cause that says so
much more than words.
No, no!
Come on, give me
something good!
Okay, I was
watching E!
And I saw Will Smith
outside the Chinese Theater,
and, oh, my God,
he looked so good.
Pam, translate.
She's talking about the handprints
that celebrities make in the cement.
I love it!
If you were a real star,
you'd put your face in it.
I love it more!
Michael, that
doesn't seem safe...
I love it!
- Come on, let's go!
- Come on!
We are here today not to
immortalize a man, but an idea.
Maybe the idea
of a man.
Hurry, please.
Greatness is only skin
deep, some people say.
Can you breathe?
Well, that's not true.
Other people believe
it's deep down inside.
Hold your breath.
And in this case,
that's also not true.
Ready? And...
Go!
Force it in as
deep as you can.
That's what she said.
Today's a very special
day for me. And it's really not about me.
It's about my grandkids.
It's about my great-grandkids.
I can come back here
when I'm 100,
and I can find that
piece of cement and say,
"That's me. Look, kids.
Your daddy left that face hole.”
I don't know.
It's a good feeling.
Okay.
Adjective.
"Tall."
No, no, "Nice."
Good one. Okay.
You ready?
Mmm-hmm.
"The tall man entered
the nice building,
"to visit a
very nice man.
"'Sit down, Mr. Smith. Can I
interest you in any good cat food?""
It's a man eating cat food!
What about
a cat eating man food?
Andy and Angela
seem very happy.
I hope nothing horrible
ever happens to them.
Yeah, I slept over at
a friend's house, and...
I forgot my contact solution, so I
had to wear my back-up glasses.
Shut up.
All right,
everybody.
Oh, my God. Pam, those
make you look so ugly.
Pam, in order to get
hotter, you take glasses off.
You're moving in
the wrong direction.
I don't have my contacts...
I can't even hear you.
It's just noise coming
out of an ugly scientist.
Everybody, we're gonna have
a little brainstorming session
in the conference room.
Energize.
You know what
would energize me?
If you,
Pamela Morgan Beesly...
Don't you,
don't you...
If you propose to me during a
Michael meeting, I will say no.
Well, it's too late,
because I'm proposing
that you get me a cup of coffee,
which would energize me greatly
and make me the
happiest man in the world.
Everybody, so how are we
going to energize our office?
I mean, I haven't done
anything since Christmas.
Pam clearly has
just given up trying.
So what we need to do is
we need to get things going.
We need to get percolating a little bit.
Anybody have any ideas what we could do?
Any suggestions?
Yes, Andy?
What if we changed our outgoing
answering machine message
so it just had a little more
zing and a little more pep?
Zing and pep. Those are the kind
of words we're looking for. Yes, Jim.
What about if we did an
even newer voicemail message
that had even
more zing and pep?
Now we're cooking, I like
this. Maybe a whole theme.
Like a rap... A rap rhyme.
An urban thing.
An urban... Yeah, Stanley,
you want to help us out with that?
Stanley!
Earth to Stanley.
Not me.
Yes, you. Come on, Stanley,
put your little game down
and join the group.
No.
Stanley, we're having...
Leave me alone, damn it.
We're having
a brainstorm session.
Did I stutter?
Good. This is good. I'm
going to grab a glass of water.
Can I talk to you a second?
What?
I really think that you need to address
what happened with Stanley this morning.
What are you blabbering
about? Nothing happened.
Well, you know, Stanley
was openly insubordinate.
That, in the conference room?
Yeah.
We were joshing
around, the two of us.
And he said,
"Did I stutter?"
And
I said, "What, dawg?"
It was joking,
Toby, all right?
He didn't seem
like he was joking.
Well, you don't get it,
because Stanley is a beautiful,
sassy, powerful black man,
and you're you.
If you had any friends,
you would understand.
Friends joke with one another.
"Hey, you're poor."
"Well, hey, your mama's dead."
That's what friends do.
It's... You're so white.
All right. Well...
If you really believe
that Stanley was joking...
Mmm-hmm.
Why don't we
go ask him now?
Okay, I will.
I'm not feeling very
well right now, though.
My stomach hurts, so I may
be going home early today.
You know, Michael, sometimes
my daughter's stomach hurts
when there's
a mean girl at school.
Well, sometimes my stomach
hurts when you come into my office.
So it's probably
psychological.
You meet a lot of ladies driving an
Xterra, because you pull up to a stoplight
and look over, and there's an Xterra next
to you, they're always driven by chicks.
So there's your icebreaker.
Scratch!
That's
a racing stripe.
Bumper's sagging.
Hmm. I doubt
that very much.
This car is crap. I will
buy it for next to nothing.
How next to?
Well, here are
your options.
You can sell it for parts,
drive it off a cliff,
you can donate it to a person that
you'd like to see die in a car crash, or
you can sell it to me and I'll use
it as I would a wagon on my farm.
It will be towed
by a donkey.
I have to pick
one of those? Yes.
Can you go over
those options again?
You know what?
You knock $1,500 off the price right
now and I will take it off your hands.
It's gotta be now.
Well, I had the
Blue Book value...
Seal the deal.
Let's do it.
Let's do this thing.
Three, two, one.
Can I think about it?
Five, four, three,
two, now.
Let me think about it.
Now. Now.
Say it. Do it now.
Thinking about it.
Thinking.
Do it now! Do it.
Shake my hand.
You will sell me this car.
Yeah, all right!
What?
I see that you
gave me that form
that I asked you to give me,
Stanley the manly.
So thank you for that. I
guess we are back to normal.
What are you talking about?
Well, you know, the thing that
you said earlier that you didn't mean.
And that I forgive you for.
The whole thing's silly, isn't it?
Friends don't need to apologize
to friends, as far as I'm concerned.
So we are cool.
I am not going
to apologize to you.
It's like I used
to tell my wife.
"I do not apologize unless I think I'm wrong,
and if you don't like it, you can leave."
And I say the same thing to my current
wife, and I'll say it to my next one, too.
Jim is in charge of Stanley
only in sales-related matters.
Hence the green line.
Green for money.
Sales, get it? There
is this yellow zigzag
that does give Ryan the
authority to discipline Stanley.
Great.
However,
in so doing,
it zigs past your name, hence zagging
you and making you appear weak.
Thus the yellow color.
Yellow for cowardly.
What's the pink?
Menstrual cycles.
Okay.
Is there anybody up here,
anybody at all, that can deal with this
other than me...
You.
Well, there is the emergency
disaster mode for the org chart.
This gives me full authority over
every single person in the office.
I never said
you could do that.
All you have
to do is say it.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Say it. Just do it.
Don't think, say it. Do it.
Five, four, three, two...
Do it. Give me
control, Michael.
I promise to give authority
back to you when this crisis is over.
Do it, Michael.
Do it. Hey.
This office needs
a strongman.
Say it.
No.
So...
All right, well then, you're gonna
have to deal with this yourself.
Hey, Pam. I really
like your glasses.
Oh, thanks.
All the girlfriends that I've
ever had have worn glasses.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, it's kind of a
turn-on for me, actually.
I should probably
get back to...
Like librarians.
...entering the...
Could you just say,
"These are due
back Thursday"?
No.
Dunder Mifflin. This is
Pam. Okay, go ahead.
A lot of jazz cats are blind,
but they can play the piano
like nobody's business.
I'd like to put the piano in front of Pam
without her glasses and see what happens.
I'd also like to
see her topless.
Mike.
I'm very busy here, man.
Darryl...
Have you ever been in a gang?
Why?
It's an advice question, and
if you don't want to talk about
it, I completely understand. It's...
No, no, no. I know
it's very, very personal.
No...
I have.
I knew it. Okay.
Who are we
talking about here?
Crips, Bloods?
Both.
God.
Yeah, them
and the Latin Kings.
The Warriors, Newsies.
Okay.
Okay, so dig this.
You're on the street and
one of your gang disses you.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah, right.
So what do you do to
get him to make it right?
Well, see, in the gang world, we
use something called "Fluffy fingers."
What is that?
That's where if somebody
really gets in your face,
you know, you just
start tickling them.
Really?
Yeah.
And he starts tickling you.
You know, pretty soon
you're laughing and hugging.
Before you know it, you've
forgotten the whole thing.
Y'all can just go to church
together and get an ice cream cone.
I would have
never thought that
gangs would be
tickling each other.
Well, it's effective.
I think it's self-explanatory.
Hey, Jim! Come here for a second.
Can you answer me something
as a true Eagles fan?
Oh, boy.
How do you live with
a franchise this bad?
On a wing
and a prayer, mostly.
All right,
whatever you say.
Listen, while I have
you here with Toby,
I need to give you a formal
warning about your job performance.
A formal warning?
It's actually not a joke. I know
how you spend your time here.
I know how little you
care about your job.
And honestly, if you spent
as much time selling
as you do goofing around with
Dwight and hanging out at reception,
we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
I'm sorry, is this because I talked
to Wallace about your website?
Because I really didn't
mean to go over your head.
This has nothing to
do with that, all right?
I always appreciate constructive
criticism about my job performance.
I thrive on it.
I'm sorry, then do you mind
explaining it a little better?
"Cause I'm not
sure what's really...
Whoa. Don't get
all defensive, all right?
It's just a warning.
If you want the details, Toby can
provide them. You take it easy, all right?
I'd say all the goofing
around at Pam's desk
and hanging out with Pam
has finally caught up to him.
You know, with Pam.
Hey, what happened?
What did Ryan want?
Oh, we were just
talking about
bureaucratic stuff.
Because you're
very important.
Yeah.
Oh, what's Dwight up to?
Oh, probably nothing.
What the hell
is this all about?
You're flipping
my car for profit.
It's my car now.
I gave you a deal
based on what you said to me.
Yeah, well, seller beware.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got to monitor a three-way
bidding war for my car on eBay.
I've got a Mad Lib for you.
"A stupid, idiotic numbskull
"named Andy Bernard
sold his Xterra
"to a smart and capable
man named Dwight.
"This is shaping up to be
an awesome day for Dwight."
Okay, everybody. Shh. Listen up.
Earlier today, Stanley sassed me,
and Toby gave me some
suggestions on how to discipline him.
They did not work, obviously,
because they were stupid.
So I am now going
to fake fire him.
What does that mean?
It's like a mock execution.
That's not a good idea.
Yes, it is a good idea.
It's the only possible
solution I have left.
Well, you can
actually fire him.
No...
I've had enough of you.
Why are you telling us this?
Because I want you to behave as if
I'm actually firing him, Oscar, okay?
Michael, if you
hadn't told us this,
then we would've thought
that you were actually firing him.
I'm not firing him! I will need
you to act like I am firing him.
Just... What I'm going to do is I'm
going to pretend that I'm firing him.
And I need you to act like I
am firing him. Do you get that?
Do you get it? I'm
teaching him a lesson.
He needs to learn humility,
all right? That's all I'm...
Okay, here he comes.
Let's just play-act.
Stanley, may I talk
to you for a second?
Stanley Hudson,
you are fired.
Are you serious?
I am serious.
We are all serious.
You are fired
like a heart attack.
You're firing me
over three words?
Yes.
Have you lost your mind?
Do you think I'm
gonna let you do this to me?
I've watched you screw
up this office for 10 years,
and I'm filing a lawsuit, and I'm
gonna tell them about every stupid thing
you've ever done
up in this office.
All right, okay.
You know what?
Now you know how I feel.
This was a fake firing.
Lesson learned. Good
work, everybody. Very nice.
So I'm not fired.
That's it.
And...
Do you have anything
to say to me?
Ooh, yes, I do.
You are out of your damn
little pea-sized mind.
What is wrong with you?
Do you have any sense at all?
Do you have any idea
how to run an office?
Every day you do something
stupider than you did the day before.
And I think, "There's no
possible way he can top that."
But what do you do? You
find a way, damn it, to top it.
You are a
professional idiot...
Hey, stop it!
Okay, everybody out.
Who? Yeah,
everybody except Stanley.
Let's go.
I can't find my glasses.
Okay, you know what?
Why don't you take my hand and
leave them, and let's get out of here.
Okay, okay.
It's Michael versus Stanley,
and it is the clash of the titans.
In one corner, you have
Michael, and he is mad.
And then in the other corner,
you have Stanley, and he's mad.
So that's about it.
I don't understand why
you keep picking on me.
Oh, for the love of God.
You just
do, and I don't know why,
so please help me understand.
Fine. Here it is. You are
a person I do not respect.
The things you say, your
actions, your methods and style,
everything you would do, I
would do it the opposite way.
Well, Stanley,
maybe you are feeling
that you don't respect me
because you don't
know me very well.
Michael, I've known
you a very long time,
and the more I've gotten to know
you, the less I've come to respect you.
Any other theories?
All right, you
don't respect me.
I accept that.
But listen to me.
You can't talk to me that way in this
office, you just can't. I am your boss.
Can't allow it.
Fair enough.
I am a good person, and sometimes
good people don't get no respect.
Rodney Dangerfield.
"Hey, I
don't get no respect. No respect at all.
"When I was in the sandbox
as a kid, I got no respect.
"My wife likes
to talk after sex.
"So she called me from a hotel
room, said, 'I don't respect you.'
"Thoughtless.
"You know what don't get
no respect? Airplane food.
"Why don't they just make
the plane out of the airline food?
"My wife don't get no respect.
So... Take her, please, for example.
"If you don't get no respect,
you might be a redneck."
"Respect is nice."
Borat.
"What's the deal with
Grape-Nuts? No grapes, no nuts.
"I don't get no respect.”
So I'm thinking as a
reward for our loyal clients
that we contact their assistants
and we find out where they live,
and then, we go to their houses in
the middle of summer and go caroling.
It is a summer Christmas sale-e-bration,
and we'll call it, "A summer sales-a-lot."
Feedback, anybody?
Stanley?
Has potential to be
your best idea yet.
That's the dumbest
thing I ever heard.
Damn it, Phyllis.
All right, everybody
out except Phyllis.