Hey. Ready?
Come on.
Show me excited.
Yes. Yeah, I'm
pretty excited, too.
Today, I'm headed over to the
job fair at Valley View High School
to find some
new interns.
Want to get
some fresh blood.
Youth-anize this place.
Hey, we doing this thing?
Yeah.
Oh, my God, Darryl. You
look like Barack Obama.
Everybody, I'm
dating Barack Obama.
Why are you dressed
like that? Like what?
Like you're applying
for a loan?
Maybe he's going
to church or court.
Figured I'd look
presentable. Yeah.
You went
a different way.
- I think you look nice.
- Thank you.
Okay, here's what
we're going to do.
I am going to instruct the kids
about management and sales.
Oscar will be in
charge of accounting,
Pam will be
eye candy.
No, and also because
that is your alma mater.
Darryl will hire some
kids for the warehouse.
We don't have to worry
about internships with them,
because they definitely
ain't going to college.
What college did
you go to, Mike?
Let's go!
Today, I am meeting a
potential client on the golf course
because Ryan put
me on probation.
You remember Ryan,
he was the temp here.
Yeah. And it is not a good
time for me to lose my job,
since I have some pretty big long
term plans in my personal life with Pam,
that I'd like her parents
to be psyched about.
So I'm about to do something very bold
at this job, that I've never done before.
Try.
Mr. Maguire, it's
been a couple of years.
Hey, Jim. How are
you? Nice to see you.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
My grandfather would be
spinning in his urn
if he knew that I was out
here with a Dartmouth boy.
You take that shirt off right
now, or I will take it off for you, sir.
I am totally and
completely kidding!
Andrew
Bernard, Cornell, '95.
Phil Maguire,
Dartmouth, '74.
Got some blistees.
Yeah, you do.
Hit about twelve hundred balls
last night in preparation for today,
so hands are
a little tender.
It's actually not funny at
all. It's incredibly painful.
Yeah, let's make it interesting.
Say, 10 bucks a hole?
Great. What are
we talking? Skins?
Acey Ducey?
Bingo Bango Bongo?
Sandies? Barkies?
Arnies? Wolf? What?
I'm going to take this petty
cash that I got from Oscar
and turn it into
next month's rent.
So many
memories in this old gym.
Pretending to have PMS, so
I didn't have to play volleyball.
Pretending to have PMS, so I
didn't have to play basketball.
Those were the days.
Little over the top,
don't you think?
Show them what
you brought, Mike.
That's all we brought.
This is all we need.
We'll see.
Yes, we will see, Oscar.
We will see, because a blank sheet
of paper equals endless possibilities.
Conceptual.
All right.
We are open
for business.
Hello.
Andy, you're up.
Let's go.
Giddy up.
Let's do this.
People assume
I'm great at golf,
but, like everybody, I hated
golf lessons when I was a kid,
so I used to just hang out
with the sailing club instead.
Got my knot on.
Damn it!
Guys, do we have
to stay all day?
I mean, Michael's gone.
Can't we just go?
Yeah, and I finished
my work months ago.
Okay,
excuse me, people.
It has come to my attention
that some of you have forgotten
who is
in charge here.
When Michael is gone,
Jim is in charge.
When Jim is gone,
Andy and I are in charge.
When Andy is gone,
you answer to me.
Okay?
Excuse me, where do
you think you're going?
Oh, no, no, no.
You are not leaving.
No! Stanley, do not
walk out that door.
If you walk out that door,
so help me, I will...
He left.
Last time I checked, the American
work day ends at 5:00 p.m.
You will all stay at your
desks until that time.
Or you will suffer
the consequences.
What consequences?
I will tell on you.
There is some filing,
restocking of the supply shelves,
replacing the water jug,
which nobody likes to do.
We eat a lot of cake.
Cool.
Yeah, and, you know, you
basically learn how an office runs.
Hello. Hi, can I
talk to you for a sec? So...
Excuse me. This is
Michael, my boss. Justin.
Hey. Remember what we talked
about in the car, on the way out?
"Only the best
and the brightest."
He's nice, and
he seems interested.
He's totally
wrong, Pam.
Hey.
How you doing? Listen, I don't
think that a handsome, funny, smart,
funny-looking kid like
you should limit himself.
You could do whatever you want
to do. You could be a classy janitor
or a cashier
with dignity
or a migraine worker.
Maybe, for you, paper
should be more of a hobby.
Sorry for wasting
your time.
Oh, no problem.
And he signed. Did he put
his name on the piece of...
Okay, that was supposed
to be a blank canvas
on which to put
their hopes and dreams,
and he just made it into
a stupid piece of paper.
We need another one.
Immediately.
Yeah, the booth
is lame without it.
I only brought
the one.
Are you mental?
Michael, do you remember
you specifically told me
to only bring one
sheet of paper?
You said it only takes one
sheet to make a difference,
and I said, "Are you sure, Michael?"
And you said, "Pam, Pam, Pam.,"
and then you sneezed in my tea, and then you
said, "Don't worry, it's just allergies."
Do you remember that? I don't.
Okay, I'll go look
for another one.
And that is why
I need a smart intern.
Hey, so, how's the direct
mail business going?
I can't complain. People
love their junk mail.
Now, are you getting all
your paper from PPC or...
You know what, Jim? I'm not really
looking to change things up right now.
I just came out here to get
out of the office a little bit,
so why don't we
just play, okay?
Absolutely. Will do.
So, I guess I'll just
work on my short game.
Hello there.
What is this company?
Well, it's funny that you should ask,
because it's really more than a company.
Dunder Mifflin Paper.
Thanks.
Okay.
Damn it, Oscar.
Yeah, I'm trying to lure
these kids into my booth,
but kids are very wary
of being lured these days.
Thank you, Dateline.
Thank you.
Extension 128.
Hiya, pumpkin,
it's Creed.
So, we're gonna
ditch this bitch. You in?
Are you out?
No.
Pumpkin's out.
Let's go, gang.
My old art room.
Oh, maybe
it's still here.
No, no, they must have
taken it down. Never mind.
What do you want? Michael,
I know you're swamped.
I just thought you should know
that everyone in the office has left,
except for Angela and I.
Do not worry, though. I
have taken down their names,
and I have docked
them a personal day.
Who cares? I'm not there, Jim's not
there. Why should they have to be there?
So, what
else is up?
Mike?
Thank you.
What is this?
A piece of paper. This
isn't Dunder Mifflin paper.
This is some sort
of Pendleton crap.
Well, I think they'll
get the spirit of it.
Pam, Pam, Pam!
We're dying here.
I want you to go back to the office,
and I want you to get the real stuff.
I want you to get
ultra white card stock.
Are you serious?
Yes, and don't
call me Shirley.
Okay.
Damn it.
You could just pick it up,
take the triple bogey.
Yeah, I'll get it out.
Thank you. Yup.
Oh, man.
Come on, Tuna.
Hey, can't really
talk now. What's up?
Just checking
in. How's it going?
You know, we'll see. We'll see.
I just drove 20 miles
round trip back to the office
to get Michael a single
sheet of white paper.
So, I could've just had
them fax it to me, I guess.
Oh, I like you.
Talk to you later?
Yeah.
All right. Bye.
All right.
I'm sorry, I've got to
annoy you one more time.
What if I bring down
shipping costs?
You can try. But I've
looked at your prices.
Even with
free shipping,
doesn't work.
It's just... It's not
in the stars, Jim.
Six. Yeah.
All right.
All right,
race to the next hole.
Winner gets ten bucks.
Wait, wait for me!
Shortcut, shortcut.
I fell in the sand trap.
All of these jobs suck.
I would rather live jobless
on a beach somewhere
off the money from
a large inheritance
than have to work in any
one of these crap holes.
They suck.
Hey, game over.
Just-in time.
Just-in case.
What's your last name?
Polznik.
This just in,
Justin Polznik.
Justin is the ugly girl in the movie,
who takes off her glasses and she's hot.
And you realize that she was always
hot, she was just wearing glasses,
and that you were
the blind one.
He's the most important
thing in my life right now.
I want you to meet
my family. Come on.
Oscar Martinez, accountant
extraordinaire. This is Justin.
Hi.
This is Darryl Philbin.
Isn't he big?
And you already met her.
Pam Beesly, office hottie.
She will do you.
No, no, but she has already dated
two guys in the office that we know of,
so this could be
number three.
You never...
Excuse me.
Come here. I would
never say this to her face,
but she is a wonderful
person and a gifted artist.
What? Why wouldn't
you say that to her face?
So, what do you think?
Think these guys are nice?
The guys I didn't bring
are even better.
Justin, I'm willing
to commit right now.
Would you
do me the honor
of spending the summer
with us at Dunder Mifflin?
I think you
are very special.
You didn't
want me before.
That's what
you said.
No, I didn't.
You misconstrued. You
were kind of a jerk to me.
And I'm going
to go now.
Why don't... Hey.
Bless you.
Thank you.
Okay, Jim, you owe me $120.
And, Phil, you owe me $230.
Let's open a tab, because you and
me are going to be playing more often.
Count me in.
Nope.
All right.
Okay, you had some fun,
and I think I paid for it.
So let me just get
my last shot in there.
Is there anything
you can do for me?
I'll tell you what.
My fiscal year ends in
two months. Let's talk then.
Sound good?
Absolutely.
Good playing with
you guys. Right on.
You know, it's a tough thing,
seeing a grown man take six shots
to get out of the sand trap, but I
had to give Phil credit for not quitting.
Which is what I told him.
I also told him that
I don't quit, either.
And I'd call him every single
day until he gave me his business.
Which he then did, after fifteen
minutes of me blocking his car.
So I am now
his paper supplier.
And I shot a 102 today,
so I'm feeling pretty good.
The job fair will
be closing in five minutes.
Eighth period will
commence as scheduled.
Hold down the fort,
I have to do something.
Excuse me.
If you can hear me,
I would like you to look
around at all these companies
and know that none of them
are good enough for you.
H&R Block? Come on.
I mean, I don't even
know what they do.
Frank Regan Funeral Home?
Too much formaldehyde.
The Air Force?
Air Force is cool.
The refreshments? Bush league,
you know? That's not what you want.
Dunder... Okay, I see security is coming, so
I just want to say, come to Dunder Mifflin.
Dunder Mifflin,
a great place to work.
Anybody? Show of hands, anybody
want to intern at Dunder Mifflin?
We do not offer college credit,
we cannot give you any sort of pay,
but it is a really fun
work environment.
Anybody? Show of hands.
Damn it. Okay.
I'm going to wrap it up here.
Thank you for your time.
And drive safe!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You realize
you are taking out.
I can't...
Beers?
You closed it?
I closed it.
Yes!
Congratulations
to you, sir.
Thank you, thank you
very much. I appreciate it.
Well done. Nice job. Thank you.
You know what?
Screw this.
Today,
I did something stupid.
I questioned myself, and
I will never do that again.
Because I look at somebody
like Jim Halpert,
and I think that guy could
do anything he wants to do.
He could do anything,
and he chooses to work
here selling paper.
Just like me.
Yeah. Kiss her.
Kiss her good.
Hello.
I was just wondering, what
kind of jobs do you guys have?
Are you interested
in graphic design?
Yeah.
Can I fill out
an application?
Oh, absolutely.
Here, take a seat.
I should let you know right away
that this is just an entry-level job.
It's really basic. We're
looking for, like, a self starter,
someone who can
meet deadlines
and pretty much just
go the extra mile,
I guess.
I can do that.
Great, and, obviously, we're looking
for someone who knows Photoshop,
and Dreamweaver, Corel Painter,
Illustrator, After Effects, all the basics.
I don't know
any of those.
It's actually not
super complicated.
I mean, I'm sure there's some sort
of adult education classes in the area.
But if you're really serious
about graphic design,
I would think about
New York or Philadelphia.
They've got amazing programs
out there for design.
New York
or Philadelphia.
Yeah.
All right. Cool.
Well, thanks. Sure.
And I'll look into
those. You should.
New York or
Philadelphia? Absolutely.
Okay. That's
where the action is.
Thanks.